Waiting for it to record.
Very good. Thank you for joining
us, Steve. Really appreciate it.
I know you've got value. Your
time is very valuable.
No problem. I will just
start if Stevie can introduce
yourself and your role.
What you do?
Certainly so my name is Steven
Spiller. You can just call me
Steve. I work as a senior
software engineer in the Xbox or
get Microsoft. I work in a
little team is called. Let's not
so little anymore, but it's
called ATG, where the Advanced
Technology Group. And our role
in the organization is to help
game developers make the best
use of the platform of Xbox.
And then specifically, I work in
networking and multiplayer
systems. So. So
yeah, I've titles are having
trouble or they need advice or
they are behind this severely
behind and they can't get their
stuff to work on our platform.
Our team is the one that helps
them out and save the day.
Exactly on the. It's not as
interesting on the networking
multiplayer side, but the on the
graphics side. Those are the
guys that really help titles
tune on our platform so they'll
be able to take.
Basically traces the games
running, evaluate them, and
offer back tips that can help
them run faster so they'll get
games to run at least in the
previous generation. You know
all the way at 1080P instead of
only 900P. Things like that.
So really our goal is to make
all the titles that run on
Xbox the best they can be on
Xbox. I think that was our
motto at one time.
OK, now, well, I think
that answers the first
question of please tell
us about your artwork.
Can you tell us a little bit
about the industry that you're
working? So. I mean,
as being at Microsoft, I've done
a lot of things in a lot of
different areas, but most
recently we can just stay with
video games industry so the Xbox
stuff is what I've been working
on since 2013.
So the last seven years.
And mostly as a.
Is what Microsoft provides
platforms and services for
game developers.
And see I mean, it is a fairly
large industry, right? You've
got billions of dollars and
millions of millions of gamers
across the across the world. And
that's what we're trying to do.
We're trying to make things
better and easier for gamers
across the entire.
I don't know panacea of the
world. Good way of saying that,
but we want to make everybody.
Everybody's like he's here.
Is there any? I'm sorry, is what
other kinds of work do you have
to do in your role?
So in my role, I'll do things
like answer simple questions on
it. We have a.
Let's see that developer forum
that specific for Xbox Partners.
And so if they have issues,
that's one of the first places
they'll go, so I'll do a little
time answering those, and those
can be from really simple
questions like is this supposed
to work like this too? Hey,
we're getting a crash in this
very strange situation. Can you
help us figure that out? And so
I will investigate issues that
have been reported by external
developers. I work directly with
the platform team so the people
that actually, the ones that
wrote all the code.
Like I work with them to get
things figured out and resolve
bugs, find gaps in our our
solutions. I'm also developed
samples and demonstrate best
practices for using the platform
and our services. So like if you
want to know how to do
matchmaking, multiplayer
matchmaking through Xbox Live,
we have specific examples and
lots of documentation that I put
together to help with that. And
then of course if people still
have issues they can come
straight to us.
Because we do work straight not
just from forums. We will also
engage via email lot more on
teams lately over the phone,
video conferencing, but will
also go straight to.
And sit on site with developers
to help them get issues resolved
or to help them get their game
working on Xbox is.
And I've I've done that several
times. Which is it's kind of
fun. It's very busy though.
We also deliver content for what
used to be in person
conferences. I don't know. We
had to cancel the last few and
turn them into digital only and
I don't know what the future
holds as far as those go, but we
have several annual conferences.
Directed around Xbox developers
in gaming and we provide
educational. Training and.
However, there you know Doug,
discussion sessions and Whatnot
where people actually come out
and and listen to us talk, which
is just kind of fun.
I think that covers almost
everything I do right now.
Think that also covers the
different people that you
interact with in your job,
wouldn't it?
Yes, so I mean I do a lot of
different things as you could
tell right? And those have
different people I work with, so
when we're developing new
samples we want them to have a
consistent look and feel. So we
actually have designers, graphic
designers that help us design
the UI flows and figure out what
the scenarios that we want to
show. Program managers who
actually are the we call them
the butt on the line. So the
people that actually own
features that are responsible
for making sure that they're
status distract correctly that
they're doing the right thing.
All that work other software
developers obviously, and then
we have another special type of
person in the Xbox Org that we
call developer account managers
and these are the people that
actually own the relationship
with the different publishers
and Whatnot. So we have one
person that owns Electronic Arts
and so when Electronic Arts has
any sort of problems, they need
to do something they want to ask
about future plans. Anything
related to this? They talked
their damn and then their damn
will be the one that often
Contacts us with specific
issues. Or other problems they
might be having, or if they just
want advice on things, runs the
gamut. And then those roles are
internal people. Then of course
externals, which I think falls
more under your clients, yeah?
Alright um.
You can you tell us about
your interactions with other
IT professionals.
I wasn't quite sure what you
mean by this, so I mean I have.
There's five people I might
immediate team or my peers, and
we all basically work on the
same thing. Then we roll up.
There's a bunch of teams like
mine that take on the different
areas of Xbox. So you add audio
graphics. Ours is networking.
Systems and CPU and things like
that, but then of course you
have the whole platform side of
things where the guys that
actually write the OS they write
the special Xbox layers on top
of things and we interact with
them quite often. So you
wouldn't have much interactions
with other club with the clients
directly or investors, I would
say. So most of the work
I do is direct clients.
So either through a forum,
through email, through teams.
You know, up and up and up to on
site visits. Yeah.
Yeah, but some of that would be
facilitated through their
clients DM as well. Yeah, so the
the DMS will will set up what we
call an engagement. So if
there's a real problem we need
to set aside time to actually.
It's going to take more than a
day or so to look at this.
They'll set up what's called an
engagement, and then, depending
on the level of that and then
other factors like, where are
they located physically?
Travel restrictions, things
like that. So if there's a
developer that's just down the
street and there are some that
are like that, we will just go
there 'cause it's easier.
Other times, yeah, we can do
things over the phone and over
email and that that actually
works out fairly well and it's
nice 'cause it has a paper trail
so we can go back and reference
this stuff again. So anytime we
go and we solve problems, we
figure something out. We have
this big knowledge base.
It's really a OneNote now. We
stuck all this information and
so we can go back and search for
it again. Sometimes the easiest
tools are the best tools.
Think it So what would you find
that you spend the most time on
in your role at would be the
networking side of things or
more solving client issues?
That is almost like a sine wave,
right? We will go from where we
are doing nothing but working
with customers and right now is
one of those times we have the
new launch of the console coming
up in a month and we have a ton
of titles that are all trying to
certify they're trying to get
their stuff updated to the new
platform work so there's a lot
of people all working in with
new things all at the same time,
so we're quite busy.
Answering questions and helping
people figure out that how
things are supposed to work.
These days they were already
started about that new Xbox. I
know it's great, isn't it? And
then on the other side of that,
so you'll have these big lulls
where people just they've become
familiar with the platforms and
the systems. They don't have
issues as much anymore where
there's just not a lot of work
going on. 'cause you know it is
somewhat cyclical as to when
software or dog software
specifically, but games are
released. During those times we
get to work on what we think of
is more forward looking items,
so we will have incubation
projects for new tools, new
ideas, new services, as well as
being able to do work where
we're building up new samples
new. I'm trying to think new
middleware projects. So one
thing that we don't offer a lot
of his middleware and by that I
mean things like the unity and
unreal engine's. A lot of
developers go to those because
it it's pre cat has a lot of
stuff so we work with epic and
unity to have Xbox platform
support built in for everybody
and so sometimes we will do
things like that. In fact, just
recently one of my colleagues
and I finished adding a new
platform piece that's called
play fat party on Xbox which is
a pre canned voice, an
networking solution an now
that's something that you can
choose to use if you use.
In real you gonna say Yep, I
wanna use that piece. You check
the box and basically it just
automatically starts using it
'cause it's built into their
engine. So we do some of that
work too and that's a lot of
fun, right? That's when you're
spending more time coding then
troubleshooting and other times
it's more troubleshooting coding
since it's actually one of the
things I like. It comes up
later. I think a lot of us would
like to spend more time coding
than dealing with some of the
clients. Yeah, there, it's it's
really hard. I mean, I've worked
in a lot of different types of
groups around Microsoft and no
matter what, there is never a
job where you're just spending
all your time writing code.
There's just too many other
things that have to be done as
part of the process of shipping
software that you can't get away
from. What aspects of your work
would you find most challenging?
So what I find personally most
challenging often is.
Trying to understand each
different developers actual
needs so a lot of times they'll
come and say Hey I'm trying to
do this and it's not working
right. Can you tell me what the
problem is? And well, yes, I
could tell you specifically why
that isn't working, but this
seems like it's a symptom of a
larger issue, right? You may be
doing something at a more meta
level. That's incorrect as far
as the pattern that you should
follow. So we really need to
spend the time or you know to
understand what the goal is.
What are they trying to achieve
and what limitations they have
so that we can then find the
right way to solve that problem
for them or to help them solve
the problem. And then of course
you know things sometimes that
works out really well and
sometimes you go on and on and
being a global product sometimes
is challenging just with the
translations. So some things we
have where I'm saying.
Trying to say like when I work
with the Japanese developer, we
have an intermediary that
translates back and forth for us
so well like all type of
response, they'll go in and
translate it. The other person
will then type their response.
That'll get translated back and
it's kind of interesting, but
you can lose a lot easier. That
looks a bit in translation, so
yeah, it does make it take
longer, and sometimes you just
you don't. It doesn't come out
in translation exactly. You do
lose what it is. I had one on
from like, oh, I thought I saw
that they were asking for, but
then they came back and asked.
Yes, it came back a slightly
different way. Like oh OK, I
guess they meant this other
thing and so that can be a
challenge. Um? But Secondly, the
with the complexity of all the
systems and how they have to
work together like you wouldn't
believe how many things are
involved from you. Sit on your
Xbox sending an invite to one of
your friends to play a game and
for them to receive it and join
and be able to play. There are
many many steps and different
systems that all the things flow
through. Sometimes it is really
hard to find a root cause,
right? You'll say, Oh, I have
this problem. It's it's showing
up. Because of this, the user
won't sign in correctly, but
it's not actually assigning
problem, but it actually turns
out that that user is part of
this title group that has this
special properties set that only
works in this other situation,
right? And it takes 510 people
sometimes on an email thread
just to figure out what the
what's supposed to happen, what
is happening and how we can fix
it. I'm glad that showed up. And
to be fair a lot of times fixing
it means telling the title
developer that they were doing
something wrong, so it's not
always our fault, but I usually
take that. Angle first that I
take the assumption that it's
something that our stuff is
doing wrong and then let people
discover that it's not
necessarily the case. I think
the end users will just blame
you guys anyway, wouldn't I?
Yeah yeah, sometimes it's really
hard to read Twitter comments
because the lack of actual
understanding is frustrating
when you read some of the things
I say. Yeah.
Finally, can you show finally
for this group of questions? Can
you share an example of your
work? The best captures the
essence of the IT industry or
your role they suppose.
Yes, So what is the essence I've
when I thought about it, I came
up with the definition that was
it's basically utilizing
technology to accomplish tasks
or to get work done. And if I go
by that I would say that when we
were developing our samples and
it sound well I didn't really
giving you the scope of what
samples are. Samples do range
from like one code file that
just does something really
simple to a full game. We have a
full game. That example is a
sample for a bunch of different
things. Which is a lot of fun to
work on. So by doing that and
having those out there, when we
developed them, we developed in
this that they would pass our
own certifications that they
follow all our own best
practices so that it's a working
example of the right way to do
it. And nice thing about doing
that is that a lot of developers
will just take that code
directly and they'll make it fit
in their engine so we know then
with when they take that they're
taking code that we've developed
and tested and we know will pass
certification and they're just
using it. So it's it's kind of
win win and I think that's
actually one of those
synergistic things where you
gain more out of the end
results. Again, with the effort
that was put into it initially.
It also makes support easier for
it as well. I'm sorry you said
again, will also make support
easy for it as well if they're
using your examples. So yes,
yeah, in fact, that's one of my
favourites. Goto is hey, I'm
trying to use chat and my chat
doesn't work in this situation
like well. Can you load the
sample and see if the sample has
the same problem right? The
samples the same problem then?
We're probably looking at
something had changed or broken
the platform and we can
investigate that way if it works
in the sample then we can narrow
it down to OK. Well, it must be
something in the way you're
calling the code. Let's focus on
that work and in so yes it does.
It does help a lot.
I'm going to leave the last few
questions for Mattie to answer
up to ask and go from there.
Matt, Are you ready?
Hi, I'm just for the sake of
simplicity when it comes to
audio, I'll just ask the next
few questions which came from
one from each of us. So Daniel
wanted to know do you work from
home at all and if so do you
prefer it to working in the
office? Or if not, would you
like to work from home at least
some days? Yes, so current
situations aside, I had been
working about 5050 between home
and office. And I found that to
be a really good balance for me.
'cause I do enjoy the comfort
and convenience of being at
home, right? I can just get up.
I have everything around me.
It's it's simple, but there's
times when I'm working with
people directly or we're trying
to troubleshoot issues or I need
more equipment than I have
rights at work. I have a stack
of Xbox Dev kits that can
utilized in many different ways
to do things at home. I only
have two and it's.
You know I can't do as many
things and it's more difficult,
more time consuming to do
certain things, but I do like to
work from home and I will keep
when we do openoffice backup.
Stick to our 5050 style.
That's that's a surprising
answer, because I guess we might
have thought you would have
worked mainly in the office
before covid. But yeah, that
does sound like a lovely
balance. Um, so Adam wanted to
know what aspect of your work do
you find most enjoyable and why?
The things I enjoy the most is
when I provide a solution or an
answer to somebody and they come
back with oh thank you this
works. I've been working this
forever and I could beat my head
over and you solve my problem.
Thank you so much, right? So
when I help people solve
problems. That's just that's my
favorite thing. That's what I
enjoy the end up getting the
most enjoyment out of. I mean,
there's personal satisfaction
with doing your own projects,
and these things like that, but
when you, when somebody
physically tells you hey, you
solve my problem and helped me,
I really like that. Yeah, that
must be a lovely feeling and I
think we can relate when we're
able to help someone out. And I
also really enjoy the fact that
my job is so eclectic at times
that I'm not in the same rut of
doing the same things.
Each each task each problems a
new challenge, almost, so it's
it keeps it interesting.
So you like the variability?
Oh Uh, so my question was, what
advice would you give to someone
who is just beginning to study
or work in the IT industry?
So it's gone a long way for me
is to find areas that you're
really interested in and then.
Kind of saturate yourself
with that.
And really, the biggest the
biggest thing you can do to help
yourself is to do it hands on.
So if there's if you think that
you know configuring and running
server farms is going to be fun.
Go out to Azure or someplace
where you can get free VM space
for tinkering and do it. Do it
over and over again. Try
different things, break it
because you will break it.
Figure out what you did wrong.
Basically. Now give yourself a
sandbox to play in because that
immersion is what, at least for
me. Makes everything else come
together more easily.
Sixense Oh yeah, so um practiced
I just study.
Right yes. Anne Shannon wanted
to know, do you find it hard
keeping skills slash learning
up-to-date? So there's a That's
a yes or no for me since we are
providing we is Xbox, Microsoft
provide new services and new
technologies all the time. It's
just kind of part of my job to
learn and know that is that are
being developed and has we're
supporting them and helping
other people figure out. How do
we use them. But I don't have
alot of time to invest in skills
outside of my job right now. So
if I decided I wanted to learn
something that's unrelated to my
job, I would really have to
spend most of my private time to
do it and. It's just I mean, if
it's something you really love
then great, but it's harder to
invest in something that you
don't know will pay off when
it's taking up that much of your
time. In my situation so it can
be hard, but it can also.
You know, if you put yourself in
the right position, they didn't
just come along with the
territory. Do you find that's a
result of. The release date
coming up and covered or is is
that always the way with your
job over the past seven years?
Ah.
It's it's been more
lately, obviously.
It's the way I do things, like
when I find something that I'm
interested in and I want to do
it. I'm just going to do it
right now. That's why I choose
to spend my free time on if that
happens to be learning new
technology, then that's that
works out. In that case alot of
times though, I tend to want to
go back and. Do things that I
would find more relaxing I
guess, so doing more retro
things, going back and playing
on the old Apple that ers 80s
old game console programming.
You know something simplistic.
It doesn't have to go anywhere.
It may or may not help you in
the in what you're currently
doing, but it's it does still
help you. Or if it helps you
bet. Yeah, you keep using your
your skills fresh. I guess the
more you do different things,
the easier it is to switch
between things. And, Um, George
wanted to know what do you think
are the most important skills
and attributes for a job like
this? I'm sorry that means, like
my job specifically, then we're
looking at having strong
troubleshooting skills, good
knowledge of relevant
technologies, so most games are
written in C++. If you don't
know C++ very well, you'll
probably have a hard time
understanding why certain things
do certain things because you're
not feeling with what side
effects are or how memory is
treated and what not. Equally,
if you're not familiar with
rest. APIs over the web.
You could easily make a lot
of mistakes.
So basically, uh, patients
and. The dedication to be able
to complete tasks. That's one of
the hardest things I find
between myself and a lot of my
programmer friends is we all
have a million side projects
that never get done.
If you can actually sit down and
make yourself go through the
process of doing everything to
completeness, that just makes it
makes it easier because you've
practiced it and your life will
be better anyway, because you
won't have things coming back to
haunt you as much.
So you'd say dedication and.
A good understanding of.
The skills that they the job
requires initially and are
going. And patient was another
good one, sometimes it's.
It's really hard. You'll and one
of my colleagues was having this
issue today where he just
couldn't get a problem that
somebody reported to reproduce
even with their own code. And
he's like I just don't know what
to do anymore. I just don't. I'm
stuck. Like, Well, let's just
keep going through it and you
just kind of keep trucking and
eventually things pop up or you
figure something out. But if you
put it aside or you.
Yeah, you kind of give up on it
then you obviously can't do that
too much when you're getting
paid for it, but.
Anne helps overall, yeah, and
Sam wanted to know what new,
what new skills do you think
will be in demand in the
industry in five years?
Oh well, the big future
investments these days are
around artificial intelligence,
machine learning and big data
processing. In games, especially
machine learning, and not until
just for games, as in like
gameplay, but systems that are
in used to make games. So I mean
a game is really about moving
and manipulating large chunks of
data over and over and over
again. So if you can have a
computer that can use a machine
learning Type, 2 minute can look
and evaluate. Hey, I seem to be
loading these chunks from this
specific place on this interval
in this mode, so I'm going to
self optimize this. An prefetch
things that I think are going to
come up and by simply doing that
you've all of a sudden increased
your load times for your game
and for other things. As an
example, AI would be more along
the lines of if you having
smarter. Systems to you
in the. Player interaction
systems. So the computer is
doing more and the players doing
this or the creators are doing
this. It's if you think about it
as when you're developing the
game you you know there's a
certain certain way you go about
doing things and you try to
optimize for what you think are
going to be. The most common
scenarios, but you don't really
know what those are going to be,
and even if you do find the most
common scenarios, what if it's
only 60% of your users and the
other 40% are having a less than
perfect experience using
something like Emil?
The software itself could make
the determination and
dynamically pick the best
optimizations for you, instead
of having to statically choose
ones that you hope are the right
ones ahead of time.
That's great. I think that was
all the questions we had.
Um, did we want to ask any
follow up questions to those or
we all happy with bash?
I think that was really
informative. So much for
that, yeah? We really appreciate
your time and I'm not sure how
long we've been recording now,
but you've just come home from
work and put in the extra effort
for us, so we really appreciate
it. Thanks Rob.
I love to help. Like I said, I
volunteer at my local high
school and help the kids there
with programming classes. Great,
that's fantastic. Well, I guess
we won't talk about take up
anymore of your time and just
hope you have a lovely day.
And I have a nice relaxing,
lovely night. Anything you want
to ask again, or for any reason,
whatever Adam can get ahold of
me. Yeah, if you want to feel
free. It's been great getting to
know you and learning about your
work. Steve, thank you so much.
Thank you. Thanks you too.
See ya.
It's
frozen.
Thanks.
Yeah, it's alright.
The guy from Xbox should give us
some good marks. Oh yeah, yeah,
we'll put him to put him to
shame. Obviously hopeless like
the recording. I'll just Shannon
just sent a message. I'll ask
him if he wants to Join Now.
Did you wanna stop the
the meeting recording? Yeah.