So I mean research the rest.
So after a quick idea is that
for both Android and iOS, that
will evaluate a individuals
privacy settings that they have
on their various social media
accounts, be it Instagram,
Facebook, Twitter, we chat. Or
we can always expand add more
later Ascential E the user is
going to give us permission to
access their social media
accounts with their details to
which we will then check their
privacy settings. For example,
like on Facebook there post
public, are there Pictures
public that don't need to be
besides their profile pictures
and then will make
recommendations based on what we
found? We can't actually change
this. A lot of the settings for
them, so the idea is that will
say hey, this is bad. This is
bad. This is bad and here are
some videos that we can link you
to on that we've created on
YouTube with a step by step
tutorial showing them how to
resolve those security issues.
So basically it's going to just
do a. Security and privacy
checkup. Yeah cool I mean Yeah
it also push them notifications
and push them notifications if
their privacy agreements with
the social media platforms
change. So like Facebook forever
changing their privacy settings
and making it harder to turn off
some things and easy to turn off
others. So when that happens or
they've changed it, so saying
that, well, we're going to share
your information with this
company. Now we need to buy the
user of that. Cool, I get to
yeah. Do they update those terms
and agreements just all the time
in the background and just don't
tell anyone where they normally
give you like this little Gray
message bar up in the top. Do
it. My lot of people when
they're signing in. Just click
dismiss. Yeah, well, you just
get that notification and you're
like oh that's not one of my
friends whatever and in there
it's like oh we're gonna tell
everybody that you own a house
or if you agree to this we own
10% of your house 'cause nobody
reads the yoga so we gotta make
sure it like we check those.
And maybe say hi, you might not
like this anymore because they
are, they're giving your
information to these people.
Yeah, yeah, because if you still
need to use the app, you just
have to accept it you. But yeah,
most people would just after you
want 10% of my house. Fine you
wanna use my text phone number?
That's OK you got me in a corner
here. Yeah I still need to talk
to those people in those cat
means I just can't live without.
Yes. Sorry,
you're happy too.
Drop a graph, a draft of what
you think that might look like.
Daniel and then share it with
Adam. I'll try and have a draft
done by our next meeting, so
then we'll be able to do that in
the last 30 minutes, like 4 days
to get it all over scratch
because we've got a fairly
simple project idea which we can
really hash out pretty quickly
on for the project plans.
Yeah. Discover
type yeah. And I'll be
available next Saturday, but the
one coming up so.
If anyone else had available,
maybe we'll hash out some last
minute things 'cause I'm sure
we'll have some as well.
Yeah. Really good idea. So my
mentioned that in Ms teams so
that everyone else knows that if
if they are available on
Saturday we might have a last
minute thing. And then it's
probably due Sunday night, isn't
it? Yeah. That's why we
gotta get some. Read all the
spelling mistakes on the website
that I just copied and pasted
it. I do that for my job so I
could help out there. I've
looked at capital of times and
like how did I miss that? Don't
know why. How did word miss that
spelling mistake? I'm telling
you there's not much squared
picks up on.
This would be right if it was
American spelling. Change the
setting like fix, fix, fix, fix,
fix. I'm so I've gotta add
an ideal job section. Don't
lie to the web page.
For yourself or know for
everyone for everybody. And then
I'm thinking the home page will
be the comparison. Was like I'll
do a tab style like the other
industry data where it's got the
individual ones so you can click
their names to just get their
ideal job summary. That's just
the paragraph where it's like
this is my ideal job and then
we'll do the comparison on the
main page I guess. Yeah, no. I
think the comparison was just
know know the because the
comparison is worth 2 points. We
were just going to try to
paragraph. I think Daniel you've
already done. Yeah, I've got
mine. Mines currently in the
personal information section
like profile section. Just
another paragraph at the end of
those profile personality test
things. Yeah. So just a
paragraph saying how?
Our job is similar to or
different to the other peoples
drugs. Yeah, the questions are
in the in the PDF and summit
too, so the graph or the diagram
or something or other was on the
industry to answer because
that's worth more.
That makes
sense, Adam. I think
we kind of concluded that that
could still be some are we. We
started to Draw Something up,
you contributed to it.
Meeting Typing
into the yeah yeah.
And for
skills. Necessary for a job.
Las data, yeah. I think we can
probably have it.
I different able to that as
well, which just lists which
skills I think, sort of which
skills are needed. While he had
like our names and then the
skills and then ranked like
which skill is important to
whoever's job you were gonna
generalize the skills in the
groups, won't we?
Yeah, like communication and
stuff, yeah. Different
jobs. Yeah, I know they kind of
blurring together and they
didn't have to make it to Jen
and make a table for us for
that. That's what I meant, but
I'm not sure that that covers
the burning glass stuff.
Yeah, I'm not. I'm not sure if
that would get us marks per say.
Yeah, 'cause that was prior that
was us putting in what our the
job we chose on the previous
assignment. What each individual
skill on that chart was rated
based on what we thought the
employer would. 'cause I think
there were three sections of the
burning glass data where they
had three different tables for
the different criteria that the
data was looking at.
Yeah, so if we group if we make
a table or chart that basically
uses that same.
Like the same criteria is what
how they listed that data. We
could do a table that way.
Yeah yeah yeah I will.
'cause it is, as long as we're
presenting data that looks like
it was from the burning gas
starter, it's really our
interpretation of what our job
requires. Different skills.
On Wednesdays, we can, we just
do another like read through of
that section and just spend 10
minutes just literally reading
through what the questions are.
Then we can all.
I think as long as we've all
done are burning last stuff.
Well go through data, format it
on the next meeting. Yeah,
that's good idea.
Yeah, yeah.
So by Wednesday.
And they will have.
Each of our individual things
done, except for maybe some of
the group project technical
stuff between Daniel and Adam.
But you'll have a draft ready by
then, Daniel. Technic reflection
basically as much as I can do
until I just get out of my
depth. We all have a working on
as well. Yeah, so it will have
all that writing done by then.
Basically yeah, hopefully
actually. Yeah yeah yeah, I
think that's the writing
sections assigned to everyone
basically and then just be a
formatting issue. And that is
how we throw formatting graphs
and adding the technical details
and then the uploading to the
website. Yeah yeah,
yeah. Yeah, yeah.
Do you want to live?
The door saying.
Will wrap up the recording
there, shall we?
Recording again. Yeah,
yeah. His condition count as
another meeting. I think it's
it's a meeting. Yeah, yeah,
Sweet Yeah Alright.