Have been ready
so this is
meeting number 66.
Meeting #6, so the first
item on the agenda is any
resolutions to the actions
of the previous meeting.
Do we have anything that
we needed to bring up? I
think it was the project.
Was one of the actions for
the last meeting.
Yeah.
Burning glass stuff as
well, yeah.
Which everyone seems to
be OK with the burning
glass. Then anyone have
any questions about it?
Maybe half a can in Laura
Unlikeness.
The was it Shannon or Sam's
talking to about the burning
glass stuff yesterday about.
I was just for the young.
I know it's terrible.
So we didn't come up to it. Come
to a conclusion about ranking
the titles, did we?
No.
So we might.
Or I still think.
Um?
With all the individual tabs we
have for ourselves, its economy
gives you like what your job
title is and then and then you
can kind of for mine. I found
how many vacancies there were
available in Australia. I just
don't know whether that would
just suit that first line.
So the problem I have was
trying to.
Yeah.
Yes, I can't hear anything.
Can you tell who it's
coming from?
No.
I said I can probably
incorporated Graffy said
with or seen with quick
mind with Daniels.
Gone now.
Yeah, sounds like it. Yeah,
yeah sounds like it. Yeah,
it's already intermittent.
Good morning Daniels and George
is it's kind of.
I I have a value of how much
like Dragon Season Australia.
Sorry. You were coming
out of it.
Is that me that's doing it?
If you're not talking, just
mute your microphone and
that'll minimize any noise.
Yeah.
Almost switching my hand.
Alright bye bye.
Yeah, so I think the only way I
can be incorporated into a
graph is if everyone could find
like how many job vacancies
available for their specific
job title. And then I could
just do that simple number
thing.
But I don't think it's kind of
necessary as long as everybody
in their own individual tab has.
Say how many jobs Alvin?
Tell me.
All that job title are currently
being seeked in Australia. It
should be fine for it.
Title for the requirement.
Is that from burning
glass the vacancies?
Now will the burning glass.
Often it's it only lists other,
but I was talking to Mattie
about it. Only lists like that
OPS 17. And a lot of our titles
aren't even that top 17.
Doesn't even.
Sorry.
Even the top one only really
represents point 8% of all jobs
that are seeked, so it's.
I'm not too sure where to use
it. For the skills, I think
glass is fine, but for the
titles I couldn't find it
useful.
Yeah, I found that it didn't
actually specify what it was
ranking it didn't. It didn't
tell us what was big. It kind of
gave Obeid description and then
no vague title and no
description on. What
was being rated 12.
One to 10 or 1 to 7 or
whatever it was.
Yeah, the burning burning glass
stuff was stuff they got from
two years ago.
But to get like the more
comprehensive data, and like the
newer data more up-to-date, you
had to pay for it so.
Yeah, I guess we'll never know.
So do we wanna attempt
to help? How how heavy
heavily is it marked?
Because we could, we
could attempt to look up
how many jobs are going
for that specific title.
Which seems like the most.
Likely to given it likely option
to give an answer, but also
still not easy to do, so I'm
thinking if it's not rated
highly. Perhaps we could
give a description of why we
can't possibly find that
data accurately.
Thought.
We could just use like
Glassdoor or seek or
something and then just do
like a list of how many jobs
there are listed on those
websites.
The criteria for industry
data makes up 10% of the
overall mark.
So for you at least get 5% of.
That would still be alright.
Mostly covered with.
Um? History of early visual
ones are already on the
other tenants. Georges in
mind we all have jobs.
Yeah.
I think that might take that
first line, as long as it's
listed in Virgil. Say like this
is my job title. This is how
many vacancies Australia, but
she's at the first line that
says. How did the IT bills
required in your skillset rank
in terms of demand?
Yeah, that's The One.
Like the one with before
that, wasn't it?
I'll be back in a set.
No worries.
So.
In terms of demand for
employers.
Thank you, keep going
quiet, Shannon.
It's.
Is Shannon going quiet for
anyone else at times?
I think I think it's just the
connection thing. Yeah.
Sounded OK, no, I could
hear. OK, yeah.
Alright.
Shannon, sorry. There yeah.
I don't know why my.
Is that not too bad now?
I sound like.
That's good, I don't know why my
main volume on my mic just keeps
on automatically adjusting
itself. It's really annoying.
Sorry kids fell off
a bit of furniture.
You're right.
He's got a bleeding lip, but
he's gonna sit here with a
tissue and you'll be alright.
Sit down and play over
there, right?
I'm. With that had each of these
rank in terms of demand from the
employees. That's just referring
to the burning glass data. Hey,
I don't think I don't think it's
any need to go look for some
outside data on that, and I
think it just refers to skills
as well, not the actual job.
Yeah, it's just one of those
burning data. PDF's is how many
yeah blah blah blah yeah.
It changes all the time, so
you know even if we use the
burning glass data, it's
not not going to be wrong.
Affecting right yeah?
Yeah. I'm sorry this blaster is,
but is that OK? Yes, one.
Otherwise, will pretty much have
to make your own burning glass
starter to answer the question.
I'm OK with you and with like it
if it's only 10%, I don't think
there is really expecting us to
do that much work on it.
I think it we've done done
pretty well like so like the.
Graphs on the website.
Yeah, is that you that
the Shannon or is it?
Who did the graphs on
their website?
They are all made by put those
together. Yeah, those are really
good. Yeah, you can get little
animations when they first pop
up. You can select each person
as well. It's really cool. It's
just a a library I grabbed off
the Internet, a JavaScript one
that lets us do it, and then
Shannon went through and put the
data in it. We at the customize
it a little bit for how we've
laid out the site because of how
I put everything into those data
folders to make it easier to
edit so it hasn't ended up.
Yeah, it's just one file that
you need to edit to change the
data in the tables.
OK, 'cause I I change mine a
little bit 'cause I didn't know
WhatsApp was then I researched
your business like probably the
most important thing for the
integration officer. So yeah I
change my stats a little bit
but. It's pretty much one or two
lines you've gotta change in. I
think it's JS graph JS dash
data. It's just and then you'll
see all the data plots in that.
Also, stop updating anything.
So he could probably even
show you he's worked it out
quite well.
Yeah, I will have a look
at that later I guess.
So we're moving on now.
Yeah, pretty much covered.
The hell walks.
Search Mark, just keep sending
them for some reason.
Yeah, I think just the
individual tabs were missing.
Adams Maddieson Sam's.
I think at the moment.
Sample text
hi, uh, industry data were
missing mine. Anne Marie's ideal
jobs were missing Marys or she
wanted. Just put it up and
Samuel. So so my ideal job in.
Industry data was sort of
together 'cause I was using the
burning glass data to compare
our jobs. So we've gotta break
him apart. So the ideal job is
just basically copy and paste in
summary from assessment one.
And when would you like your
alluc comparison against like
the skill set of the other
team members, chosen jobs?
'cause I thought of doing that
in my burning glass one as
well, so I could probably cut
that bit out and put it in the
ideal job one or I think
burning glasses just mostly
just against that data, not
against the other team
members.
But it's kind of weird.
Yeah, 'cause I thought the
easiest way to compare a
different positions was taxi.
Use the data 'cause I didn't
really, otherwise I would have
had to research a lot of what
your jobs square and stuff. So
it was the most efficient way
for me. I've learned the easiest
way for that is you just
research the title and just get
the description or summary of
the title. And that's pretty
much everything you need for the
ideal job. Like summed up in
like 200 lines.
A summary of Google.
All right, we'll move on then to
deliverables and progression
reports of for each person's
been working on.
Anyone wanna start?
So when you say
deliverables, deliverables?
Individual bits that we have to
do so like as not not commits
the total part of what whatever
task assigned yet.
So I think I've besides the
contribution slash group
aspect, I think I've done
all of mine. I just need to
put them on the website.
But what you concluded when you
were going through them today?
Yeah.
Yeah yeah, OK.
Say I got at least two
to upload.
Website for.
Well, I hope to do some of
it tonight and latest
tomorrow evening.
Girls with covered Samuel with
these deal job are the project
that's coming along quite well.
Don't Daniel posted some.
Yep, sections of that already
have started plugging away at
some nights. Yes.
I've done like 3 sections out
of out of it and I'm just
working on the Descripcion now.
I think I think all my other
content in other parts of
websites all sorted out, so I'm
just going to knuckle down and
start working on the
description.
I started to get it done.
I think I've done tools and
technologies and then I've
just got to elaborate on
those and then the skills.
Yeah, Yep Yep Yep.
Then that'll be done.
Do we have any? Did we have any
references or was it just the
two? Yeah, I've just got two
references in the motivation I
can I can for some more in there
I'll I'll see should I should I
look for some references to the
like the tools and technology?
Because I'm just going off what
I know. Online.
Yeah Yeah, 'cause I like for
my assessment. One project I
gave him no references 'cause
I was just like you're gonna
need this this, this and this
and this yeah.
I don't, I don't know.
No, I got. I got funny really
good. I was really good on that.
Oh well, thought it out like
quite a low. Yeah, yeah, I think
just having the two references
is fine by me. I think there are
you in this time. We really need
a reference as if you're.
Talking about someone else is
work, so someone's done like
research or something. So if you
were doing. If you like
providing statistics or
something from privacy breaches
or something as part of your
motivation, but you need to cite
that or reference that. So yeah,
I've got two references in the
motivation that I just copy and
pasted for some abstracts and
just squeeze them in. Pretend to
type on that.
Chief something that's not
yours. You need to reference it.
Yeah.
Wait for you something
that's not else.
Yeah, yeah, so if you're using
someone else's research or data.
Hi.
Or if you're trying to.
Create your own argument or.
Solution using or basing it
on someone elses stuff 'cause
I don't think we need ref
references for the materials
that we used on the website,
I don't think.
I think it depends 'cause I
think they can just look at
where we where. I've grabbed him
from 'cause I was pretty
descriptive in those comments.
More academic.
I don't think they're gonna
really care if you grab
stuff off Wikipedia and
then reword it.
Alright.
Do we want to review
anything that we put on the
site like assessment
criteria wise? Anyones
unsure.
I think if I think of take
pretty much over.
I have a question.
Um?
I see that you've put the the
discord link on there. Yeah, we
surely want to include that
because they seemed quite
explicit in writing to not.
They didn't want discord because
they wouldn't be able to get the
history of the channel.
Where? We've got the history of
the channel in that in that
archive, so pretty much when you
join a discord server as a user,
you only see the history from
the day that you joined and
forward where on there with the
bot we've got a history from day
zero. So we've got.
All that that they can
actually download keep.
Anne. Yeah. Which is why they
wanted us to use teams because
teams doesn't actually delete
anything and they've already
got access to just say
whatever we've been saying.
Yes.
The only thing with the
discord archive it it does
have like a comments where we
were looking at the other
other team members websites.
That's market research
though Yeah.
I mean, every few things are I
was like Oh no, I don't know.
We should be saying that in a
professional setting, but
well, that's why I put it down
that it was used as an out of
band communications tool for
general discussions of minor
issues that were two minor in
nature to presented a meeting
or general feedback and
support amongst team members.
An off topic discussions.
Just.
Put it in context conversation,
yeah? 'cause like I say, you're
developing a game there like
you've got your meetings and
then you've got your like your
one on one meetings again so you
know with other developers and
and like you pass along ideas or
you'll be using like a chat
service to pass along ideas
amongst each other and they
don't necessarily document all
of it. I've got where they can,
they they do. And I'll mention
it in like a ticket. Are you
know, discuss this with with
someone so via email or on
Skype. Here's like a transcript
kind of thing and eventually it
does kind of make it into the
the the code vault, so to speak.
'cause no one likes meetings.
So we can leave it or we can
take it. Does what people want
to do on that.
I don't mind.
Wasn't sure sure. I'm sure I
read somewhere that they
said they absolutely didn't
want discord, but.
What are red?
Maybe unlike the.
The canvas they posted
something.
On the assessment.
Now find it.
I.
Do not use SMS, WhatsApp,
Facebook, we chat, select
discord, etc.
I think it as weather
switch page.
Page 3
face 3.
20 members, so it's .4 on
Page 3 or messaging between
team members should either
use Microsoft Teams or are
most email.
Well.
So tonight when to sign in some
point in the event that there
are difficulties amongst team
members, other communication
channels have proven to be
insufficient for arbitration and
moderation by army staff. That's
the only reason I bring it up
really. 'cause they seem quite
explicit there, but I'm not
phased if we included. It just
might be a markdown for us.
But it might not be.
I don't know because we didn't
really use it as a main thing
was kinda just a side thing.
That's why I thought like
whether we include it or not.
They have used teams a lot.
Yeah yeah stop.
Like is there any anything
in discord that you think
should be included?
Well, that's not really
important discord.
Important or not important in
that kind of thing, it's.
If we know anything except for
the Sega, complete for
completion, 'cause we're yeah,
feedback based off like website
designs were mentioned on there.
Rather than making a full
meeting on it on on teams.
I don't think they wanna go
through like. Redial, I mean
like I don't think he's got
all the relevant information,
they only want to. We can ask
him tomorrow.
Ask him. Yeah, told him
last year.
What was next?
That the class if you want.
Yep.
And with everyone details so we
can give him that bro.
And everyone's managed to
use GitHub.
I'm still struggling. I'm going
to help George after this
meeting with it, so I've got my
document already, sorry.
Our kids, when I've looked on
the contributors for the on
the page, there's only four of
us like Adam, Shannon, Daniel
and myself. So if you change
because it's only going to
show you the contributors for
the master repo.
So you actually see him all
you've gotta change in the
branch, change to one of the
branches or click insight and
then it's gonna show you the
contributors and buy based off
their commits. So I guess
give hugs pretty lacking when
you've got multiple branches
going, so I'm gonna really
track tracks to master.
Where was that on the website?
Just out of curiosity?
Yeah.
Our tools.
I haven't updated that graph
'cause. I'd be updating
it every day.
Yep, cool.
The the links to the commit
history which will show you the
individual branches and who's
been. Who's been adding what?
Yeah.
OK, and I saw your note about
that. Your comment
about it underneath.
That was good.
Now.
Kids that don't wanna go
to bed, sorry.
I saw your comment
underneath that
contribution graph as
well, Adam, so that was
that was good of you.
Trial doesn't accurately
reflect.
Hell.
Yeah.
Stuck in that answer.
I am any other questions, so
we'll move on again.
Were there any deliverables that
we've missed, or are we?
Network. Haven't missed any.
No.
Out all traces down if you. If
you haven't submitted something.
I think Adams put a space
on the website for every
question that I've sort of
seen on the spec sheet, so.
Yeah, seems like we covered.
We can do a final run through,
maybe read through the Rubric
on our last meeting or
something in mark ourselves or
something like that and make
sure we don't miss anything.
Then after the Saturday.
I'm eating it will be pretty
much just to run through by
everybody through each page,
checking for typos, spelling
mistakes, and reporting him to
that the teams page. So I'll go
through and I'll fix the typos.
One big final commit.
Sweet, what do you solve it?
Do we all have to submit a
copy of the report or we all
just ordered one person? I
wasn't sure on that without
end explained it.
I don't know. I haven't read it.
Says that.
One person from the groomer
system, both files.
It's actually a number as a
group test about two falls.
Heidi just one member has to.
A PDF Ms teams info.
And then the actual.
Full formatted PDF report
GitHub Page, link to website
version and repository.
And then I think we all
submit a copy of the
contribution sheet. I didn't
look at that one either.
Yeah.
So moving on, are we?
Checking
it's easy to understand, so
you're all good with the logo.
With a group project. Do you
need any help?
Description if you wanna have
a read over, you might wanna
reword something 'cause it
probably won't be hard to
judge it up a bit and get a
few more marks. 'cause my
writing is pretty mediocre.
The more eyes on it the better.
You think really?
So do you wanna? Once you've
uploaded a more finalized
version, do you wanna just post
in the comments?
Uploaded it.
Files there in Ms teams and it's
on the website for like the
three sections that I've done,
so you're welcome just to make
notes straight on that file. In
Ms teams, I mean, you just
change the whole lot. You don't
even have to ask me. You can
just do it well. So are you
editing it within Ms teams? Or
you editing it externally and
uploading to Ms teams? Whenever
I change something I do all of
it at once so it's all on the
same version lab. I do the
change the Ms teams file, then I
update. The website and I check
a file, a copy of the Ms teams
file in the data section of the
Master Branch. So yeah, so
it's, uh, it's always going to
be all up today. OK, so if we
make any changes, you'll
yeah.
Yeah, put him on the Ms teams
section of project ideas. 'cause
I I realized when I uploaded an
unfinished version of my IT
technology, I wasn't sure if
anyone had contributed to it.
Anyone had typed on it so I
thought Oh well.
With the.
I'll put it up with edits where.
OK, I see. But no one had.
Never mind, ignore what I said.
Hello.
Ideal industry data cover
that is there any new agenda
items that we need to raise
in address today?
When do you wanna do the group
reflection? That's Saturday at
morning and afternoon.
In the last two meetings.
Sarah.
Some people can make the morning
meeting, but not the afternoon
meeting. So we'll have to get
their information and whichever
meeting they attend and try and
relay it to the other members.
And then put it on the side.
Sorry, miss you kid, I
was smiling.
So is the is the plan to still
hand it in Sunday, midnight or
are we going to hand it in
until? Tuesday, Wednesday, or
just whenever we finished, I
guess. Anthony's kinda hinted
that the you know that we looked
on very favorably if it's
limited on the original date
versus the other date.
But they wouldn't confirm if
would get extra marks or not.
Laughing.
I think it would be. I don't
think they'll be extra marks,
but at my unprofessional, if
they told us outright then that
would give extra months for a
good mood when they're marking
it. Yeah, and and and submitting
hours on the due date like
'cause? That's kind of a
weighted scale for the whole the
grades they give it to the
class. If we get it first, yeah,
it'll look good.
They can't really Marcus hard
and then them easy if you know
what I mean 'cause then.
Yeah. Yeah.
I'm happy to see it in original
day. I've seen the other sites
that we can find which it
doesn't look like many of even
got a website yet.
Are you guys active on the um?
The class discords.
No.
Not looked at it at all.
Yeah, it's pretty quiet.
The class discord that
the one I'm on anyway.
I can't think of anything else.
Are we leaving the red push
button on the final submission?
Yeah. I think a bit of humor
weight lose us any points.
Yeah, should we query to see
if any Anthony or Tim are
possibly epileptic?
Before.
With that button.
It's not, I think, are in my
table frowned upon. Is killing
it, killing the shooter without?
Come grading time, yeah?
Strange yeah. Ask like off
the cuff link now. By the
way, you have liked it.
This is a question like do you
have to Kim? Do you think it's
important to take into account
when writing software? If the
the user could possibly, you
know, be epileptic and may have
a fit you know. Do you have any
experience in that there but not
like so? It's an indirect
question, but to get the answer
out of him, yes.
I could ask if you like.
On the agenda.
Just just don't be flexing
before you ask how you got
a new iPhone.
Can't even use it
all right, why not?
Face for it and I'm scared that
I'm going to break it.
Like that, that's not
the right way to Flex.
Try not to.
Alright.
Question and answer time.
That's about it. I think
we're pretty much done.
Great. Have any
questions, things?
The kid goes. Do you have a
question doing what do you
wanna ask everybody?
Leah.
No, no, they don't wanna
play yet.
Dakota.
Would you like them to play
with your cars?
Hey Daniel, you want Daniel to
play with your car?
Over in 10.
Yeah, he wants you to play with
these cars then. What about any
of the others? Anybody
else, Yep.
Apparently everyone's invited.
Alright, so we'll wrap it up.
Bing, at least.
With the PDF report.
So is there any way like we're
gonna bring everything
together? So will everyone put
their their contributions on
the word doc or something or?
I was going to work on the
PDF, but I might do it
within teams so that you can
have a look as I go.
I was just kind of waiting
for a soul to get out stuff
on the website.
And all the finalizing done so
that any spelling mistakes that
we fix will be correct in the
PDF as well.
So I think we I do put some
template stuff up for the PDF
fonts images from the website so
they kinda look the same.
As well.
Do I need to make the
background Gray?
Nope.
'cause it might look a
bit weird.
Get wood and it wouldn't
print very well later.
Push button in the PDF.
The push button.
I don't know if you don't say
yes. I can try. I could say I
can look into that if we can.
We can't do it. You can't do
much that changes in a
period. I think you can
change your background.
Stop.
You don't need my boy
taken away.
Alright, so we'll finish
the recording.
Good meeting.
Yeah.