Right, yeah? Cool, just quickly
run through the gender that I
set out the progress report on
the content as the project I
dear update, just sort of a part
of the first one and then review
and confirm group roles that
content calls. If we feel like
it then just general group
questions and issues. Maybe
questions for Tim and schedule
next meeting. For the next
meeting. But yeah, I don't know
if we can just go buy one by one
and report on the.
Progress of the content that
we've done. Section.
Yeah, I guess we can go
section by section, yeah?
Yeah, I did a quick run through
before and it looks like we've
started all this sections that
we can't 'cause. There's a
couple like the feedback
feedback in Group reflection.
Gotta wait until Week 6 or 7,
probably Week 7.
But we may decide on pretty much
everything. So we I think
looking in a decent position.
But I'm pretty focused. It's
running a meeting so I don't
really know what I'm doing,
sorry. Well, I've come, I
haven't started too much
of my section my, you
know the four different.
Things we have to do.
Yeah, I haven't done much of
mine 'cause I was doing some of
the weekly work. I haven't even
seen this weeks meeting from
Anthony just yet, so I haven't
actually made much progress at
all.
Really.
Yeah, but I what weight is it?
Do you I forget?
We still have like another three
weeks, I think or.
We're doing pretty good
considering, yeah, other people
don't have groups yet.
Yeah. I started the website.
Yes, it looks good I.
I haven't actually looked at it
yet. I haven't added the team
profile pictures. I just took
yours Mattie from canvas.
'cause I didn't get back till
just now. So sorry that's
alright. That's The One I gave
you anyway. I just went with
like two different colors of
Grey 'cause I didn't know what
colors used wanted to pick.
I can change that at any point.
I don't what was the little
animation I've oh it's a little
PAC man. Yeah.
So while I do the content in the
background so it's actually
ready to display rather than you
see half loading pictures, it
will just display that until
everything is ready to go, and
then they'll receive the whole
page in one here. Oh, that's
that's cool. Yeah, is that like
a JavaScript thing? Yeah, I
commented all the code there,
'cause in case you guys wanted
to use it. So you can just read
that and write the comments, and
it's all explains what I'm
doing. Retain profiles when you
click on a picture, it's going
to open up a like a window on
the page in JavaScript and then.
You should be able to say that
if you go to that and just yeah,
it looks great. Love it.
Yeah. It's amazing.
So I thought, you know, we might
as well add some class to the
site. The other team's a little
bit. Maybe will distract him
with all the fancy stuff it does
anyway. Write anything and just
give us full marks.
No, you didn't put any of
the flashy. Strophic strobe
lighting on there. Yeah Oh no,
not yet. Not yet. Not so work in
progress might be randomly when
you click on one of the team
profiles, it'll just load up a
disco ball in the corner and
just. Like a disco.
So has anyone had time to work
on their pieces?
Uh, yeah I I did my cloud
service services and serves
servers. Uh, yeah I am
researching. For that for the
last three days, right?
Got some echo from you
George. Yeah I know I can
hear myself with a little.
Alright, I'll do this hello.
Translator
No. Sorry,
but no.
I don't know. Is your microphone
too close to your speaker?
I'm just using the fine now.
I think maybe the connector
came out a little bit and it
was using the speaker audio
or something, yeah?
Sounds better, yes, better now,
yeah. OK cool yeah. Well, I've
been researching that for the
last three days and I've done
all of that. So if you're
anybody wants to have read in.
You know, have any like a
feedback on that? I'll be good.
Uh, yeah. So I just done that
and then I did my profile as
well. And what was the other one
IT? The one with the other
section that we had to do the
questions no the other one are
the ideal job. Sorry yeah.
Yeah so. That section of me
it's it's done so.
How did we want some?
Oh was that the?
Was that the research part of it
or where you had to include
statistics? Or was that the
other part that you mean? No,
not the other one, the other one
just the one this summer. Just
like it. Yeah, the summary of
your ideal job, yeah?
That's cool. Are
you are doing cloud services?
George yeah. Yeah, so anyway
anyone wants to have a look.
They have it right there.
Well, nice.
You have to make
sure you put your.
Before we complete everything
left to make sure we put all
of our resources in.
What's a call references?
In Brooklyn.
In text citations
and all that
stuff. Your reference list is at
the Harvard standard.
Can you do?
Copy and paste those web pages.
I was gonna use the Harvard
referencing system at the bottom
after I used citement so it says
on the assessment like at the
end, like you specifically have
to use insight like in text
citation. So every time like you
mentioned. Someone else is
research or something you have
to do, like their name and like
the year or an even like
sometimes the page depending on
what it is. I hate that.
I will have lost marks for that
on my assessment one.
'cause I didn't do that.
Yeah, but it is usually only
like 5% of like that part of the
assessment or whatever. So if
you didn't like do it, then you
have run the last a couple
marks. But the rest of it
would've been fine. But like I
was like right at the end. Oh,
I'll just quickly do that bit.
Read it. You text item on
whatever you call it. I just got
yeah all of my websites
correlate to that data that I've
put in. So I'm just going to
copy them back to where they
meant to be. After you cite this
for me. Let's
go. Um, Shannon,
I think you did yours a few days
ago, didn't you? Your web
technologies? Or am I?
Sub Studio. Is that the
one I'm remembered?
Technologies,
yeah?
What did that sounds pretty if
you know yeah Sunday.
Just before the meeting.
Yeah. Obviously I've been
working on my programming at the
moment. I just had a chance to
get back to fixing some of these
files back up. You were a bit
ahead of us anyway.
Tomorrow.
FedEx relies and fix
it up and report.
Leah.
What about you guys?
So sorry.
Your web technology or will you?
Working on the idea, yeah.
I uploaded um section, my
section on the personal
information like the team
profile and then the little bit
like George about the ideal jobs
as part of the team profile and
I just got a discovery discussed
with Adam which parts of the
project idea he wants me to
write but we just give you those
up anything that's less
technical. I can write like
maybe the motivation or
something. How do we go in
studio? Find out whether we
could use Facebook allowed in
their packages. Adam. Oh yeah,
we can take a look at the
privacy settings that they've
set on posts and what apps
they're allowed that they've
authorized on their account.
That's what games they play, and
which ones they want to remove.
But we can't make any changes to
that.
Web. So
we can say it, we can change a
couple of things, nothing major.
And less we write an actual
Facebook app which then they
have to approve and goes on to
Facebook and then we can. But we
could still just turn around and
go. You've gotta change this,
this and this and this and then
just direct him to some YouTube
tutorials on how they do it.
Yeah, it might have to be based
on recommendations or like.
Here's where things look like.
Now we recommend this if you
would prefer your information
not be accessing these people or
body. Which would still
be valuable. So to speak that
yeah. Be pretty cool.
And it could still like. There's
still possibilities for other
apps, although I think they'd
probably be similar, wouldn't
they? Give you access to what
the settings are, but not how to
change? Yeah, that's pretty much
Twitter and Facebook. Both do
that. Anything Facebook owns,
which is lots of stuff.
And then Google would
probably Google owns a lot of
stuff, so they have similar
settings on across there.
Different things I don't really
have a social media platform
anymore for us to worry about.
No, I think they own social
media platforms. YouTube.
But that's.
New line.
Open up your lines Instagram
these days. Wonder
who owns
Myspace these
days? Yes.
Wasn't it a newspaper
company? Baby, I think the only
question is it is Tom.
My sweet. Yeah,
Rupert Murdoch's Newscorp
Fair
enough. 60% of
everything else so.
Facebook. You can use Facebook
to sign into Myspace.
I got a link
that data. So we're working
through some stuff and then
there's some things just take
time. Is there anything new
Daniel that we could talk about?
I don't think so. How long is
sort of everybody's happy.
They've gotta feel on.
How it's all gonna be completed
I guess like so to let the road
map to completion. Doesn't sound
right. Uh, yeah, covered all
that basis pretty much.
I think everybody's done a
question for interview.
Oh yeah, I've done. Yeah already
supported their originally. Just
ask for a new Xbox.
So
your. So
Steve and he said he is
available was at Friday night's
Australia fun. American top,
which will be Saturday for us.
What time zone?
For us time, what we haven't set
because we didn't have the
questions to give him yet so I
can organize that. Now we've all
done our questions. And then
give him a couple of days to sit
on him or something. Yeah, so
you're busy. You're busy this
weekend. Anyway, out of my yeah,
yeah. And I'm free Saturdays.
Next weekend, it shouldn't be
a problem, yeah?
Free Saturdays I'll be working,
sorry. I don't finish until 6.
It's quite possible like we're
not gonna be, will be there.
Yeah, I'm usually busy on
weekends as well.
But if I know like a like a week
in advance, I could probably.
Make time.
Yep. Happy to do that.
Or to put it into
perspective, the time that
we're going to have to be
out. It's currently Wednesday
in the US and it's 4:47 AM.
Yeah, so if we were
in the US.
Really washed in the US
is usually Washington State. 12
hours difference. Oh, it's like
17 hours ahead.
Like 17 hours ahead.
Behind behind behind
behind us.
Yeah, so I guess you just let
him set the time when we sort of
work around it, or we can get
like a time time block and work
around that would suits and
there were eight o'clock there
would be. 4 in the morning.
This is not my actual answer.
So I'm. I'm I'm not
sure I'm not able to calculate
that. I'm probably I'm working
Sunday morning from 8:00 AM.
Alright, anytime before that,
yeah, I'm free.
Like the following Saturday in
like 9 days or whatever, yeah.
Yep, cool. Time zones in such
a pain in the ***
I can have that can be an app,
you know that it can be a
project. I think there is an F
already really. Yeah, it just
depends how many ads you want.
Oh dear. I did
have a question for you Adam.
Yeah, I honestly did not
comprehend GitHub all too much
like I only enough to make the
basic website that you saw.
Yeah, so I think I think we can
ask questions. I think we all
need to upload a little bit too
GitHub. Um? With what you've
worked with, I'm not going to be
able to do anything without a
little bit of support from
someone. Because I won't know
what you've written, even if I
look at it, I won't understand
it. I don't know how to add an.
I won't know how to not **** it
up. We can do it tutorial at
some point if you lie using
teams I can just show you.
Show you how to do it.
Yeah yeah, thank you.
And, um, like whatever whatever
I'm putting out by imagine I'll
have it already written up in a
Word document. And I know you
can do. You can add to the
Reaper as you're going. It will
just update it and you can. We
can always rollback changes. Or
Daniel can always rollback
changes since he owns the repo.
So if you accidentally delete
anything we can get Daniel to do
a rollback and we can get it all
back and just not sure how to
add once they get a time, yeah?
OK, do you have GitHub pages
installed? I think it did, yeah.
Alright, when did you want me to
do show you how to do it or not?
Not until I'm a bit further in.
The content. No
problem.
We could probably do it on
discord. That sounds painful
with. Unload on asking. Sing it
without the other day. You gotta
change windows and it's like I'm
not gonna show you that.
Every talk something new pops
up. You'll change screen share,
yeah. Screen screen.
Show conversation
Rachel and. And.
Going. Traffic to share content
I'm guessing. Oh, there
it is.
I do something.
Girl shuffled now.
And it's not.
'cause I I wrote all of mine
in the space of four hours
with just paragraphs and
headings, paragraphs and
Headings. So other than that,
I have no idea what I'm doing.
Set alarm Yeah, I can see
you won't take long. I don't
think so. I just figured you
didn't get the chance to draw
last night.
Yes.
Reported.
2000 E.
Used or Ms teams. Features yeah,
yeah yeah it's important. Plus
in preparation for.
Yeah. I don't know how to get
rid of it.
Oh, there it is.
Area. Fun room.
So is there anything else we
need to go over?
It didn't. We do need to make a
bit more time.
Just to get to that 25 minutes
so if we've got nothing to talk
about, maybe. So just to
confirm where we're still
meeting meeting every
Wednesday, say 3030.
Yep.
Don't know. What we
gonna do another another meeting
needed round, round or weekend.
Technically done 2 already from
Sunday. We've done 2 already.
Eating 3. Wait, so we
can possibly wait till
next Wednesday now?
Will even. When do I
wake up last night?
I'm just saying for this week
just scheduled groups organized.
So people are still organizing
groups, so so just do one this
week. Yeah, so I don't know when
the count from assuming it is
Sunday to Sunday.
So we done Sunday Wednesday, so
we have fallen for this week.
Thank other groups are about the
same where we're at as well.
Yeah. That's good to know.
Plus, I think they'll, they'll
say, like the progress we're
making, or like how far ahead we
are considering other people
haven't got their groups yet,
so. Like if there's nothing to
talk about because we've each
allocated to us, and then we
currently completely number
then. What are they gonna mark
down for yeah.
So do we have a goal on what we
should have? We should complete
this week. Like what should be
finished? Yeah, that's a good
question. One of the goals can
be locking in the appointment
for interview, so I'll have that
done. And I'll try and get my
report done. I'm about.
Half mostly like over halfway
through at the moment, so I'll
try and Polish that by the end
of the week as well.
So running reports done by
the end of the week or by
next meeting.
We could do it next meeting,
yeah? The next meeting Saturday.
When's Day currently?
Um, and that like we can. In
that time we could go over each
other stuff and do some.
Corrections in.
What not?
But suppose I could have a team
profiles section done. By
Wednesday as well, yeah, most of
the content done for team
profile. Now we just need a
four, yeah? Format as I still
need to post my summarized
profile, but we can do that
tonight or tomorrow morning or
something. Did we wanna have the
ideal? The part one of the
ideals job? Ideal job section
done by then as well or leave
that till next time? Just it's
just a very small summary of
ideal types, not the not the
research data part.
Profile section of. Yeah yeah
yeah yeah that would be cool.
Ideal job go under our
individual profiles. Is
that going under its
own section altogether?
Rules summary part that goes
under the team profile section,
which is just just when we
compare our ideal jobs to each
other, yeah. So you thinking
Adam, that each of our
individual. Summaries go under
our photos like you've already
put those through and then
comparing the jobs would be a
collective page. Yeah, just the
page with that graph where we
don't really have to summarize
the jobs too much. I'll just
link back to the profiles for
the different job names.
Yeah, cool. Yeah, and then for
the industry data section where
we look at that burning glass
stuff, I think we can just or
answer the couple of questions
that are on it.
You just don't do that sort of
separately as well, and then
Chuck it all together. So I
think that's got some like a
personalized question section as
well. Which yeah, I
don't know how much.
I will let's just two minimum.
Well, I got the 100 words.
What did you say Shannon?
For that one was talking
about with the ID.
Industry data. For the audio
jobs. Mine currently sits at 200
words. I don't know whether
that's you know like if you had
all six hours together. It's
1200 words for one report.
Plenty for Tim to read. Yeah,
sorry gonna read it.
Yeah, like I've covered covered
everything in a small amount of
Wordage it's not.
I mean, I'm sure he knows what
most jobs are. What's what's the
mark for that section? Has a 10%
combined? Then I think
that's just fine.
I think we could all do that.
And then we're gonna add the
graph, which will probably bump
it up a bit.
Stop Spider Web graph.
I think we do.
Everyone has the industry data
we can build that graph from the
industry data into the yeah.
Yeah, ideal job in the profile.
That's the way we're doing, yeah
yeah. They wanted.
A variety of resources, so like
one had to be data one had to be
description in one had to be
like a graph or a photo or
something. So getting a bit of
variety would be good. So I
think that's covered if we just
keep it simple with the writing.
For 10% Mark, I think
we're really focusing on those
web technologies.
The project idea.
Yes, I feel bad that I never
actually looked at the website
and just look at the report at
the end. General.
A PDF report at the end I just I
don't know. I guess they just
click through the website really
quick and they wouldn't really
be reading anything. Just make
sure all the links work and
stuff. I think I think I heard
that they used to only do it
through the web page, but then
people's Web pages wouldn't
work. So the PDF is there.
They've done, yeah.
That's what Tim said about the
assignment one. I mean, when I
legit took screenshots of my
website. I just want select all.
I just formatted a little bit so
I didn't look all.
Doesn't know messy and just
submitted that 'cause I was like
I'm not rewriting any of No I
did it the other way around and
wrote it all up in there.
On the Class I discord people
were saying all they did was
submit a PDF that basically said
the link to the website. The
link to the repo, their name in
their student number, and that's
OK. No content.
I mean, you could copy how she
male coding in there just the
content there, yeah? Yeah,
well, I just gave him the
URL so it's like OK.
No, you definitely needed the
whole script in already, but I
can understand why they thought
it might have been just given a
link and the basic information.
No. So are we good for
this week? Were there any other
questions? Just questions
pertaining where that any
questions for Tim tomorrow tell
us any other thing.
Anything? Just the.
What Adam said last week, like
whether it's possible. Doable
for the. Um, for the next
project, although. Well after
that. Know how to how it had to
be feasible. Algorithm idea, we
can change it between the next
assignment as well. I we asked
Adam the other night Anthony
yeah yeah so it's not set in
stone that we do it that we have
to have the idea now for the
next ones we can just change it
as we go along.
OK. As long as
far.
Wait, what? Bots teams?
Set the Polish guy. No, honestly
wouldn't know how to say that I
like. Yes, we have to make this
thing. I think it's finished all
the modules already. I think he
finished them three days into
the course 'cause you know Bart
stuff. Of course before. Yeah,
that's what I read in one of
these things. He's done of
course, but then had to drop out
at the end, so he's already done
it like it was cherry picking
his team members there was like.
'cause I was looking through
week three stuff in week four
and seeing that he'd answered It
on the 30th of August.
Incidental waiting for the
day we started the course.
Yeah, have you guys seen
that movie about whether
the interns at Google?
Oh, is it the fence? The yeah
yeah yeah that one you know that
guy that made at the first day
that's going around picking the
best team members in his ****
**** Impression that I get
from bottom like that guy.
It is going OK. Maybe should
be should stop recording this.
Either way.
Sure.
She's sharing next meeting.
I guess I can share next
meeting. All on Wednesday, so if
there's another meeting before
then, I probably won't be
prepared for that, but.
Next week next Wednesday, I can
share. Cool and recording
that yes, lovely.