And we're recording.
Beautiful closes meeting too.
Now you see I probably put a few
agendas on what I thought would
be pretty good to go through
tonight because of last night we
got up to. Well, pretty
much got down.
Sorry.
Pretty much got down to the IT
work. IT work part.
Now laser, although
obviously I see as the main
marks for the assignment.
So I see where we pretty
much discussed Adams already
got someone in mind that
murders coming up with
questions, so that's pretty
much taken care of.
So moving down IT
Technologies is something
that we should really.
So the way I'm saying it is
what a group of six. We need.
Four of those reports, plus
the project idea. So I was
thinking breaking it up into
one person per report, plus
two people on the project I
did.
If that makes sense.
Because each of these reports is
like 1200 words and I think
yeah, one person. Each one is a
bit. There.
Sorry, what did you say saying?
So we have to do for these
reports, but it's the kind of
low in terms of word count,
so I think if you have
multiple people working on
each report, it's a bit
inefficient actually, yeah.
I'm sorry I can go yeah
of 'em up later after
after I've already done
well on cyber security.
And then, like Maddie said,
she wouldn't want doing
autonomous vehicles.
But then again, I said it's just
a rough draft and said you
import input would be nice
'cause my writing skills are
great. I'm more more than math
and science person. I'm not an
English person. Yeah, yeah we
can still collaborate a little
bit to Polish 'em up. So that's
right, I find Alright, Alright,
but I repeat similar phrases.
And I go back. I'm like
that's a bit repetitive.
Some, sometimes that's just what
you need on there. Some of these
for the word count yet, but they
are also, there's no lies.
So in the actual.
I don't get that from Oh
yeah, so how will this affect
you like it's 300 words so it
is pretty much personalized
to one person anyway.
I would love an electric car.
Not on this call.
To lose any other looking at
those headings, does anyone else
feel like doing any of that?
I'm thinking.
Like so who was into like
networking and stuff yesterday
someone in wanting to get
involved. Yeah I was getting
into that. Yeah network yeah I
think like clouds, cloud
services and service would be a
good one this if you're into
that. Yeah yeah I'll be keen
into that yeah so sorry so we're
going to be working two person.
One person for each report, one
person for example. Yeah and
then two for the roof idea, the.
Thing that we're coming up
with? Yeah, OK.
Probably collaborate on the idea
where I'm yeah yeah yeah.
Just talking something
that is in.
No, yeah I'll yeah I can do
that. Clouds and services.
So that's yeah, yeah, anyone
have an interest in any of
the others?
Might be interested in doing
the Blockchain One.
Yeah, yeah blockchain.
That's cool. Means still
understand more speculation
and stuff on that, so it
might be interesting.
Adam and Dan can start
working on the project idea.
I guess out we obviously
elaborate. Please not doesn't
seem too much either, it's.
But he was in there.
Does anyone have problems
with those or?
Hello, that works for me.
Alright.
Yeah, so cool.
Anyway, how should we go about
deciding what the project idea
will be? Yes, that's all coming
up now is only one think that
their individual idea was.
Obviously good enough
for the project ID.
I don't think mine was too
creative in my most kind of just
an app with. Information about.
A wide range of pets on it. It
was mostly just the invention of
an app which isn't too new.
Isn't brilliant idea.
What?
Yeah, my sister now.
That was super simple. Very
achievable. But yeah, what was
on your app? Daniel? It was
basically just like a notepad
app. Really it was just
ridiculously. Like I don't know,
High School E.
OK, 'cause I don't think we
actually have to make the app in
the next assignment. No,
'cause I was just looking at
which is much is next point
'cause the assessment 3.
Mostly moving on from that
project idea. 50% of the overall
mark of a 40% mark, so.
Like the project audio come
assessment, threes worth pretty
much what this entire system
it's worth. Oh yeah.
So we can get find something
half decent this time and at
least then we know we're gonna
have to work on income
assessments, right? 'cause we
need artifacts totally.
Oh yeah, something to prove that
we've. Tried to create
something.
Like a screenshot or
something like that.
Like a pre pre Alpha
build or something.
So we don't want something
that's too simple that we
can't get the word count
for in their next
assessment, and we don't
want something too
complicated that we can't
really make any artifacts
for, and it still needs to
be original, doesn't it?
In some capacity in some
capacity. Basically, we're not
ripping off an idea that's
already existed, so we're not
gonna make like a a GitHub
Clone or a discord clone or
something like that, yeah?
Fortunately, not a canvas
for this phone.
Or is it didn't say no do
that. He just said it would
be too complicated.
I mean my idea like 'cause I
wanted to make like a browser
based noise exposure timer for
like workplaces. So use the
microphone from your device and
if you're exposed to too much
loud noise, it counts down.
And then eventually, if
you're working too much,
it allowed environment. It
tells you you need a rest.
But I'm not sure 'cause my
knowledge isn't that advanced
in building that kind of
stuff. I don't know if it's
too ambitious or not.
Like we have to learn
JavaScript. You know how do
you know? Put like access the
microphone in a web browser
and all that kind of stuff. So
and then would have to stream
the audio to whatever server
that we're going to set up to
listen to it, to check the
decibel limit. I don't think
it needs to use a server just
like text this straight up.
Straight up information from
the microphone and counts
down on a timer like just on
the web browser.
But I'm not really too sure
about that much of that back
end stuff either.
It would just need to detect
when it would need to record or
store. It does store through
like a timer.
But when you refresh the
page, it'll be be gone. OK,
I've got won't store data
for a long period of time.
What did you have Adam?
I I have a like a timebank kind
of thing. Basically people
exchange skills for time and
then so they can get somebody
else to do something like know
your lawn or somebody fixes your
computer. They do trade one hour
time to do that which then.
The person that fixed your
computer gets an hour. They can
then say given out or somebody
else to cut their lawn, for
example. So Anon dollar currency
based exchange site visit
bartercard back in the day or
something. Yeah or skill
something or other airtasker or
similar out go on.
Go on. But without money, yeah.
So like replicate trade system
used in. Old time.
System basically, except your
instead of saying I'm going to
give you a goat for 10 chickens.
It's like I think you an hour of
my time and exchange for
whatever service you can.
Give me in return.
OK.
Go.
Sorry, I got a kid in here.
I shut the door.
Can chickens?
For.
Mine was like a stocktake app.
I don't know if you ever done
like Stocktake you use one of
those like arifi scanners. The
portable barcode scanners, yeah,
but you use your phone instead.
That would be pretty easy.
Yeah, 'cause they've
already got a barcode
scanner software built into
Android. Yeah, I was
thinking about like a QR
code or something, but
that's as far as I can get
like I need to research
more of like on programming
and how it will work.
So what what sort of what sort
of person or situation or
workplace would use that?
Supermarkets, yeah 'cause.
They're like $2000.00 each you
know. So if you can just like
get it on your app, everybody
has a phone so I say so broad
yes yeah yeah cool.
Doesn't sound too bad.
I wish I had more information
on. How to do these things?
Of course you could take.
Does it? Does it specifically
have to be like software or
something we have to develop? Or
could it be like a it can be
something we can make, like a
robot or something if we wanted
it like it couldn't be like her
like an auxiliary sort of
service. They go along with and
already made app or something.
Maybe not really bad idea.
North not could be.
Um?
It wasn't anything that said
it couldn't do that. Couldn't
be an auxiliary service.
Did you have something in mind?
Source.
I was just trying to think of
like is your ideas we could make
if if the problem is like most
of us don't have the technical.
Skills to come up with something
maybe? Something a little
bit less technical, but I
think the idea is more that
we if we do have something
technical that we have to
research it. So we learned.
So maybe we should come from the
perspective of 'cause it
originally we had to solve a
problem? Or didn't we?
Yeah.
Slash my idea. Yeah, however,
major and minor. the IT had sold
problem. I think it had to be.
Somewhat original.
So should we think of
problems first or stem off
of what we've already got?
Good question.
Do we have to pick one of the
ideas that we already came up
with an assessment one?
Yeah, we can choose an entire
new one. Yes, even assessment
three it says, been picking
entire new one, so we're not
happy with your idea
assessment too. We can just
scrap it and go again, OK?
Yeah. We could just say that
we want to write an app that
checks your privacy settings
on your social media sites.
Sounds like something that
should already exist, right?
A double check privacy on and
then it's even further down the
check processing all your apps
on your phone. Yeah, actual
things accepted that aren't
meant to be, which there be
privacy issues with say Facebook
allowing a privacy checking up
to look at someone's privacy
settings within Facebook.
If not, if the user gives
it permission to do so.
It's.
Seattle basically be logging in
under their name, having to look
around except in code.
Mexican tile install it never
like OK I want to authorize it
to access Facebook, Twitter,
Instagram, Snapchat and check my
privacy settings and then adjust
them or give me recommendations
on what I have to change.
Privacy is a concern for people
at the moment, especially with.
Like tik T.O.K going being
banned at right now today?
Again.
Yeah, yeah, sounds like a
naughty. And work on that.
I'm happy with that.
Yep. OK 'cause man gives us a
general idea on the 1st on the
assessment to weaken right?
You know it can be for the
Facebook and all then. Then we
can further elaborate with the
plans in the future of what it
can do magic and turn it into
an entire security system for
your phone and stuff. Yeah?
Story of what her we will
progress. I don't think we
have to progress it much
further than like an initial
stage. It's just a.
He is 4 port is PS4 pages of
what we're gonna do?
We could bounce that idea, often
Tim on Thursday and Stephanie.
He has any advice.
Just don't wear.
Session with him rather than the
group thing in case other people
haven't thought of an idea that
they want to go with you. Yeah,
yeah, yeah, probably a good
chance with just a simple email
through him should be fine.
Over. The next week, teams come
up with this new app. Check your
privacy. Another $10.
Now that sounds good, so
I'm fine.
Yeah. Yeah it does that soon.
As I just thought this whole
choosing a project would take a
lot longer time, no idea.
But when she got one, so
it's good. I think everyone
just had good ideas, so it's
hard to pick.
Like how do we do that? Or is
that too simple or is that too
complex? But the best bit
about doing an app as we
just do a mock up.
Like in Russia.
And say, Well, this is what we
researched. We can you know we
looked in how would connect with
Facebook or say Twitter 'cause
we don't have to? Look into a
mall just a couple to say that
we've researched it and like
possibly how will do it.
But we never have to
deliver functional Apple.
I think we need to say how it's
going to be feasible if it's
going to make money or not.
Yeah, I think people would pay
for it if it was like if it was
an automated system which would
have to be I think, and it could
easily be couldn't.
Do I just put at the end that we
plan on selling the app to
another company that wants it?
Because I don't have it.
But even if I, even if like it,
cost me. If it cost me $2 to
download an app that
automatically like I gave
permission to check all my
security, that's an income,
isn't it?
That's if you had to do it,
or selling it, or like we
wouldn't really want to do
ads on a security.
Would we? No.
Defeat the purpose of the
privacy protection.
Then there's the option of
subscriptions. Facebook
would probably buy it so
it doesn't get released.
We accidentally leaked the
source code.
The check clears just calling in
and its security is just. It's
so easy to write about 'cause
there's so many problems. So
many ways to fix it.
So yeah, that seems like it's,
uh, yeah, pretty easy to attack
that project idea cool. And if
we don't like it, we can always
change it for the next one.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, Yeah, Alright.
So this would be a good one is
like a concept.
Research anyway. Alright, so
we're at 20 almost 29
minutes, so we've got a
little bit longer.
Started.
From 5 two, I don't think I
don't know that no, we've
been recording for 28 almost
29 minutes.
Is that what you think?
That's yeah, I'm not
too sure that they can.
The recording actually started
from like a 5 minute point and
I'm just getting news on. Are
the cameras from when the
meeting started. Like
when players.
So I think we've only
been recording for 20.
Alright then, going off 'cause
I've got a little recording
thing saying. Madeline
Dupree started recording and
then it's got a timer.
The last one was only 38
minutes or something. The
last video file. OK, 'cause
it was definitely like 44
minutes. Yeah, when they've
been here for 24 minutes, so.
He started recording this
right here based off of what
you've got them.
So we've got a GitHub setup by
Daniel as well. Yeah, was that
OK? Did that. Yeah, that's fine.
Yeah, we need to make one
adjustment to it for the GitHub
pages. I don't know if you
notice that I did a separate
branch block server branch in
there for the website, so if we
can. GitHub pages at that all
the web code will go into that
branch and then anything you
guys want to submit to the repo
can go in default.
In the Master Branch.
'cause it will keep
them separated when you
check in and check out.
But it's basically just give
you 2 places to upload files
to. Yes I using GitHub
desktop or the Atom editor.
I was using Adam for the code,
but I was using GitHub desktop
as well, but right now I've
got it up in the web browser.
Yeah, well if you if you go on
and it should be a little like
a drop down menu there where
it says master if you click in
there you'll see the other
branch its website. Yep Yep.
Yeah, sorry. Oh no, sorry yeah,
did you want the website to be
default? Anna I want oh I'll
talk to you later about how to
change the settings for the
GitHub pages settings on the
repo. Yeah, no worries, 'cause
I'll leave master's default
because that's the one it will
select when anybody adds the
repo to say GitHub Desktop.
Oh yeah, cool. So with the
GitHub pages. Which one did
you want website obviously
website. Yeah.
And if you could just post this
thing, you are out for that. So
on my testing we can see the
code once it's up.
Yep.
Uh, I think I just did it so
it'll work once you've gotten
index stop HTML file.
And I think once everything is
done for the assignment, we've
all got to click the fork button
on that repost of each. Got a
copy in our own GitHub accounts.
Yep.
Yeah.
Going to upload anything, I'll
probably need some help with.
Everything you just said 'cause
I only understood half of it. I
think we can share desktop in
meetings that we could.
Oh yeah, tutorial at some
stage if you want.
Maybe recorded one, probably
not what something we need
to submit though.
Hi, fair enough.
Sweet.
Girls, I think that's pretty
much all the agenda was
needed. I did forget to say
we had decided name for
anyone I didn't see. We had
to fight the fighting.
I'm.
Did I do that?
Yeah.
1.
I didn't do that wrong, you know
no. OK, that's good. Yeah no,
sorry it's just a cool name that
is told us not to have one that
was too edgy because it might
come back to haunt is yeah.
It's got sharp teeth. That's
really edgy though. Did we
almost won that name?
I just woke up this morning and
it was there, but I'm unclear.
If anyone objects, we
can work something out.
Anyone object to it?
No, I'm cool with that, cool.
Was there anything from
yesterday that we haven't
gotten to Shannon?
Not too sure.
Going through those, I just
looking at. The.
The days we want to make me at
meet up. Yeah that was the next
thing on the agenda at the end
here. I just wanna double check
first Adam and Daniel. You want
to start on that project idea.
This week I'm not too sure
how we're going to split
that. They usually do some
content of it anyway and just
upload some drafts and then
we can collaborate on it.
Yes.
Adwaita divvied up.
Yeah we can all help each other
with it as well, but I I guess
you two would like the Main.
Main leaders in that section.
So if anyone has any, like
any advice or information on
any of the other topics we
should be able to share, I
think yeah, yeah I don't
have a problem for asking
for help when I get stuck,
so I'll I'll scream out when
I don't know what I'm doing.
It says there's no word limit,
but you know it says it's a
usual 1500 minimum, so same as
assessment one really destroying
a new program into it.
OK.
Right about others you
motivation descriptions. Yeah,
but now for this assessment I
guess. What did you say, Adam? I
was just checking if I
definitely going with the
privacy app for now, OK?
No.
Yeah, I think it might help you
if you like.
Face your face, your wordings or
base your topics off of the
previous assessment questions.
Yeah.
That might help you out a bit.
So yeah.
Motivation description the
other one would be the tools
and tech skills.
And the outcome?
Or a mix of age depending
whatever you want to.
And then it was pretty much all.
The only other thing that again
and I was just looking in
meeting times. I'm not too sure
whether everyone is happy with
the Saturday Sunday. Well,
I've one preferred during
the week and next weekend.
I'm pretty busy so I won't
be able to meet unless
it's early in the morning.
So.
Wait, we got meetings on
Tuesdays and Thursdays. If do we
all watch teams meetings or do
some of us watch other ones?
I just want things yeah yeah,
just watch teams too. I
really get a chance to watch
it live 'cause I'm usually
working or something.
I want that runs the main one.
I say.
I don't know whoever it was. I
didn't mind his because we were
traveling in the whole time.
But for this week I watch
at East Class. I watched
the Anthony's class this
week, and then I kind of
skimmed over teams one.
So I'll go on everyday Monday
through Thursday. 'cause about
programming Monday, Wednesday.
But as I said, you welcome my
tree watch those just mainly
the class ones. I like to be
involved with, which will be
Wednesday, Thursday.
But the Wednesday ones, at 8:00
o'clock in the Thursday ones,
obviously. With you guys
anyway so.
The car caught car course. Wide
ones aren't too intriguing.
And I can always be reached
later 'cause there's no really
feedback like input that you
anyone gives through Adam.
Do you think it's a draw on the
white board if you don't attend?
Alright.
Yes.
No, you don't have. There was
pictures of Homer. There were *
**** **** getting drawn with
getting called a racist.
Very turned off chat.
I didn't want the programming
one during that entire lecture.
I had it in the background, but
I was just doing my programming
assignment during it.
So.
So your.
Shannon, you're you're what
days are you available?
So I need any day.
Well, first, I wouldn't be the
same Wednesday I got one at 8:00
o'clock at night.
So are you available Wednesday
or not available Wednesday?
I'm available Wednesday before
8:00 o'clock, but I've gotta
go to the class. Went at 8:00
o'clock. OK, so you're
available everyday but
Thursday at around six 6:30.
And George, what days
are you not available?
Now I'm pretty I'm available by
basically every day I finish
work at 6 and I have.
Wednesday Thursdays off so I can
hear any day after 6:30 I'll be
fine and Sam, what does he not
available? So my schedule is
always changing, but if I know
like a regular time from.
Next week I can adjust, but this
week I'm not available Tuesday,
Thursday, and Saturday Sunday.
So Adam, are you available
Wednesday, yeah. And Daniel.
This weekend I'm OK anytime.
What did you say Adam about the
weekend Obvia Way on site this
weekend for three days Friday,
Saturday, Sunday. So Wednesday
6:30. Yeah, that's good.
Good to me, yeah. Sorry I
took over a bit channel.
I don't know.
And then the other one.
Oh yeah.
So. There was Monday and
some available on Friday.
Is everyone available on Friday?
Except for Adam.
Oh yeah.
What about Monday? I mean that's
that's tomorrow, but it's a.
It's a bit weird having the
meeting three days in a row,
Yeah, but in future we could do
Monday. Like from the next week
onwards. And yeah, it's yeah
it's OK just to just so we meet
the two meeting criteria.
So I've got. I've got cheese day
then anyone not available
Tuesday. I don't have to re
check my schedule for Tuesday,
but we can maybe work around it.
And it is OK if we have absences
as well. Yeah, yeah, that's a
good point next week, probably
Wednesday. And then the
following. Wait, we can do two
from there. Tim did say that
even this week that doing the
two meetings a week
that cause groups still
forming wasn't a real
necessity. OK, so Wednesday.
I will start their wakes from
the Sunday, so this account as
well on my phone so.
So maybe a Friday?
Cool. OK, so Wednesday and
maybe Friday.
Sorry, sorry, sorry so Wednesday
and Wednesday and Friday.
Definitely Wednesday
maybe Friday.
Is it 1 Fraser in the
afternoon at all?
Most days.
Yeah, most days, but Wednesday
Friday every other day again.
Pretty much after one every
day I'm available.
OK.
So I guess for now we can look
in Wednesday 6:30 yeah?
Yep.
Schedule that.
And you want to do that, like is
like a regular like session each
week, so we have at least one.
Wednesday 6:30 should be just a
regular one weekend, yeah?
Cool.
For this one, one day a week,
you know report.
Can you have a second meeting?
Another side we need to, but.
The second meeting can
display other name.
I don't know the best way to
say that it can be called a
point if necessary.
Yep.
So was there anything on my?
Are the actions from this
meeting come up with the team
name done right out of
paragraph of personal
information to combine later?
So we just need to do that
individually. Each write out
three personality test outcomes
and descendants on how this
information may be helpful to
the group and individual task.
Write a quick summary of our
ideal jobs. We've covered that.
Find the next meeting covered
that collect the list of group
websites covered that.
Create a GitHub repository.
We've done that. Discuss
three things.
Discuss these things for the.
Our meeting we've done that.
Come up with some questions for
Is It Steven or Stephen?
Adam.
Thursday.
Steven
is probably Steven.
Covered everything, do we
need to? Do we want to like
planned out something to talk
about next time? And who
wants to share next time?
I'm just about the actions of
the meeting. This meeting will
just talk about as we've gone
through, and I've just put in
there prior to. This is just
next week, will just be at the
moment we have progress.
Report of all the content that
was. So since we're going to
Wednesday, I'm not too sure
how free people, but if we
start uploading those
documents and then we can see
where we're at with that.
I think we got the majority
of the basics covered now.
It's just a matter of trying
to get content in, yeah?
The other thing was like the.
We were supposed to come
each of us with one question
for him for Steven.
Do we just add the questions?
Just type the questions into
the word file that we have
there in teams.
Yeah Yep OK cool.
And did we?
I was gonna say.
I'm just trying to find out.
Search direction next time.
We might talk about any
questions we have about the
individual staff or any
questions following the class
meetings that from Anthony.
I just kind of talk through any
any problems we might be having.
Going to look like.
Yeah, and like if you
might have some.
We might have feedback from
their assignments, but into
the first assessments.
And like with with the app,
we might you might have some
questions about how sort of
how that's going to look or
how that's going to work, and
it would be good to talk
about that as a group, 'cause
it's kind of A.
I think intellectually it's
a bit of a bigger task than
the full report.
Coming up with the idea and
how it's all gonna workout,
it's a bit more creative.
So we could discuss
that on Wednesday.
Up
not sure what else we need
to talk about that.
The team.
No.
Not project.
**** the.
Spark plus, by the time you get
to workout is that an individual
thing. The spark plus.
Rolling survey
their individual, did you say?
Yeah, I asked him about it last
meeting thing. Last Thursday and
he said not to worry about it.
They'll let us know it might be
after we submit it like after we
submit the assignment to or
might be before that. He said
he'll let us know in a couple of
weeks. Cool, I said vague.
Maybe we will have more stuff to
talk about by the time Wednesday
comes around on Wednesday.
I want to say it's gonna
look like.
All like style yeah, what
do you want to look like?
A.
I I don't mind it.
Just nice and easy and
functional.
And in particular coverages one.
Bright pink
pink and purple.
Purple anyone there? Yeah yeah.
I think. Service check check the
Rubric because the last one said
like you have to make the
website look like good.
Yeah, like whatever that is
like, they never said what
kind of criteria they
actually wanted. So like a
salmon color, black
background with pink and
purple text.
Not violent on the eyes at all.
Do you want like it flashing and
pulsating? Oh yeah, like good
I've got the strobe light going.
Kind of thing, yeah?
Chasing the side margins of
the website. It just like
flashing flashing colors like
RGB, just really really basic
colors though.
I'll see what I can do.
Search
I think we need to include some
photos and stuff as well.
Should we each submitted
photo of ourselves in the
group profile? I was just
gonna use the ones that you
had on your individual pages.
With me, because mines
of my dog like this.
Funny photo.
So I'll I'll give you 1.
Or just in the original project?
It didn't have to be specifies
anything about the actual web
pages that you create one. It's
it said somewhere we need to
include a range of like.
Like some graph, some data,
some photos, some.
Oh yeah, we need like
formatted data, images,
videos, links and and
similar information. So
yeah, I just thought maybe
that that would go well with
the introduction saying that
we've already got photos,
set up, websites pretty
much. Just our report.
Can smoking graphs?
What do you say, Adam?
Rex
I've got that from a note
from last meeting.
Sick.
Uh, did the something about the
ideal jobs that needed to be
they wreck highly recommended
putting it in a graph for
comparison, which kind of seems
confusing to me.
Like was it?
That's a lot. Makes a lot more
sense in a graph. Yeah, I'm. I'm
guessing once we look at like
the burning glass site and see
what what they're kind of
talking about. Like maybe we
might have a better idea.
Little bit the the.
Oh yeah, two sections for ideal
job. Yeah it was. It was the
comparing each others jobs
to each other, one that they
wanted her I need. I need to
read that section is I still
have no idea what burning
glass is a reference to.
I think it's just like
industry data for different
occupations. So like maybe
how in demand specialist is
or something. If you checked
it out yet. If you go onto.
Miss teams and then go to.
Where did you post your thing
Shannon about your job?
Data.
So.
Go to industry data and go to
the files section and Shannons
posted one there if that.
OK.
Is that I looked at his earlier
and I was like that doesn't
sound like what I was writing
and then I realized it was
something different. And
then it has all the Bangla
started there in the PDS as
well. It's just simplistic.
Call girls yeah, no worries.
Some dealer Google some of it to
understand what the hell they're
talking about. So once we've
once we've done the other ideal
job section, the more personal
personalized wine, not the data
one. The one where we just
compare. How are jobs are
similar or different? Once we've
kind of written a bit on that,
Adam? We might be able to
work on how to put that in
their chart or something.
Wrapped up something or other.
If it makes sense or not
the question.
We could just just be the jobs.
Similar and then we each write
what similar. Then we what's
different. We tried. What's
different just for the sake
it? I think they just want a
different form of visual
display. Yeah, yeah.
Girl names, skills
and jobs and ticks.
Yeah, I was thinking of have you
ever seen those charts, but you
know when you have like you know
like 3 three like 3 circles and
then whatever the circles like
they get together it means like
those people they have like a
things in common typing skills.
Yes, maybe something like that
where you know everybody chooses
the industry and whatever your
industry has. Some you know.
Lions. How quick?
Excel PowerPoint, yeah.
Sorry, it's just looking
at your children.
Everything is not everything,
that's everything that was on
the list here. Hello.
Freaking wrap it up then.
Alright, I'll stop the
recording here.