Just thinking about it, there we
are. Good morning everybody.
This is meeting #7 at 8:00 AM,
Australian eastern daylight
savings time. Today we're gonna
come with it. Contributions form
that we've all gotta sign and
cover some group reflection and
then any changes that need to be
made to the website or concerns
about the project, idea or any
other section of the site.
Believe everybody who has
completed the contributions for
man is happy with the agreed
contribution so far that's been
put on there.
Yeah. Yep, Yep.
OK.
So move along, then on that one.
I don't know if we're gonna get
45 minutes out of this meeting.
Well, it says that we only have
have to do 20 and then.
Ah, OK, that's better. We might
be able to make the 20. Yeah, so
group of 20 group.
So group reflection we have
to answer 4 questions as a
group totaling about 400
words combined where we have
to cover what went well. What
could be improved? At least
one thing that was surprising
that we can all agree on as a
group at least one thing you
have learned about groups.
Yeah, and then we've got to do
like a 200 word version of that
in our just for ourselves as
well. I think Daniel
and I already did the
individual ones, yeah?
I've got one from Daniel. I was
working on my last night, but
it's not finished yet and
everybody went over the 200
words and now I like the
obligated to do like the similar
man as well.
Actually trimmed down a bit, I
was just like throw it out.
Whatever, that's alright.
I'll just answer mine the
same way I think it would be
easier for everybody.
Right? Like moments like it was
here, 300 words or something
maybe. It's alright.
So I'm just gonna quickly put
yourself on the spot. He's can't
reference the content that
you've already written, so don't
look at it. What went well?
You got 10 seconds answers the
question go. Finally, just go
quickly. I group came together
like how quickly were able to
organize meetings and set task
for each other.
That was really good. We also
have friendly way really
quickly, yeah. And how easy
everything just. Yeah, how easy
it was to work with everybody as
well, like. We didn't have any
problems really. Everybody was
like happy to do.
The Tasks in.
Yeah, it was very smooth. I
think they made one mistake or
accidentally did something. Mary
thought she was gonna do.
Oh the translator.
The transcript. So that's quite
a bit because I was doing the
PDF, but then she wanted to do
the PDF and I'm like I just
assumed I was doing the PDF
because I was doing the website
and there was the conversation
we had about that we had to
submit the website and the PDF
and I was like I just copied and
paste it for my assessment one
and it got good marks so we'll
just do that. So I just assumed
that's what I was doing and it
says I can't know. I'd like to
do it. Yeah, everyone's over
eager to do to this year and was
like now I've got nothing to do.
I've gotta wait for people to
hand in stuff so I can do stuff.
Well, I found something to
do. I made tables, make some
nice make some nice graphics.
Yeah we we worked on the that
all those tables and charts
and stuff and getting them to
actually load on the page.
OK, so will do the
next question. What
could be improved?
Well, I guess we answered that
to where we could.
Clearly outline some of the
tasks that we didn't had earlier
on. Yeah, just a few small minor
ones we missed, yeah?
And I thought.
Like we didn't really have a
problem, but when the Daylight
Saving Time changed, like it
had to organize it better. Yeah
yeah we had like we went
through a pretty well 'cause
all you guys were pretty
flexible but it had real
potential to really cause some
issues.
I think I just assumed everybody
was in Victoria, like I saw on
Shannons Page. He said he loved
him back as much as I can, but I
didn't read any further. But I'm
like Oh he's in Queensland and
what are and then I just assumed
everybody was in Victoria. You
know it should have known better
online course. Could be anyway,
like Georges Hamilton. Island
and Samuel are in your
inventory. And I'm
liking. In Horsham.
So when I saw it, Dan wasn't
coming to the meeting this
morning like that makes sense
for gold. Four in the morning
for him he had to get up at
4:00. Yeah, 'cause he was
talking to him last night about
the project and he was saying,
Oh yeah, I'm gonna be up at 4:00
in the morning so I'll be able
to review it then. Why why you
going to fall? And he's like
a talking. Attend that
meeting. I might, you know
you don't have to attend
both. That's the reason we've
got the afternoon one so you
could attend that one. It
goes. Oh, that makes sense.
WA doesn't have daylight savings
doing. No, the header defriended
like 10 years ago to get rid of
it. Yes.
Tonight. Owls don't have
it either.
Yeah, now we're good.
Yeah, yeah. Does New South
Wales still have it? I thought
they did. Or is it Queensland?
All I know is that Queensland
got rid of it because of the
tourists that confused them.
Yeah, but like I'm what's Tweed
heads where the airport is like
half the airports in New South
Wales and half cent Queensland
and like yeah I'm on your phone
can change.
Suck.
But then you get to the terminal
on the other side of the
airport. I'm early for my flight
check, then they go back. I'm
late again. That would be
annoying. It would really. That
would be horrible. That's crazy
daylight savings. I should get
rid of it. Farmers have
flashlights now and Tortures and
self driving vehicles.
And that usually out there
11:00 o'clock anyway. So
what does it matter?
So what was at least one
thing that was surprising to
everybody about? The group.
Like I was surprised like the
extra time and they help. We all
gave each other like you did the
GitHub tutorial and everything.
Yeah, so people like going
beyond what they needed to do.
Even though we're pretty much
complete strangers. Yeah.
And good camaraderie in
teamwork. I'm surprised
how well it went.
Yeah. Because you got stuck in
Night, 5 strangers and just
given a task to do, you just
don't. You know everybody was
pretty period before everyone
joins in.
Yep.
It's good that was no
fights to fighting
over who's gonna do
what, it'll just,
it'll just clicked.
That's good. At least
one thing that you have
learned about groups.
I just always keep saying that
there's no I in team.
Yeah. Yes, one thing
Open is where I work or where I
worked 'cause I've been
currently fired. The teams were.
Like the team aspect, it all
working at work doesn't really
work very well together. Yeah,
because. It's just, um.
Yeah, a lot of bigger and a lot
of **** I guess what I learned
from this group is that teams
actually can work together. Got
at work. I used to work by
myself only because when you put
two of these together, it's
always just a clash.
'cause everyone had their own
like you so certain people you
could work with. But then
there's other people you
couldn't work with. My God just
said. Yeah, completely
different personalities
throughout the group and.
So I can give The Apprentice the
job of digging a trench, then he
will have a sugar beet digger
that range so they don't get it.
**** it, I'll dig the trench and
then you can do the hard stuff,
but then he doesn't know how to
do the other stuff 'cause he
doesn't have the knowledge to do
it. Then you just like, well,
what do you want me to do it or
I'll do it all then and you can
just. Sit down and
play on your phone.
I'd like a job playing on my
phone all day.
I guess you get what you got.
Amazing stuff in RT where you
gotta teach him how to do stuff
and then local always doing
boring stuff like fixing peoples
desktops or printer issues. I
don't want. Well once you learn
how to do those then you're
going to be able to do the
complicated stuff, but you can
watch me do the complicated
stuff and eventually you can do
it. Right? Then
Is it? Sure.
This sort of ties in with what I
wrote like good, good morale and
good camaraderie that goes along
way like when when people are
actively like they really want
to do the task with each other.
You know, it really helps a lot.
But we wanna get a good grade
and. Get through the assignment
to move on to the next one, so
we had a common goal. It was
pretty. Pretty good, and I think
we had a lot of fun too.
That was good.
Yeah, also as well, I think like
the seeing what other people do.
Does you learn from that as
well? It gives you like new
ideas. Like you know there was
times where I was like oh ****
How do I do this? And then I
look at someone's work and I was
like, oh OK, I can do this as
well. It's kind of like.
Brings up more.
A wider view of what you
have to do.
I'm going to suddenly learn a
little bit about making a
website and stuff by trying to
figure out how to update data
and stuff on the web page.
So Linda Linda. Look through
your working now. You Shannon
Daniels. I think you guys did
the most initially on the
website at the start.
Yeah. I tried to leave this
JavaScript. He's not gonna
transfer my Java knowledge into
JavaScript really easily. Yeah,
and Java Scripts a lot easier,
right? It is, it is.
Say for you guys. So if you
wanna use any of that you can
just yeah, and I explained how
it's how it's working so.
Good. Well, alright, so we
can just review the content. I
guess everybody's had a chance
to take a look at what's on the
website. In the different
sections and happy I've picked
up anytime anyone picked up any
typos besides Betty.
I was reading last night the
project idea an.
I understand sorry 'cause the
project idea on the websites
wrong. Oh no, no. This document
by the document. Yeah, there's a
document I put under report,
project ideas, final report. I
think it is Adams review. I
think it said it did say Adams
Review and then I had Daniel
sign off on the changes. So it's
if you go to files that's
actually now just called Project
ID dash revision.
OK, James wouldn't let me update
the other link. It's like no,
I'm not, you're not allowed.
OK, it's like I wanted to update
the what I was working on the
project idea, but Daniel had it
open so I wrote all this stuff
but it wouldn't save so yeah.
As soon as I click close on,
teams are still gone away. What
on my lucky I had it in Word as
well. Something like copy paste
and then I'm just typing
messages into the document. Can
you close it so I could say?
Did you get to see where the
cursor is? Well, there editing
it. There.
Alright, I will be leaving the
red button when we do this. When
I do this admission 'cause I was
talking to Daniel he he just
wants me to submit the PDF2.
Um canvas So that it's
easier.
Unless anybody else wants to.
Sorry, what
was that? Turn on Sunday, 'cause
I just assumed Daniel is gonna
submit the PDF assignment but he
just said like yesterday when I
was talking to him. He just
wants me to submit the PDF
report for the group.
So I was just asking do we wanna
wait the red button and stuff?
I see one.
Nice yeah, I think Tim might get
a kick out there. Any penalties
if you leave it there?
No, no yeah, I didn't get any
penalties for foot jokes in my
assessment. One in the source
code. It's just the yeah, yeah,
should be good.
Thomas, we can still turn it
off. Yeah, it makes him like 10
seconds. My say 10 seconds, but
I think it's 15 seconds. I think
I I think I never obtained it.
What it takes to it.
Anything
else? Do we keep
the discord mentioned in the
tools? I was just gonna leave
it. OK.
Uh, 'cause I think the only
reason that they say that they
don't want discord or you may
get marked down for using
discord is the the lack of
ability to have a history of
what was said and by who.
Because generally you can't just
copy and paste out of GitHub,
GitHub, discord and save it
somewhere. And you can't
record the videos.
So any meetings?
We all addicted discord
discussion, which is like little
itty bitty pick stuff. And then
when we came to a conclusion
that got transferred to teams
anyway, yeah, so I'm just gonna
put it there just for the sake
of completeness. 'cause you
know, we did cover a couple of
things or wake people up on
discord to get him to come
across the teams. So it just
shows that we were able to use
multiple tools to accomplish the
task, but we kept all the
professional stuff on teams and
some out of what you call out of
band communication on discord.
Cool targets phone in there.
Don't see any reason why they
marked down for.
Actually, like if we had a
meeting in person like you
wouldn't record the meeting in
person. So or if you had a
conversation in person. How
would you record that to put it
on the website kind of thing?
Thing go.
Alright, OK, well we've got an
extra person for the meeting.
Supervise.
It's just a look teams as I mean
it's alright, but it's chats
very awkward. It is.
Specially when you're trying to
read back through the replies
and the message boards and it's
there 'cause you're like, where
did they reply to that? And then
it goes. Goes bold and you click
on it and then I don't see the
reply, but it says I do an
activity. And then I click on
activity. Then I click on the
thing and then it takes me back
to the same place and the
message is there. This is worse
than canvas. Oh, I wouldn't go
that, at least is the canvas.
Describes it fit him, so if he
watches this evening, will be
honestly the reason why we left
it in there, yeah.
And I think.
IT work, I think all we had to
do was put the answers to those
questions which we've done with
them's transcript. Yeah, I sort
of. Put all his answers in the
underneath these questions so so
it's easier for them to see
grow. Yeah.
Yeah, that was good.
What question, Oh yeah, the that
matrix or what is it?
No no no. Yeah Steve. Like just
the interview we did. So yeah
yeah. I just got the subtitles
and clean him up a bit and made
it to answer the questions that
was supposed to ask. Germany put
numbers next to the questions.
It will supposed to ask or like
a dot point or something just to
make him stand out more.
Oh yeah. Like
'cause I think we numbered
the questions anyway.
Yeah, it might might help.
And I did include a couple of
the follow up questions you and
Mattie said as well with you.
This can be like start talking
about something a little bit
different and you sort of needed
to have the context for
clarification and yeah. Yeah.
I like the only thing I need to
get done now is I did make
direct changes to the website.
In information I put in, so I'll
just have to transfer that back
to documents in the mastery in
teens, teens and git teams and
get, yeah. 'cause he's gonna
look at what's loaded files to
teams then get home.
Apparently. Sorry, I was also
gonna just. Add a few things
into like ideal jobs.
Just another paragraph maybe?
Just to make it stand out, yeah.
Oh, once we submit, everybody's
gonna do a fork of the
project. On GitHub.
It's not as well, yeah, so we've
all meant to have our own copy
of it in our repo's.
So you just gotta go to
thegithub.com, select Daniels
thing and have it on Master and
just click fork and all four
should fork. Both branches.
The website and the the. In
theory I haven't, I haven't
tested it, but it's supposed to.
I'll test it now, I'll get you
on the phone.
Folk.
At my only folk, like the
Master branch, but I'm just
I'm just checking it's gonna
take a few minutes.
No, that's
pretty. But we're pretty much
complete. And when is that?
When is that spark plus things
gonna be done at the park
Sunday? Two weeks or something.
He said to do it, oh.
Yeah, did they are
in no rush for that.
Because yeah, that they
extended that because they
didn't have all the complete
groups to put in to activate
all the different group
accounts.
Which is like Dave and even told
us how to log into it yet.
Does anyone know how to log into
the? Does spark cluster I've
tried? I I don't have enough. I
got a link or maybe.
Or not. Would it be on the 8 two
or something? Or I don't know.
There's like, yeah it's it's. Is
it under this assessment is
spark plus like this part not a
two. So it's like I don't know
if it's feedback about our sign
was in feedback about them.
The notification you from the
clap. Is sharing
his Clapper rent?
Groups need to be finalized for
assessment to before I can put
in the group member details into
spark plus system.
Sadly, there have been a number
emails from students having
issues with the communications
participations their groups.
So students groups are still
fluctuate. ING. Spark plus will
be open to beyond the assignment
to deadline, so that's OK.
'cause apparently they had
students that were in groups
that they won't own groups in
canvas that were in another
group and we're responding to
their actual growth, yeah?
So.
I'm just here. The assessment to
obviously the due date
contribute contribution form 2.
Four days after and he still
waiting on groups to
actually be groups before
spark plus is released.
Which makes you feel
bad for those people.
Or maybe it's their
fault?
Hey could be their own fault.
I mean it, it isn't online
course like we got pretty lucky
that our team I think.
Right, so I think all teams
that have actually got content
were created around the same
time as ours. We just got more
content and then.
I think it was only like
4 teams.
Yeah, it wasn't many
teams ready.
So I don't know if you saw our
discord links. We were posting
at one stage, Samuel, where we
went through more hunting GitHub
for all the other assignment.
Yeah so sorry couple of the
sorry couple of the websites so
the one that was like a just a
template and then the other one
that was just a great page.
Yeah.
I think it was Shannon that said
it was market research. We
weren't stalking them at all. I
said that I said that to you.
Market research. You're going
to see what they're doing.
Well, I reckon if looked at
hours and just haven't said
anything like if we worked out
to search for the assignment
that they want it named as.
I'm sure other groups
did as well.
Alright, is there anything else
that we wanted to mention on
this meeting? Help me **** This
is a hot wheel track.
Yeah 60 James raise these first
meeting agenda item.
And it has a trailer that
expensive to put all his cars on
it and then drive it around. But
sometimes they get stuck, yeah?
Yeah. Yeah it's not
showing till date.
It's different,
yes? Thank you any other thing
is like what should be working
on today to get it.
So today I wanna make any
changes to your stuff. Today is
the last day kind of because we
need to give Mattie some time to
be able to copy and paste
everything. I've got to complete
on the project idea two
sections, oh. And the end of 1
Section 'cause I wasn't sure
what we wanted to put his
innovation under description. So
we're just going to say that
we're going to use AI and
machine learning in the future
to be able to scrape website
that the social media websites
to adjust settings for the user.
And then I just got a complete
tools and technology which is
I've put some night rough notes
in there. What we need. So I've
just got to go through and say
why we need it. Add some images
and then the schools required
and why we need it.
Otherwise it's done.
And then I've just gotta
do my group reflection.
So, but this is the.
Changes in.
What I was gonna say. Tools and
technologies. Others at the
subject we gonna touch in the
next meeting. Just if we
finished tools and technology,
what you just said about it.
They just two sections of the
project idea that I haven't
finished yet. OK, so that's what
I'm gonna be doing today.
And if you guys want to make any
changes to any of your content,
do so to today so that we can go
through and check everything to
make sure it's alright tomorrow.
And that gives many time to
transfer it to the PDF. If you
change anything on the
website, please make sure you
update the GitHub Word
document version and the teams
version of that file, yeah?
Yeah.
That's pretty much it.
And then we can submit on the
original submission date I guess
and hopefully get some sort of
prize. Not that much to go.
Yeah. And
everything tonight. I can tell
you what we changed, yeah?
Cool. Sounds good.
Yeah, overview of what we
changed. Um Ann just will just
review the group reflection as
well for the other people that
weren't weren't here since we
don't have any concerns with the
site, we don't need to.
Mention them at the next
meeting, either now who's
attending the other meeting
today? So I'll be still not
sure if I can. Yeah busy
tonight, but if you have
raised on the next one, if
you if you don't make it.
Nothing. It should be alright. I
finish work around 9:00 so I
sometimes I finish earlier as
well. So if I can finish.
Early I'll try and get there.
Jump.
And George, are you gonna make
it to the yeah I'll share that
the last one yeah I finish at 6
oh so pointing your time yeah I
got one hour to get everything
done here. And Shannon
You're going to be able to make
tonight's, Yep, I'll be in.
Alright, set off set aside my
weekend just to finalize it all,
even they'd be.
But it kind of looks like I
don't need to do that much at
all, no, really. I'll be
available most of the day if
anybody needs help with
anything, I'll get stuck or one
spinner review anything they've
written. So. If that helps.
And probably we can conclude
this meeting less is anything
else you guys want to mention
before. We got on Earth.
No, I think I've already
covered everything, yeah.
I'll stop the recording.
Start.