Is there any way to indicate
that it's recording?
This red icon. Oh yeah, there it
goes. Awesome, so this is my
first time chairing a meeting
ever. So go easy on me.
So it's the 7th of
October 2020 meeting #5 I
believe. And yeah, so we all got
our results back for our
assignment, one this week or
yesterday. Congratulations
everyone, I think you all did
pretty well. Nichols, Adam got
full marks for the website
so. Good job for that I
think I should have made my
profile longer there.
So is there anything that?
Someone wants to
discuss about the.
The assignment or anything like
any feedback that they thought
was interesting? Or did Tim
offer any suggestions for future
assignments or anything?
He did on mine could because I
legitimately couldn't think of
what to put in an app like like
I could think of the content to
having the app, but I couldn't
think of the.
Technology features to have in
the app kind of focused on the
content rather than the
features, so he gave me a few
suggestions on features.
And I remember what my score was
for that. But I I had lower
scores just due to not having a
lot of my teeth.
Technology in it.
And so he gave me stretch into
that and then with my website.
He said, obviously mine was very
simple so I got half marks
there. And so he just said that
I need to incorporate more HTML.
Basically. And I think if I was
a bit more prepared or I
understood a bit more.
Have a fair bit more in there.
Yeah.
Too
much.
In some things.
Far from
it. I got was just he suggested
rubric more as opposed to what's
worth the most marks.
'cause I did cut back on like
ideal job for example, I didn't
and I think profile to like this
to fit in the profile.
He said 'cause it was one
of the higher markets.
The rest of his comments are
pretty good. Yeah, love
the project idea.
Love my, except obviously I was
just missing a few things.
Everything else is really happy
with. I think George
is a bit hard done by.
Yeah.
I did.
Hey. Did he pop the
feedback? Are you just talking
about the Max?
Yeah, they're pretty hot.
But then again, you don't know
whether. He changed it again,
lights admission for the last
10%. 'cause of that or so? I'm
just not sure. He may. He may
have missed the PDF report to
you, don't know.
I didn't look too much of these
website only. I only skimmed on
everyone's website so. I really
still don't know what do you put
in there. A process that's
fine. How do
you go, Daniel?
Um? Is my audio OK, by
the way, 'cause I switched
laptops, kids alright, it's a
little bit noisy, but it's OK,
yeah? Volume so I wasn't getting
anything in the test. I did have
you got the power plugged in?
Yes, maybe if you unplug
the power it might reduce
some of the noise.
Batteries screwed on this one.
OK then don't worry about it. So
sometimes if there's like a bad
how connection the microphone
can get a little bit noisy.
Yeah.
That's what's on
my end now.
Whatever you just
done? Yeah, sorry.
Is it just one?
Echo. Is this noise? But it's
a lot quieter.
Actually, I can hear myself
coming back really clearly.
I can hear everyone coming back.
Several Times Now, I'd say
someone speakers are up
too loud.
Alright then just unplugged hold
up there, yeah, yeah.
No, that's worse.
Whatever you had gone the first
time might have been the best
option so far.
Whatever you've got going
now isn't working.
We've got no audio,
Daniel.
That
Yeah, we can hear. Maybe when
you're not talking to Mike
otherwise we're going to have a
buzz the whole time. Yep Yep
Yep, Yep. OK.
That's
good.
Now I'll just sit here and get
busy. OK, I'll just get
this over with. I
just got next.
I I got like this in the rubric
I got the second one from the
end all the way down.
So. I guess I was kind of
consistent. I didn't get great
marks on the project.
But on the project idea, but it
wasn't too bad. Overall I
thought I was only going to get.
I was aiming for 50 to 70 so I
got 78 so I was happy.
So that's good. Yeah, I think
most of us got around 80. Hey,
yeah, yeah like.
That all is expecting lower,
yeah, I was expecting.
Not really if you consistently
get around 80. That's still a HD
so that's still yeah be a GPA
that's maximum marks. So yeah,
so maximum results with minimum
effort. Yeah, that's good, I
think website wise, we're
looking pretty good like it's
looking very professional.
Sam, I think will get good marks
there. Not a template or
anything so. Not pretty
good. 'cause I saw some of the,
uh, the ones you showed on.
Oh yeah.
Yeah, it's really good.
Yeah, the artwork was really
cool. That yes, right?
The red button yeah yeah.
That's hilarious. Right, 10
seconds to turn it off.
Next we need an air raid siren
to play play with that as well.
I I thought about it, but
browsers now, mute audio sources
by default. 'cause pop up ads
that used to. You know like
noises and stuff, and play music
in the background. Yeah, what
about those ones that pop up.
YouTube videos that
automatically start playing that
because you've already 'cause
you clicked on it.
No, the ones that you don't
click like you scroll scroll
past it and you can there's
audio somewhere playing
somewhere, you have to scroll up
and find it. No
rest. Yeah, yeah, I know
the ones. The first time that it
goes to do it normally asks you
or brings a pop up. Do you want
to allow it? Yeah.
Like son allow officially.
Everyone. What
time, the what time the To Do
List? So next time on the agenda
I've got the progress report.
Further. No,
we didn't. Yeah, somehow I got
four out of five on the personal
information, I put.
Very little personal information
at all. The project I did a
project idea did well. Got 28 on
that one. 15 on the profile, but
he didn't leave me any feedback
on why. Ideal job 22 interest
in ITA to 10. Presentation 10
or 10. So 80
seven o'clock. Interesting RT
got low because I've.
You got 8 of
10. Yeah.
I mean a job it on a
Fitbit, maybe didn't want that.
Pretty pretty OK with everything
so on the rubric I got the
second highest for most of them
except for the ideal job, I got
the highest one.
So just because that's probably
the one I spent the least effort
on I notice. We all got 8 for
interest of IT, except for
Shannon that got 8.5.
I wonder if I wonder if Tim was
just like copy, paste, copy,
paste these. Otherwise I'll that
realize what I'm doing.
My feedback for on the rubric
for interest in ITV, as you seem
to have a good interest in IT.
Boilerplate is swimming.
I can't remember which one, but
there was like one of my schools
where he gave he said really
like positive feedback. He was
like he did great with her. She
did great with that right with
this and then with no negative
feedback and I didn't get it
grade that kind of match the
words he was saying. Yeah I was
like. Must be higher.
They overall Mark I didn't
understand but that, but like I
think it was my introduction or
get to know me profile something
other. Thank you very, very very
well. But I'm not gonna make you
biased. What was that noise?
The kids.
And I was a.
Outlook.
Dictation.
Making music.
Do you guys know about a GitHub
tutorial? Thing from 7:00 PM to
8:00 PM. I think it wasn't Adam
Gonna show you. GitHub.
Or teach anyone GitHub if they
needed it. Yeah.
OK.
That notification Adam
was about a
GitHub tutorial theme.
Gonna do after. Yeah, did you
still wanna do it? Yeah 'cause I
think George wanted to do it as
well, but I don't think he's
gonna be. Here.
The only comment I got on my
rubric as I put in the source
code, I doubt anyone will look
here and then he put I did this.
So easy to write.
Very professional or
unprofessional. Very
professional website.
Easy to read through.
Sir. I've been like using the
developer Tools on my browser to
look at like code for websites
and that just to sort of
immersed myself forbidden.
There's stuff like that all the
time, yeah? Yeah, selected
pretty stuff, pretty funny
stuff. And yeah although giving
a shout out to like their friend
or something like Yo dude check
this out. Yeah, it's
good. Sorry, I interrupted you
before saying when I asked you
what was that much of you this?
So, so next time just got like
a. Progress report to see how
everyones doing like with the
The technology reports in the
project and stuff.
So I think I think Shannon
you've pretty much done your
report. Care for fun?
It's it's on there, I'm still.
I'm kind of happy with it I
guess. I could still use more in
text citation, but I I think I
covered exactly where I
actually. Used a reference.
Yeah.
I know I'm pretty happy with the
report Wednesday. Yeah, I'm
pretty much the same with mine.
It's a little bit bloated, so I
might. Edit some stuff out
later, but. It shows that the
Blockchain and Crypto isn't it.
Yeah, I did not notice. I don't
know if it's a typo, you have.
What is technology?
Technological developments make
is wait. What technical
technological developments make
is possible? I'm assuming it's
meant to be it, but you have
that heading twice. Oh,
different lots of text.
OK, I'll probably. I'll look
that up, Yeah?
I am What's that it
is the most marks for this
assessment, so yeah, if anyone's
not happy with what someone's
got, then label means or I feel
that can be added. As I said, if
you feel like changing my
report, I don't care, just add
some stuff to it.
I think George finished his.
Hey. Yeah.
I haven't completed mine, but I
uploaded a file showing you guys
where I'm at right now, which is
a bit over halfway.
Ann, I haven't done any.
In Text Citation 'cause I'm.
Not really sure how to do that.
But I'm just adding all my
references down the bottom and
will come back and fix those
references up to make them
easier to do in text citation.
Is every time you.
Bring up like evidence or
something or something that you
didn't like. Obtain yourself.
So if you like reading article
or something, you just the
easiest ways to do like brackets
and then the name of the person
and then the date or the year.
If you want to get really like
academic like you can say you
know this person's findings
brackets the year and then.
Do they do it that way.
Oh no, I did I have done too.
I've done a quote from Elon Musk
and I just afterwards I wrote
like CEO. Sorry dash. Elon Musk,
CEO of Tesla at the China AI
Conference in July 2020, but I
haven't put a link there. I do
have a link to a video where he
said it. Um?
That's just in my references
down below but do you guys know
if I'm supposed to like add a
hyperlink to that quote
somewhere, although? That's
usually the best like maybe from
the sound of what you've you've
written like just put the date
the year in brackets.
OK, and then yeah, and if the if
the reference says like Elan
Musk is like the author or
whatever, then you can put him
in the brackets too.
Or whoever was doing the article
or whatever it was. It was well.
It's talked about all over the
Internet, but it was in a video
conference that he said. And the
recording is on YouTube from
Tesla China, which I'm not
certain is like it's that's the
only video they have there and
the only description of the
channel is the China, their
monthly specific thing for
referencing conferences as well.
Maybe look up like a Harvard
Guide. Further Want the link and
then just at the time and where
in the video he said it.
Knock. And then the
other one was.
I wish
I was
referencing. Something called
the Society of automated and
automotive engineers, an.
I said they created a standard
standard for less levels of
driving automation, and then
I've got. That's the title of
the standard and then I've just
put dash and then the link.
Dash and then continue my
sentence, but I appreciate
that's not how that
supposed to look.
So I'm not really sure how to do
that. Have to see it to workout.
To workout the best way but I
could, I could help if you put
it on the thing I can have a
look in. Offering you
suggestions or anything like
that. Um.
Gonna take me a second you
guys wanna talk about something.
So, so the the project has
that going guys.
I looked into the API but I
haven't written anything yet.
Yeah, for that, um Adam I was
wondering if you just wanted to
tell me whatever sections. You
don't want to write.
And I I'm not sure maybe the
motivation might be easiest for
me if I'm non technical.
Yeah, and a couple of others.
Pretty much yeah anything you
want me to do, just tell me and
I will do it. Yeah, Exeter.
Um?
Yep. Or salmon ladder
available 90, so I can pop in
few pieces here and there for
the project to yeah, I can
help contribute as well.
Sorry, that was my alarm.
On a on a new iPhone that she
was flexing on the force.
Count to 8 weeks for it all to
arrive. I wasn't trying to flex,
I was just getting really being
humorous. So it's
here.
Yeah guys say that Yep, Yep, so
that seems fine. I don't know if
it's like the Harvard Standard,
But. Yeah, normally what you
would do is you would do it in
text citation and then the link
would be in your references.
So that way you don't. That way
you don't have a big block of
text in your references. That
is, unless in your body, that
isn't unnecessary. OK, so would
I just. How would it in
text citation look?
It's like just after that bit
because that is the name of the.
Link right there.
How do I just?
Open brackets and say accessed
it at this date or open
brackets. It was created in
2016. I mean, I've already said
it's in 2016. So when you
when you accessed it or
whatever, that's usually in
your reference list, so.
Yeah, and the website would
probably be in the reference
list as well, OK, so I could
just remove that website drop it
down in my reference. List yeah,
OK and this, this, I've
screenshotted from that
document. It says down the
bottom that it can be the
summary table may be freely
copied and distributed provided
essay which is where I copied it
from international is are
acknowledged as the source and
must be reproduced as is so I
presume. I'm allowed to copy and
paste it like that.
Yeah.
Yeah, cool. So
why not? Doing anything
wrong and now I don't know
how to stop sharing.
Does anyone?
What? Is anyone given in Tesla?
No open in a taxi. Once in
Japan that was a Tesla.
Am I still sharing that screen?
Yes. Right?
And it was by signs one
anywhere, we go around it just
doesn't work.
No.
What tests do, but you
know, just sitting it up
and just watching it
dance is just insane.
And it's a very, very spacious
considering the size of Yeah.
Also went on a completely
electric bus as well. That was a
bit trippy. Yeah, so that they
have them in Japan as well. Did
you gonna bullet train, yeah.
What was that like with the
people pushes? Although they
don't usually on the bullet
trains, but I've been on the
people pushing trains as well.
Bit uncomfortable, specially
when it's late. Last train on a
Saturday night and you're in the
middle of Arthur nightclub area.
Pretty girl. Don't be doing that
in open set with the people
pushes on the train.
Yeah, the the Melbourne trains
like the seats are set up.
Really bad for high congestion.
Public transport. But anyway,
that's a different topic, yeah?
Cool.
Say with the IT project. Now
that few of us forgot.
Bit more bit more time to spare
I guess. Maybe we can help out
if you need anything any help on
that. The apps can
actually.
So privacy app to check your
social media accounts
privacy settings and then
make recommendations or
possibly changes.
Did we confirm that that it is
possible to view Facebook
settings? We can't change
anything, yeah, OK cool and
did we need to talk to him
about anything?
No, no
deliverables
will need a.
I think says it, so we need we
have deliverables for the app on
this assignment. Or is it the
next one? I don't think we do
for this one. I think you mighta
artifacts on the next one and
you need several of them.
Which Seattle sector rehash of
the project ID from the last
one? Yeah yeah you must
copy and paste. I think
from assignment one.
Since we're not using a project
idea from us anybody's
assignment one, we could just
switch to yours. You got pretty
good marks. We could we could
help you in face baby.
Don't say. Mine was A
at the time bank.
My people. Yeah, given our take
an hour in exchange for a
service.
Cryptocurrency.
We could swap it to that.
Or an anybody is really it's
already done. Yeah,
but I'm greatly.
Act Yeah, this is not really
worth that much effort, is it?
Just say the the.
The assessment sheet that you
need to expand on.
The items from assignment one,
so you can't just copy and
paste. They put they put that
little clause in there. Yeah, I
think you just have expanded on
it. Already too much when I did
assessment one. So.
There is it? It's actually
fairly short. So I think a
lot of wood and a lot of the
marks be in the artifacts.
I don't think so for this
assignment. No, not not not
number two I'm talking about
numbers. We need tangible
artifacts for the submission of
assignment 3. So in summary, we
actually have to have something
done with the project would have
to do a mock up of the website
and some of the code.
And if you feel like a
promotional video or something
as well. Presentation in the
Laderas in the next assignment.
Yeah, the promotional video was
an option as one of the
artifacts for number 3.
Just think like if we didn't
have ideas about that. If we
didn't have a lot of code to
provide them, we could provide a
video describing what the
outward or how it will local
bloody well just for this. If we
do the app, we can have some
just image templates of what the
app is going to look like, some
rough ones and some high quality
ones, and then other tangible
artifacts are our video
walkthroughs on for the Facebook
settings that we can't change
with the app.
That we have to give him a
tutorial for so they would have
been perfect deliverables. Yeah
yeah yeah. Yeah, whichever ones
more feasable I guess yeah.
The Apple ID is probably the
easiest one to do. Yeah, because
that's just some photoshopped
pictures, or we can use one of
those tools that he linked to
us. Last time. I think it might
have been answering link. Just
two UI designers for apps and
the videos, or we can just
recording with webcam.
Yeah, and open broadcast.
So we go to the website and
then we have to write a whole
website and do images.
So we're thinking we might stick
with what we've got now.
At this stage.
Yeah,
yeah.
Yeah.
Cooper is a
Can you hear me?
Time. Hello
really quiet
like.
Not better.
Yeah, little
bit. I don't know
if it's me or not.
Yeah, that's alright. I can turn
up my volume so I can just see.
Change. Problems
there. 3. Shannon
can yell but no one else Yo
'cause I'm at full volume here.
For some reason, my volume on my
front panel just keeps on.
Dicking around.
I can hear I can hear you
fine now. Not not normal,
but I can hear you.
Yeah. Too
much. Sorry,
better.
Mark volume is moving by itself.
It doesn't make sense to me.
I might have corrupted it when I
was playing around with it
before. It's it's it that you
always at 80. Now it's slowly
climbing to 90 and it did jump
20 before so I don't know what's
going on? That's right, so
much gave me perfect.
Now it's good.
No so now now like that, we're
going to do next so.
I guess the thing that we all
need to sort of do is the ideal
jobs. Comparison. So now that
we've got the results back we
can. Have a better idea of our
ideal jobs were good enough or
not so. OK, I think that's The
One I did best actually.
I think I did Alright there. You
said that my I picked a similar
answer to most other people in
the most people picked a entry
level or general.
Just like you Sam I think.
Specifically, entry level, one,
but it was sort of like the
upper level of if you would
choosing a broad path so yeah,
sorry? Yeah. Except George.
Yeah. Ken
16 online
But mainly because my
description wasn't for the job
posted. I got 21.
At 22
20 Why don't
we push down?
I'm Jenna. OK, thank you, I
didn't even finish my sentence
and. Where I get?
21.
Ideal
job.
I just checked Georges
IT technology submission for
cloud services and servers
is not finished that
argue. You have got typos,
and yeah, there's big
chunks sing so.
I know Tim said a lot of IT
professionals started with first
level support. That's what I
meant, Sam, OK?
Not not anything to do with.
So yeah, so we sort
of needlework yet how to?
Use the ideal job comparison so.
Yeah, we need to sort of
workout? What differentiates
between all our positions and.
I feel like that stuff.
I just wrote a paragraph doing
that like from my perspective,
yeah, so that was good.
So could we?
Could we do like a quote from
each of us stating?
How ALP, but our choice was
different to other peoples
choices. We do a graffle.
Something. Typing at the end I
guess. This to you could do it,
rotting and doing like visual
elements as well.
And you're pretty much get
marked on how concise everything
is, so if we're all doing
separate paragraphs, that might
not be as consistent as it could
be. No. So could we do
a graph with like?
We could identify some of the
features that are common in the
jobs and then on one access have
like. Entry level
Specific or security and then
each one that fits into
security. It'll be on the other
axis or something like that.
We need to workout some criteria
for if we're gonna do like a
table thing, like some broad
criteria and then we can add a
bit of information of each of us
in there to see who's more
similar and who's more
different. When we're getting is
a radar graph for that.
For the Does the
industry daughter? I think yeah.
Which is an LC very similar.
There are similar but a bit
different out of the industry
data was like.
So the industry daughter is more
what what skills are in demand.
So, which section are we
comparing in so the ideal job
one. If you go to
the assignment PDF page 4,
coming to canvas going too.
Minutes and then the assignment
and then click the PDF there's
two sections that mention.
Jobs one of them is about
industry data. Yeah, and the
other one is about us. Each
comparing our job selection to
the other people. People
selections in the industry data.
When it refers back to the
assignment page. Not the PDF but
where you get the PDF it refers
to a link on that page.
Um? Wait, you can look up.
Ah, how frequently people are
looking for the time skills that
are listed in your job that you
picked. That's OK.
Yeah, I just did that.
I did the industry data on this
afternoon, which is pretty much
just the same as Shannon did it
just answering all the questions
in the industry data section.
Yeah, so am I getting that
right? Shannon don't know.
So industry data is page 5 by
the way, and then the ideal job
is the page for yeah.
Hi.
I just I was looking at the.
Obviously, the rubric of how
much point marks yet for it.
And it's not like industry data
is pretty high, up as opposed to
profile and it just seems the
what we have in the ideal job in
the profile outweighs? How much
we have in industry data.
That makes sense. 9.
So you're saying.
Is the is the job comparison
weighing more than the
industry data and industry
data is weighing more than
the profile so team profile
pretty much has all the
different things in it, and
the so the ideal jobs.
Further team profile. You'd
say, would be like 2 points
out of the five or one point
out of five when you get the
industry. Data is worth 10
out of the possible 100.
OK, at 10 miles out of 100 where
instead of the ideal jobs in
team profiles worth to be out of
the 100. Just just seems what
I have in industry dad. I'm
just answering the questions,
seems very lacking for the
section of 10 points as
opposed to how much I've
written for ideal job in team
profile.
I think that's where it'll help.
If we've got that spider web
graph comparing the different
skills. In the industry auto
section. Yeah, for the table in
ideal jobs, it can just be super
basic like almost just our names
and then the positions like and
then maybe expand another couple
of fields. But yeah, you can
just be super simple I think
like one accesses our name and
our job title access
similarities or differences,
yeah, maybe some if we just do.
Maybe at the fields of the job
titles. Maybe have a tiny bit of
overlap or even just hardware
based software based.
Something broad like that and
not not touch on any of the
skill set stuff and label the
skill set stuff for the
industry data section, yeah?
So probably break it up into
like software hardware, customer
facing non customer facing. Yeah
nice broad fields for the jobs
and then just do a line graph
and where they overlap.
Yeah, yeah. And then you got it
there, yeah and then and then
we just do our paragraph each
and that's ideal jobs done sort
of things 'cause for the for
the exemplary Marks and team
profile it just says a clear
discussion of the differences
between your ideal jobs.
That's it, yeah, so did we need
ideal jobs in our individual
profiles. Or do we just put that
thing and we needed to? I think
that was what it that's in the
group profile. If we do, we have
a spot for a collective group
description of some or some
sort. Details. The home
page. Do you like a little bit
of like an about us? Yeah
paragraph or something, yeah.
Or like we could change the team
profiles and push the individual
pictures down and we can put
text in there for like a summary
of everybody. And I'm I'm
thinking just just for this spot
like is there just for this
topic about different jobs?
Because it's not each individual
person. It's all of us
collectively on one graph is
that? Can we make a spot or?
Collective. He's about us not
not like a summary of us, but
just somewhere after pizza
better jobs is that what I'm
getting. Yeah, like a like a
spot where we can just put it
graph that includes information
about all of our different jobs,
a small gram. So if I just put
it on you page in under team
profile called ideal jobs, we
can push it in there. Yeah yeah
yeah. 'cause it doesn't fit
under 1 profile. It doesn't fit
under one yet. Even I think sums
of weather team or the ideal job
in there, you know in all same
profile already. I just copied
offered and it honestly in his.
Oregon is still OK to have that
and then have a summary as well.
Yeah, sorry, I lost track of
what you're talking about
showing. So Dan, annoying. I'm
not too sure if anyone else is
done it in the profile
themselves. We've given ideal
job in a paragraph underneath.
Yeah, simple simplistic
paragraph with differences and
similarities to everyone in our
group, OK? Did you want to just
leave it there then? Do you mean
I see no reason why you get
marked down for having extra?
He did say he didn't want him to
leave. Yeah.
OK, just like a description
paragraph, then describing how
it's differential similar to
everyone else is.
Yeah. Two or three
questions in the ideal job
section. OK. Yeah, and so.
So we'll stick to making putting
a bit more information in the
industry data section, because
that's way more.
Yep. Ann
So once we've all completed our
industry data like.
Does Shannon?
Trying and Daniel.
Yeah, so once we
I think Shannons down at George
is done at an.
Send an in George of done
industry data. Have you done
yours? Said no no, I had to look
at the burning glass but I
didn't like commit anything to
write yet. Yeah I uploaded mine
to the to GitHub but I haven't
actually uploaded it to.
Ms teams I don't mind I didn't
take it for an get so I'll grab
it from there and it pretty much
all I did was look at the big
chart that had all the skills
like rank to what was the number
one skill and then the lower
skill. That's pretty much all I
got so far. So what I've
actually done, sorry.
I just waiting the rubric tears
you have clearly and accurately
identified and ranked your
groups required skill set now in
team profile on teams I did make
a graph table setup using Green
Glass Garden. Um.
That could probably go
into industry down.
But where is it?
For graphing teams, tables for
grub, yeah, I was thinking we
could use that for that spider
web thing, but now I'm thinking
that would be better suited to
the industry data where it used
the burning glass and then
separates us into different.
Shows Yeah. I'm not too
sure. So maybe before the next
meeting like we can all.
Finalize that burning glass
things individually. Then the
next meeting we can all
collaborate and. Workout what we
can, how we can bring it all
together. Possibly. Yeah I
have. I have consolidated some
of the headings into like a one.
For example all the programming
language I've just put
programming skills. The thing
you were talking about before
Shannon, whatever use brought
together from. Burning glasses
that was going. Yeah, I'm not
sure I understand what you're
talking about, so I see it.
But it sounds like you've got
something sorted already. Is
that what you're saying?
Typing with all their names down
the side. Adams adding and
editing it. At the moment I'm
just looking at it trying to
workout. What kind of graph I
can make it.
That actually looks pretty cool
with someone else entertaining
for anyway. Real time editing.
Yeah.
We could probably make it a
biograf, or we can make a line
graph if you wanna see overlap
of different different skill
sets, I think overlap would be.
Be good 'cause I think did I
want some comparison in this
section or not.
Yeah.
I just find it again.
Let's see accurately identified
in branchial groups required
skill sets. South ready that
seem that group situation that
lists are saw.
Which Wich?
Hey profile
in teams.
Change profile files
and it's called
table for ideal
job go. May just be pretty
much just the top 10.
For the skills.
I'll just consolidated the
programming languages as I said
to just programming languages.
But I don't know if that's
any help for.
It works.
So the ranking system was that
something. Ranking wonder
10 most. I was gonna say.
10 being most important to your
ideal job. And one being least
important that makes sense OK,
so it wasn't expired is based on
necessity. I think, OK, so it
wasn't to do with burning
glasses. Most popular skills. It
was to do with what you thought
the industry was looking for for
that job. Yeah, so I've put in.
So burning glass has it stop
representations. That's what
we're filling out, and then the
ranking system for each
individual's for your ideal job,
as opposed to.
Like for example, graphic
design, I'll go one on one
because it be.
Wouldn't be needed to do sub
security? That makes sense
otherwise, and other
programming programming
languages being 10 'cause you
would need another programming
languages.
Where is the program?
When you say windows in I, I
guess you mean the operating
system. Or yeah, how to open a
window. System.
So these are two graphs, yeah,
so the combined together so
it's got top IT skills and
then top generic skills.
I'll have to come back to
this 'cause I'm just not
getting.
When when you go to the burning
glass site, you'll start to work
it out. After all, they're all
sort of in demand skills that
are listed on burning glass.
OK. I just I just found it hard
to interpret my ideal job across
to the tables. 'cause I don't
know too much about some of it.
Um? What time with for example?
You sometimes may work in a
team, but then other times
you might not work in a
team. So is it?
It's one of the top skills
required, but how necessary is
it to doing your job?
OK, so are you. Are you
ranking it based on what
you what you think the
employer values at at or?
Yeah. Something or what
burning glass values added
support popularity what you
value it has.
OK.
So have you value?
Like if I thought that I was
going to need a very good
comprehension of Windows
computers, but not Max then I
would put Windows 10 and Mac
Cicilline. Yeah, or if you
needed a general understanding
you would put a 7 or like you
don't need a?
Like you need another basic
skills, but you don't need to
know absolutely everything about
it. It can drop in value.
Getting
I prefer the minus
10,000 Adam Yeah.
So much I might try that.
Think it might ruin our mark.
So, for example, offers you make
it if you double clicks the
graph, it changes things like
that to minus 10,000.
That's in. I'm just having sex.
I thought Daniel Just go just
for person 87654.
Yeah, pretty much what do you
feel is? I should I can't
member the write something
in the actual.
Teams of how
The
corner.
Yeah.
Wanted to system as to
how important it is to
your ideal job.
Yeah.
Oh
What was the
next Sam? RT project do you like
continued So what? Are we going
to do next for the IT project?
They've been recording for 5050
minutes. OK, no, no. The
meeting's been gone for 15
minutes isn't. Not the meetings
been going for 57 but the
recordings been going for 50.
The long run impressed in.
I'll just, you know, really
reduce the quality, may be black
and white. So yeah, I take
project continued as in for the
next assignment or so. I don't
know what's the next step that
we need to do, or is there
anything that we need to other
people to do or anything like
that? Pretty much got to
describe their product. Yep, at
least the technologies we're
going to use in the product.
I'm.
And then expand on it, really.
Sections from assignment one
yeah. If we had to use GitHub,
but if we just make a word file
in the Ms teams and just edit
edit it as you go, so everyone
can just keep up with it instead
of what. I think we've only got
a stored on GitHub when my done.
No way everyone can just add to
it. As soon as I see fit.
You have the other groups can
steal their stuff. Yeah.
So we're going with idea for
assessment to or yeah.
They probably run still yeah,
yeah, yeah. Unless we
wanna make life harder on
the next two assignments.
So when when is this one drew?
How long have we gotta do? We
need to make a plan.
Sorry, some groups that haven't
even started yet. I think all we
really have is our project idea
in our feedback. Really to go. I
mean there is some obviously
some more work to do on some
reports and that but the base is
there. We gotta do the interview
on Saturday, the work section,
the project. Any follow up to
the interview? Like do we need
to describe what we've learned
or talk about, how it's relevant
to us, or do we need to do
anything there? Or is it just an
interview for our best days just
to you? And then we write
something about the questions so
we can just a quick thing on
that. We do need to summarize at
least 10 YouTube videos or other
web sources. To do that, that's
only if you don't do an
interview. I think no, it's a
different one. If you was it, I
don't know what that that. Don't
worry, I misread it. So sorry,
sorry to scare everyone.
Like 10 videos. I don't know if
I can watch linustechtips that
lot many times it alright.
So we need to get the last.
We get the reports done, get the
project description done, and
then make sure all contributing
to get.
Stuff. Yep.
What was that him? We gotta do?
Group feedback or something as
well. Group of reflection. After
we've done everything to before,
we submit it, we got to reflect
on our group.
Because that other external
site, we gotta do.
Set Tim was meant to tell us
about all this we've got to do
this. Yeah, that's um, I
think week eight, so I think
there might be. After we've
submitted maybe. And then
there's the contribution
shape we've got to do as
well. On the PDF, we've
gotta collect everything
onto a PDF. Yeah, yeah, oh,
that's easy. Which we've got
all the individual documents
so we can just.
Oh, got it like go through the
'cause it might look different
once it gets to the website.
There might be things added or
taken away so we can just copy
and paste from the website.
Pretty much for mine. All I did
was copy and paste from the
website into a Word document.
Yeah, and it kept most of the
formatting. I just tided it up
just a tiny little bit. I
thought it looked ship but Tim
is that. It looks great, but.
I love morning was screenshots
of the wizard.
How's it gonna type out again? I
just hope that looks good on the
website. It can be screenshotted
yeah? So.
Yeah, do that again so we just
need to get all of our
individual stuff done by the
next meeting. Basically, yeah,
so do you want to everyone can
review each other's work as
well? Yeah yeah, yeah. So like
the industry daughters, someone
wants to raise the other persons
or we all do it just to see if
there's any changes that need to
be made or if it's lacking in
somewhere. Yeah, I copied mine
some Ms teams as well so you
can. Hello. I'm
gonna get that that locker and
I'm just gonna circle like
everywhere draw things.
Although I still feel like I
need to add some things to mine.
It's just I wanted to get the
base reports out of the way so I
can look over and add more
stuff. If we had time or with
the way that I said it out. If
you check it out there's just
one file each for each one of
those that is gonna edit.
I like cyber security is in the
data folder. If you go to the
web page, it tells you at the
bottom when you've selected it
for location data. IT
technologies IT cybersecurity.
And then you can just edit the
individual ones and this
formatting already in place for
you. If you wanna do that, or I
can put do it doesn't bother me.
If we need to individually add
out bits and pieces where we
where we can just to get you
can. It's up on yeah or even if
it's just like taking your Word
document and committing it to
the master branch like into the
individual folders. It's just to
show that you've got an
understanding on how to check in
and check stuff out again.
No, go ahead.
At 7:30 now, so just go
through and change spelling
mistakes 1 by 1.
I guess you commit.
Commit and then commit, and then
I'll get a check something and I
would like *** **** it.
Merge, Merge, Merge Merge
Management. Um? Next
week.
This has been a long meeting, we
probably do not need a second
one. We're making up for not
having to meetings last week. I
guess it splits into two it
could classes two meetings this
week, too. Quick stop the
recording and then we'll start
it again. And when I upload it.
I'll read ate it and top that
bit off that I just said what we
were doing. Do you want me to do
that? Is that possible?
Well, George is here now, so
it'll look like this and you
meeting. Yeah, except it's gonna
come up in the recording with
the square of George.
Hello. Hey welcome, I think he's
microphones on me. Oh yeah.
Sorry schedule another meeting
for this week or the weekend or
or we got the interview. Oh yeah
that could be a meeting, but I'm
free Sundays also hello. Hey
George, sorry oh. It's all good.
Victorians in their daylight
savings. Yeah, didn't realize
until like run from work OK.
We want to perform at least for
next Wednesday at a different
time. Dare. 730 Victorian
time, which will be
630 QLD. Yeah, yeah,
I could just sit there.
Five 5:30 WA.
4:30. It was 3:30
for me today, so get 6:30
meeting. Do I have time or
savings they used to? I think
about 10 years ago maybe. Yeah,
headache that they had this
Traglia is its own country now.
Daniel 4:30, right now
over here.
Please.
Hello, I just assumed Daniel was
in Vic. I thought you were.
And then I'm just looking at
your window like Oh, it's bright
out there. So 730
Victorian time. OK.
Yeah, we can make it later. I
get if I to help in the Wii
people. I don't mind anytime is
good for me works.
I can do 7:30.
So it's OK with you George.
Yeah, yeah, 7630 your time
George. Yeah Yeah, 'cause I
finished at 6 so I still have
half an hour.
And were all who who
wasn't available for 10:00 AM
Saturday. 9:00 AM
Queensland Dollar.
Which I don't think is a huge
problem because they essentially
said on the assignment that it
had, like if it was an in person
interview, which it obviously
can't be. They recommended two
people. Obviously we'd prefer
everyone, but not everyone can
attend. I don't think that's a
big deal. In person interview
because of all like Melbourne
people were on lock down. I
don't know what it's like in
Queensland. No? I mean they just
didn't specify how many of us
had to be attending in the
online interview, Yeah?
And spices, there's no
restrictions there. We can do
whatever we want. I had
Westerners generally, is more
open. Yeah, but they don't want
to open their borders with
anyone. They've always wanted to
be their own country anyway, so
yeah, Queensland following suit
to borders shut easel.
Play George Junior. Wanna
Summary of what we've kind of
talked about? Or will you re
watch this? Yeah yes please yeah
yeah just a quick to see what
where we are.
Sam, did you want to summarize
or I will yeah so first we
discussed about our assignment
results. Ah, yeah, if anyone had
any anything to say about that
so. Yes.
Yeah, my assignment. I thought I
was not going to be that very
good. I knew that my IT project
in my my presentation wasn't
going to be that very good.
Yeah, but yeah, it was pretty
basic. My presentation so that
really didn't help with my grade
and as well with the IT project
as well, I didn't knew too much
what you put in it.
And Yeah, it didn't help,
either. But? Yeah, did you get
any helpful feedback?
Yeah, yeah, actually those two
subjects that I just mentioned
that's that's what team said to
me, yeah, I didn't elaborate,
too much. I wasn't too
ambitious. Kind of in respect to
the IT project.
More help you do more of like a
reset. Yeah, so at least I know
where I. Yeah.
You passed. Yeah.
What is next time next
time? Look did progress reports,
so how you?
IT technology. Papers going in
your team profile as well.
Yeah, well, I've done that yeah,
I already finished that.
Yeah, cloud cloud, cloud
computing and yeah, my profile
and everything else is done yet.
Did you submit it to the?
To the team's been yet.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
OK cool, yeah.
And the How did you do
the industry?
Dota 1 yet?
Ah yeah that one, too, yeah,
it's in the.
Uh. Is separate from ideal?
Where is it? I'll get something
get confused with all the steps?
It's under industry data George
at your job, yeah, so yeah.
Yeah, is there too as well.
Also, you don't industry data
and ideal jobs. Yeah, oh cool.
So it ahead.
We kind of concluded that we
would get all of what you've
just said done by the next
meeting, 'cause not all of us
are there. Yes, so, but the plan
was was to everyone does like
the industry data thing and then
the next meeting will
collaborate and work. It had to
bring it all together.
Yeah, that's what I was thinking
too. 'cause Yeah, not until we
all do that. We can start like
yeah, putting everything
together and see how we?
Relates to one another.
So if if you choose to re
watch this recording,
you'll see like kind of
what we tossed around and
brainstormed, but
essentially will have will
have to all do our
individual pieces before we
can set anything in stone.
Yeah. Harrison
Um. George is the ideal job
section of that file you
uploaded is that for the ideal.
Is that two documents in one?
Oh, so you had the industry data
at the bottom and the ideal job
at the top. Yes, two separate
ones is it? Yeah, two separate
ones. Right then you want me to
put him together. I don't know.
And I already together is only
one document there. Yes, that's
the first paragraph looks like.
So ideal job section, yeah?
So the there were two topics,
one about industry data and one
about our comparing our
individual chosen jobs. So there
they were a bit different.
'cause I've got.
It's like this.
Industry data. I
did not. IT support
specialist and down the
bottom. I had another
sectional. Yeah sorry.
Industry data.
Some, do you want me to
separate it? Yeah no, no.
It's all one document, isn't
it? Yeah, that's All.
So it's meant to be 2
separate ones George.
Ah, so yours is just in one, so
just separate ideal job into the
ideal job section and then I'll
just leave your industry data
paragraph. In there on the site
where I've got a moment.
I think if you re watch out,
like what we've talked about. We
went over it a few times 'cause
it was a bit complicated.
And kind of sussed it out.
OK, yeah, that's all good.
That's clear, an Adam too dumb
we wanna talk about potentially
a once. This is once we've all
got our individual stuff done.
You offered to help us do some
commits if we're not really sure
how to do that in a group
setting. Yep. We can't commit to
anything like that just yet. Can
we
Wait? So
very check that.
Said the word Commission to
different circumstances.
You said you might be able to
help us a little bit with
learning how to do that if we're
not quite sure you have example
another meeting booked after
this. So if you wanna do it, I
can give you a walk through and
show you how to do it. Or should
we wait until we've?
All of us of each individually
done our pieces. Um?
Have you have you got any
documents on teams that already
that I finished already or?
Um? Could you probably
wanna timeline of commits rather
than just a whole heap at the
end? You probably won't say that
you know you've done a commit On
this date this day. This day,
this day. Yeah.
So that doesn't look like
OK. We you know everyone
just done one or two at the
last minute to make it look
like everybody used git.
My interim personality test is
completed. You can even upload
unfinished stuff as well because
it will just add the changes
next time you do another commit.
OK, well I've got one. I've
got at least one finished
file and then I've got one
unfinished file, upload it
on teams at the moment. So
yeah, yes, so should we wrap
up and stop the recording.
So, so just confirm what we have
to do for before the next
meeting so. Everyone needs to
get the burning class burning
glass data done.
And finish any reports or
anything or that, yeah, finish
your reports and your profile.
So I've gotta I've gotta
complete my industry data.
And the project summary
basically assessment one stuff.
Yeah with Daniel.
Yep.
I'm gonna do my.
Website my technology.
Yep. Burning glass job
summary. Yep.
That's pretty much all, and then
we got the interview in between,
so that'll be good.
So with the with the interviewer
we doing that like what platform
are we doing that on on teams or
that were users teams? We can
just invite him to the meeting
as a guest arc. It's cool, yeah?
Sweets and then we can use teams
to record it rather than have to
use something else and yeah.
So should we
He's probably watching is
right now. Should we attempt
to be there a few minutes
early if possible?
Yeah. 510 minutes early do
mic checks and stuff, yeah.
And I'll try and make myself
less purple. Well, they can
complain to him about that it's
teams doing that.
Not. Adjust the computer
to surface surface like Surface
tablet. You can also blame that
as well. Is that ragging on it
like this? This is a red jumper
and it doesn't work now? This is
definitely a red jumper. Now
it's now it's purple pink.
Yeah, it looks red.
That's just the wall behind you
that's Purple. Oh Oh, let's read
it looks the same as you jump to
the man is the person that
painted this rental was. I think
there were couple born.
Our last rental I think was
painted by Hippies or something
there was light lime green lemon
yellow dark Brown and bright
purple bright pink and Apricot.
Well, I like to prove my kids in
is is green on one wall, but it
looks like they did it with a
sponge for like WAVY lines in it
and then put glitter on it and
then it's pink on the.
Click on the other
wall. Alright, can you hear me
now? Yeah yeah, think on the
other wall and then it's like
blue on the roof.
The roost cheese. Yeah, they
painted the reflow.
Alright, we should. We should
wrap this up and yeah, I have to
go now. OK, I'll end this
recording. Fighting
mongooses go.