So first group meeting on
the. 26 of
September.
And I will meet my friend.
Sorry.
He was it was on earlier today,
but I just haven't seen him
since about. 12 one o'clock.
I thought we.
Started too early so we haven't
heard back from Adam.
Will probably be here any minute
I guess yeah.
Happy to wait.
Yeah. So what do you guys
think of assignment one? How did
you go with assignment? 1M? How
you feeling post?
I think it was OK.
Like it was a bit more work than
I expected for.
I don't know if I did too
much or not, but.
Or too little I I'm not really
sure 'cause. Is there's like a
lot of elements that you had to
put together. And I think my
website was pretty gross.
Black one black one. Yeah
yeah yeah that one.
Purple, pink or purple or
something like that. Yeah, like
when I originally did the links
like they were like a really
dark blue and I couldn't see
them so I made in pink and it
looked really good with the
Black. Yeah, I like that. That's
what I remember about it. I saw
it in the like the rubric it
discussed how it needs to look
good. But I don't really know
what they expect. The good
looking website to be. Yeah, I
like. I like my 2002 vibe for my
website, so it's pretty good.
Couple of your websites looked
really good, so I mean they were
pretty good, but I'm I think a
few of them. Like with the
Scroll down and like the.
The section changed as you
Scroll down. That was really
good. I think that might've been
you George or someone.
No, I think that was a Adam. Or
maybe Adam. Yeah, yeah. I think
Shannon had the best like title
page that was super slow. Yeah
yeah, that's a template. Or use
that said, you could use a
template. So I decided to go
with it. Yeah, why not? It looks
pretty good. I mean it did take
a little bit of editing in it,
but not as much as I thought.
Find any templates I like trying
to collect all of the resources
for GitHub and like all of the
HTML stuff and.
All new to me, but I didn't
realize there were things like
that to go off of this so much
information that I found after
submitting the assignment that
would help me, and there's still
more than I'm discovering now.
I'm like, oh, that would have
helped. That would help.
Yes, I would have liked to have
made menus or like multiple
windows that would be nice. Most
multiple tabs I mean.
Yeah, I spent a lot of time on
W3 schools looking at random
stuff. That's pretty much how I
yeah, no. Website actually
actually don't think it's that
bad, but was it W 3 schools or
the other one that was like one
I found really easy and one that
I found really hard.
I just love you guys. Can't hear
things like here Mega website.
Yeah you like.
Rules are light. It was the
other one that was like a
tutorial on what you did a
walkthrough tutorial, so I can't
get it. That on some of those
GitHub tutorials I had were a
bit a bit full on yeah and then
and then Tim just did it like in
two seconds on the lecture.
Yeah yeah, and I found a written
format of that. Those directions
and really simple form after
they submitted the assignment.
So cool I'll say that later, but
I'm is. I did let the whole
thing. They followed the video
where it used their terminal to
use GitHub. But I'm just scared
of using it and accidentally
like destroying everything. But
in the right run command like,
I'm pretty sure like it it
wouldn't, but you know.
Just like one command and you've
just like destroyed everyone
else is work kind of thing,
Yeah? I I did all of mine within
GitHub on my browser. I didn't
use anything else. I didn't use
a text file or anything, 'cause
I just didn't know how. Yeah I,
I ended up doing that halfway
through 'cause it's just easy
like when I was like adding
photos and stuff. I just dragged
it in instead of pushing into
the repository. So I'm I'm still
learning all of the commands.
Off the website.
Where can I might like when when
last we do this again for
assignment two? I might like
right down my own commands like
guide sheet or formula died
once. Yeah, what about you
George? How do you go?
Yeah, mine was pretty simple
like just like plain white an
yeah I was reading a lot of.
W3 that that website and I'll
just basically just like
following every step. And yeah I
read a lot.
But yeah, I think like I have a
copy of my.
Of my website, so I think I can
you know, as we progress, I
think I can just keep keep
changing things and then just
keep making it like look.
Better. It's just the start, so
yeah. Yeah, we heard
from Adam yet.
Not yet. I thought there were
six of us and then I thought
there were five of us, and then
there's definitely 6 and I
thought I was going a bit nuts.
I think I think originally there
was six, I don't, I'm not sure.
Yeah. They're they're still six.
I mean, it was like an hour ago.
I was like 5.
What what's the limit on team
members is like 6 or 6?
OK.
Pretty good, that's right. Try
recommended in four to six.
Oh, maybe Phil Haack
in sometimes?
Yeah.
Bad or something when you want.
When you start a meeting mine I
didn't get anything.
Nominator. Charlie going. I
think we have to put it on the
on the calendar maybe and then
you get like a reminder,
something I didn't add it in
through. I didn't add actual
attendees, I just automatically
assumed that goes for everyone
in the group, but my reminder
came through Microsoft Outlook
itself. I had outlook open,
so there the reminder came
up through outlook.
No, I really want three screens.
It's great. I'm
not sure. I've just opened Ms
teams on my laptop.
Yeah. But
it didn't.
That's alright.
Anyone have any good name ideas?
Yes, just thinking that like no.
I was thinking about that the
other day. Yeah 'cause it says
in the. Assignment like shape
that like employers could look
it up later.
So yeah, we don't do so. Be
mindful of you silly.
Damn nonhuman
sign. It's something cool,
something that sounds like smart
and technical. Yeah,
yeah, nothing. Did they
give you some sort of format for
the teams? Like
We sort of sport wise or I I
have no idea like even examples
of teams they said it could be
anything. But my friend started.
It is like Oh Nighty Company and
it was called Ret SIM which is
just Mr backwards. But it looks
like a really fancy technology
name. Yes.
Try putting aladji on the end of
another word. Yeah.
This is not my Department.
Maybe we can think
on that as we
go, yeah? Sure.
Our agenda first was team
profile name and.
So it's kind of roles in the
group, but we can.
I was thinking maybe we could
start with. 'cause I seem to
want us to.
Discuss assignment one abit and
how that impacts us as a group
is bizarre but.
We've got to do that.
Sign in. The
assignment 2.
What page in my arm?
Page.
Page 2 actually.
No.
No, you're
right. Um yeah, so
profile.
Page 4
profile down
to specifications. Um, that
aim profile so will need a team
name, but we can think on that.
That doesn't need to come first.
It we're having trouble there.
Um, so will each need to wash
our own little paragraph of
personal information. Which I
think we can do separately and
then just bring that down.
That's fairly straightforward.
Yeah, and then we need to
discuss the the test that we've
the personality test. I think
they mean. Um, I'm just
what that means for us.
Spell and you will have a chance
to reflect on how well you got
this work later, so giving you
feedback on assignment one as
well, and I'm not sure if like
we're supposed to talk about the
results from our first
assignment as well. They will
wait for the hour, yeah?
I think we need to touch on it
by def. It's definitely
mentioned that we should talk
about it, yeah?
But the other country that just
yet. But we can talk about the
three personality tests for the
team profile. Just to, I'm not
sure how they want us to write
that out, but it says to
condense the relevant content
you produced from assignment
one. I I completely misread, so
I can't condense one anymore.
It's pretty much basic as it
was. Only write 11 big paragraph
about the all three tests.
'cause I honestly think
these tests were. I don't
know. They just.
Yeah, they're slightly accurate,
but. I found
something, yeah? After it
very accurate too as well.
I found one pretty accurate,
150% accurate and one was like
completely the opposite of me.
I think I think two of mine
actually got contradicted each
other a little bit. Yeah, I got
that. Yeah, but like I don't
know if it's just like you know
when you see like a tarot card
reader and they say Oh yeah,
this and this and like put
connections in your head that
you might not really be
connected with. Yeah yeah, that
explains me perfectly when it
doesn't really. And then it
becomes a bit of a self
fulfilling prophecy. Or it's
just so broad that it can
attribute to anyone. New things
will be happening to you
tomorrow. Probably like you, you
may end up with financial
troubles in the coming months.
You know, or you have to pay
bills or something? I could have
told you that.
Now I will.
Yeah, I'm sorry, maybe we just
need to. It says to summarize or
condense. So I think maybe it's
like. So who was
introverted? I was.
Yeah, I got like 79%.
Wake up 99.
Not sure. I think online were
pretty like. Similar like I was
like a bit of everything, but I
got like the turbulent mediator.
From the 16 personalities one,
yeah I got mediator as well,
yeah? Well I got.
The learning styles 1.
Like it was a bit of bit of
everything as well. For the
learning styles I had.
Visual learner and partly
kinesthetic. So it was like
even Stevens, but slightly
slightly more visual.
Wish my brain was
working a little faster
today. People do for the third
test like the one you could
choose like. I just did another
personality one. Yes I do it,
yeah. Yeah, same.
As I look through the other ones
and I just didn't really, I felt
the output of the actual thing
wasn't. I like told you whether
you're one of two different
things you know, like, yeah.
Aspera, see how lucky you are to
fully conspiracy theory one.
I don't know if you wanna tell
your employee that kind of.
Employer that kind of
information. Think only added
one year. It's just what I run.
What kind of celebrity
personality do you represent?
Like it, it gives you the other
percentages. But then what?
Celebrities? Nice life and mine
came out as Dexter and I thought
that wasn't right.
Good thing this isn't online
course I guess. I just thought I
just, you know, take that away,
not put that one on there.
Around this.
My computer is slightly frozen.
Camera like very
dark. Yeah I can. I can
just see a silhouette every Adam
pretty dark. You look like a
hacker offi ads, yeah?
Yeah, I got the computer screen
glowing on you, so it looks even
more ominous. If I can fix
it, but it keeps giving me
an error when I get a load
up the camera settings.
So I just want you doing that
and I'll just summarize what
we've touched on so far, so we
haven't come up with a group
name yet, because that's.
A lot of creativity, so I'm just
thinking about that in the
background as we talk.
Um, and then we kind of talked
about assessment one, how many,
how we went. Obviously we don't
have any feedback yet. We don't
have our mark, so we can't talk
about that. But they do want us
to at some point.
And then we need to summarize
out personality tests and woman
into. Like a great personality
or summary of the personalities
within the group. So we're just
going over our personality test
results. Just briefly, and I
think we'll have to.
OK Alright. Personality summary,
like obviously some of us have
summarized it quite a lot, but
if we could just put 4 hours, 16
personalities the Myers Briggs
test, we could just put the the
name rather than the description
and then for the next one.
Whether we are a.
Visual learner, kinesthetic
learner or. So like 7 rise again
in like 160 words to the for the
page. Yeah I yeah.
Or even I think
because the. It works.
Say.
Yep. As a only a small
mark that it gets anyway, yeah,
it doesn't make too much if it
like. The Rubric says that it's
just all relevant information
and keeping it simple.
I have to get, expects us to
write like a big essay on group
dynamics and that kind of stuff.
So like I'm thinking if I was to
write mine, I'd write that I am
a. What is
my?
Oh, it's an ISFP dash T, which
means the adventurer and just a
sentence on what that means. And
then I would put that on a
mostly visual learner but partly
tactile kinesthetic learner
probably don't need to write.
And then a like a very
short summary of might be
quiet personality test. So
we could each do that and
just leave that there if we
want it. What do you think?
Sounds like. So are we
also said earlier Adam that we
need to do a tiny?
I'm just looking at the
assignment team profile on page
4. Have you got that off in
front of you? I
go in a minute.
Yeah,
I
got
it
open
now. Page 4
Um, down at specifications.
So we haven't come up with a
name yet, but will will do that.
That's straight forward and then
personal information. We can.
Each writer and paragraph and
then bring that together and
just put on the page and then
for the team profile each
summarize our three tests and
then put that in there as well.
Sorry, do you think we could
each do that individually?
Interest rate altogether.
Yeah yeah, yeah.
So. We want
to ideal jobs.
We
Yes. Time to organize this one,
so it might be good to have some
regular times. At least one
scheduled time each week.
Scheduled half an hour or
something at least. I've been
looking through the assignment
details and what team said in
the. The. Meeting this
week. It seems like we have to
do too, but it would be good to
have at least one plan.
Sorry, can we all available
tomorrow to do this week
second meeting? Or does
anyone not available
tomorrow afternoon evening?
I can after 630
again. Or not, yeah,
I'm fine. Or or or tomorrow
morning, but I know I think one
of you is from Perth. That might
be a bit. Yeah, I could
probably set an alarm, I don't
mind. If it's 6:00 AM, maybe but
yeah, so same time tomorrow for
our second meeting.
Cancel. Just want
to chair tomorrow.
Discuss
tomorrow.
Sorry, I guess
we'll. Yeah we can. How long
have we been recording for?
2728 minutes OK
sorry. Oh
So I got a little bit longer to
just come out. One or two more
things. And yeah, yeah, through
the rest of the spec sheet in
the second meeting tomorrow.
Yeah, yeah. So I think we could
talk about ideal jobs 'cause
that kind of needs to be
discussed bouncing off each
other. Compare and contrast the
ideal job speech person in the
group. This may have changed
feedback from assignment one we
don't have feedback.
What common elements are there,
if any, so?
I'll start with
my. Good job.
So I cherish.
Search
I see support officer in South
Melbourne and remote working
required initially due to cover
19 so I kind of wanted a job
that would be remote most of the
time but there weren't a lot of
jobs going like that. I like the
sound up. Um, but I think
I'd also like to work.
Advice at times as well. So this
is with saying Australia S A&E,
which is a national mental
Health Organization working to
make a real difference in the
lives of people affected with
complex mental health issues
through support research and
advocacy. So I would be the
right person for the staff who
work insane Australia. That's
basically the job, yeah?
And.
Appeals to me because I have an
interest in mental health and
community service. I've had an
community services before I
studied it for awhile. It taken
down that it wasn't the kind of
work I ultimately wanted to do.
However, I wouldn't much like to
work behind the scenes and
provide Technical Support for a
great organization that provides
mental health services. Um?
There's a lot of skills and
experience that's required for
the job that I don't have.
Just get and I really don't
understand too much about. So I
when the same on page 4. And
yes, I meant like.
What changes may be made like
other than learning the
skills I don't know. I think
that's what we're supposed to
discuss. Did anyone get a
different impression?
Thank you. No.
Sorry. I mean, like
you sort of chose that that
position, 'cause it was a bit
broad as well.
Yeah, so that's that's similar
to what I went through like.
You're like a. Systems
integration officer, which sort
of works for like software and
hardware and everything. So I
just picked the one of the
broadest sort of jobs I could
find, 'cause I'm not really.
Sure, what path would wanna take
yet? It is like is like
an integration officer for
disability. People with like
impairments like vision and
deafness. And with like hardware
or software to help people
integrate with different
technologies. The sound of that.
I wouldn't say that one.
That's cool, so does does a bit
of everything, like with like a
lot of web development kind of
stuff as well.
So if I wanted to go to that Ave
or if I wanted to work with
actual hardware systems, it also
pretty much does everything that
job so. So I think the goal
of this part of the assignment
is to just summarize or.
Summarize that that is the jobs
with picked desire. Our ideal
jobs are indeed.
They compared the jobs.
Each person in the group.
I'm a bit can I? I'm not 100%
sure like how was supposed to
collaborate with this part.
Elements are there, if any.
That's one of the first
questions. Yeah, sorry. Common
element you've identified is
it's broad and both yours and
mine are bored. So what about?
What job did you get? I chose a
back end developer.
Basically, we write the back end
software. So how to explain it?
Probably easy take Facebook. Are
they got a front end team that
does all the UI and the design?
But then they'll have a back end
team that makes all the magic
happen. Basically, code that you
don't see, so like.
Content distribution the fact
that your videos get resized
and compressed all happens
with back end software, not in
the interface that's.
My sleep watch. How is that?
Because I don't really like
doing the graphical creative
side of things. My skill sets
more suited towards that at the
moment, so. So perhaps this
difference that would be that
yours is quite nitty gritty and
detailed, and ours is probably
the ones that Sam and I have
chosen. Probably more broad. I
think that's the question was
supposed to be answering.
Yep. Stardust, like this,
based on the little knowledge, I
have an. Your website, it seems
like that matches up with your
skills. Daniel, where are you?
Yeah I did I did not put very
much thought into this, but I
just found a systems
administrator add which I think
is pretty broad, like Salmon
Madeleine. It's yeah.
Just like overseeing and
computer network for like a City
Council, I thought that would
be. After a lot of different
bases in. Be kind
of interesting. But do you know
what some of the specifics of
it? Specific
say. Not.
Sense of technical skills and
experience in Windows Server.
Active Directory Exchange. SQL
Server, VM Ware virtualization
and San Technologies. I don't
know what most of that means so.
Does anyone know what that
means? Mostly adding, adding,
and maintaining users in Active
Directory, adding new machines
so they domain are there the
audio visual parts? Probably a
conferencing system that they're
using. But you've gotta look
after. Yeah, so you get given
pretty much a big stack of
paperwork when your movie.
Alright, So what was the name of
the the title of the job systems
administrator? I think I think
that's one you definitely need,
like a few years experience as
well, like a network
administrator is at 1.1 sort of
more junior job. Do you have a
junior network administrator?
Or systems administrator
and then a senior.
Sweet and makes it easy.
How is the place where they had
Chinese in Naturals? Yeah, so
yeah, that would be definitely a
good way to do it.
Not just learn from the pros,
not too much pressure.
So I'm not sure that I know too
much about that one, so I can't
really draw similarities or
differences. There
can anyone else?
I choose the.
IT support specialist pretty
much, I think, the same as you
marry. You know, like
a kind of like abroad.
Broad. Korea 'cause I
don't know much about the job
either. But yeah, my plan is
just to basically.
Help businesses you know? Just
provide the IT support an
reportes in maintaining the
networks. Oh cool.
Stop. Yeah so.
Submitted crossover. Even with
Daniels job there as well.
Yeah, every choice, yeah so
yeah. So I guess what I think it
might change. I think it might
change in the in the future as
we know more, but for now I
think it's just that.
So I guess Adam is already got a
bit bit more of an idea of what
his one training and we're not
really sure, so we pick
something general just to just
to start off with I guess.
Controls
Then Weird with the question. I
ask 'cause you have to actually
for an advert for a job all can
actually falling advert for a
job that I actually wanted. So I
just put one that I've found so
I wanted to do something for one
I chose was cyber security
analyst. However I just wanted
something within the field of
cybersecurity. Now there's so
many different specific.
Certifications in different
ways. You can do cyber security.
The one I'm looking at is
actually like the integral
hacker role where I can actually
breach the defenses so they can
implement devices to protect
their systems better.
Cool sounds definitely like the
most glamorous know then.
Out of all of ours.
Put on the wire.
Best drain it's movie like the
Hugh Jackman Swordfish we got
the cubes coming together.
So what's the French? It's each
position position from the
others. If anything, I think we
summarize that how similar or
different leukorrhea plans
across the group. I think we
covered that too.
Um? Be tackled
numerous ways in writing
and in visual elements of
concise coverage analysis,
slash, completing covering
all would be good.
Concise, so short and to the
point, which is good because I
think we can do that just fine.
Um strongly recommended table
presentation of comparison data
as it is a very easy to
highlight as it is very easy to
highlight a lot of information,
simple for others reading.
Interpret too so.
I'm thinking maybe we could eat
right out like.
What job title is?
Like the main roles and then
put, put it in a table each.
Sorry, put the hour jobs in one
block of the table edge and then
list the differences underneath
and contribute it like that.
Could be very quick.
Maybe? Right?
So. I'm
having trouble explaining what I
mean, but yeah.
And then we just find a little
aspect of somebody else. Is
that similar and say this is
my ideal job blah blah, and
Maddie's is also similar in
this way and then that kind of
might be it? And then will
just fill those individual
ones together and and also do
a pretty table as well,
putting it in a table is
probably the tricky part I
think by trying to make it
look yeah efficient.
Anyone got experience with
putting that on the website?
Making a table on website? My
website? I made a really tiny
table. Just to try it out, but
it's not not anything pretty
like not for something as
comprehensive as this, but it
depends how pretty you want it.
And how much time we wanna spend
on it? It's a concise, so we
could keep that part simple.
Life like this like this
elsewhere. As long as we're
meeting that criteria.
So we've reached the 40 minute
mark. Do we wanna pick a chair
for tomorrow and?
Leave it here for today. That
sounds like a plan.
Anyone want to volunteer?
I have one question that we
should probably look at
tomorrow. We gotta organize the
custom questions that we wanna
ask Steven. Are you OK 'cause he
just wants to just like?
So we just like each of us just
come with one different, like
what would one question it just
like added up to like the other.
By your questions and yeah.
Questions beforehand there so so
we want to prove messages on
teams. Do we want to come up
with a question each contribute
to list and will have that
sorted by tomorrow.
Yeah, we can do that. Yeah
tonight or something, yeah?
How does that sound item with?
Yeah, that should be great. He
just wanted a heads up so 'cause
he doesn't want to be like
caught off guard on a question
and be like I don't know how to
answer it. So just for the
record, what's what was his name
again? Steven, and he's a senior
software developer at Microsoft.
I think he's working in the Xbox
teams at the moment.
Cool man, so you've already
spoken to him.
Yep, it is just waiting for when
we're ready to.
Give him the questions and
then give him a couple of days
notice and then we can do the
interview. Lovely, he's happy
for it to be video recorded,
so if we want to put the video
recording on the website we
possibly could.
Just apply that to the shooter.
Yeah, sweet. Phone and as many
of us who want to attend can
will probably limit how many
people ask questions though.
Yeah, each person ask a couple
of questions each.
Say I I think I read that
we all need to be present,
but we don't all need to be
asking questions is what I
think that's what I read.
Because it's digital, like if it
was a interview in person. They
said like one or two people, but
digital and needs to be all of
us. The time zone difference
might be tricky for us all to be
there being there. He's in the
US. Put that on record, then if
we if we can't organize it to
have us all there. Otherwise
we're going to do some Cardboard
cut out of each person. Just
having in front of their webcam.
Remember what did they move?
What did he say, George?
Uh, what day is this? When
are you planning to do the
interview?
Who will have to discuss it
tomorrow? 'cause we're going to
be there. Well, we can discuss
it through chat, 'cause I think
we're supposed to keep our
meetings through 40 minutes
long. Yeah, so any other
quick questions before we go
or. Do you wanna continue on
chat if we have any more
questions? Yeah, I guess we
continue on chat. My batteries
are dead on my laptop so.
Finish quickly, I've added
little questions, document to
IT, work tab for the questions
for him so.
Of all these birds with these
questions on there, yeah yeah,
how about just add extra
question on today?
For all that Word document
itself. Alright, I'll stop
the recording here then.