Yeah, cool.
So whatever is everybody, using
on issuing the Atom.
No.
I don't know whatever I'm using.
But it's not Adam.
So.
Plus plus notepad++, yeah, I
might have that.
Yeah.
I figure so I think the
course they recommended using
the Atom editor anyway.
How? I think Tim dude, so I'm
just I'm gonna do the tutorial
with that. It's pretty. It's
going to be pretty much the same
as notepad++ it since this is
going to open up a different
program to edit it.
I thought just download that.
Now I'm gonna download Adam
right now 'cause otherwise I'm
not going to get it. Yeah, so
it's just Adam dot IO.
So, like holier.
What do you know again?
There's a fine game where you
control the whole of life.
And it chewed up buildings.
Go on.
How?
Yeah, I'm downloading now.
Daniel, see this marvelous
lighting screen.
Everyone can see my screen OK.
Ah, it looks very
pixelated for me.
Open.
Yeah is it flipped
around why? Yeah.
I was trying to figure out
what that was.
Sorry, uh, translator.
Well, it's backwards. On one of
my screens, but then teams is
telling me it's the right way.
So is that better? Yeah, that's
it. Yeah, get out. Yeah that's
it, yeah. I'll just wait is
download Adam. I'll just be
one second.
It's pretty clear to.
I do recommend the game Collier.
So I just arguing with the kids
about cleaning the land room.
Search pixelated or did you want
me to change the mode?
Adams window, it'll come up
bigger if you haven't done that
already. Yeah, looks like
really nice and clear on
mine. Yeah mine OK.
I might be my connection then,
yeah. Because I can't
really see much.
Probably double click on my
picture. That help.
Ah yeah, that's better.
Just got worse, just got worse.
And it's better now.
Yes, it's it's fluctuated it's
fluctuated. App.
OK, in the recording,
Yeah Alright so.
I've got like 2 two mice
going at the moment.
Do I need to open a record?
What was that?
Click to open report
on my following along.
Uh, no. I'm just checking
where everything is.
Taking the 'cause you did both.
Night invite.
Alright, so I'm assuming you've
all got GitHub Desktop.
Yeah, maybe. Yeah, how
do I tell?
Yeah. Yeah you should. You
go to start.
Yeah.
If I lose 300 G.
Do I need to open it GitHub Inc
and they should be GitHub
desktop installed as well,
'cause there's two ways I'm
going to show you how to do
this. So what was helping? Do I
need to look that up too?
My start bar was covering
your direction.
Let's start and then under
the letter. G you should see
GitHub Inc. And then they are
under that should be adamant
in GitHub Desktop.
Huh.
What is target up?
Keep.
James
uh never look at my
computer in this way.
No.
So what's the difference between
using notepad++ an Atom?
Adams gotta like a sidebar fee
for the Git Management so you
can just click the files and
open them from there where
notepad++ you would open.
GitHub desktop like this and you
need to click open in notepad++
or show in Explorer.
Which will then yeah.
Show you the files there.
And my Rockstar again so far.
I have get home, you've got it.
Alright so first we were going
to do the Adam way so we're just
going to click. Where do I click
version control with Git and
GitHub so you just click on
that, so opens here. Then you
go? Open the git panel.
My phone yes.
But how did you open that? You
you did things before you OK?
This screen here.
Get.
Text editor for the
21st century window.
Ah, yes, I finally do Yep.
And now it says get to know
Adam. So then you'll see version
control with Git and GitHub.
Have a quick there.
Then we could open get panel.
Yep.
Within Gonna Just go
across to GitHub.
Appear.
Trip.
I need a screen.
What was that?
Sorry, I thought you clicked
something, I'm confused.
What are you clicking next?
Published.
So see how on my window,
I've got this.
Oh, I had I had a recorded
message over that. No, I cannot
see that. Actually, it's rocked.
Yeah yeah, yeah.
Yep, and then we will go coin an
existing GitHub repository.
Now they changed it.
So we need the git repo 'cause,
it's not letting it's not.
Smoke.
I don't know why use this
one, so just bear with me.
Come now.
That's what is calling.
Directory.
I'm pretty sure this
is meant to sign in.
Daniel, do is add a middle. Yeah
I used items for my first
project. Does it isn't an
ornament automatically meant to
let you sign into GitHub.
When?
Yeah, when I opened at him
just before I was still set
up for my old one.
I can't I can? I can barely even
remember how actually set it up.
Right right now, I've got, I'm
using GitHub Desktop.
And I've got a clone of the.
The Master Branch, and that's
what I've been using to upload
files to GitHub. I think I'm
just going to scratch the Adam
bit. I'll get back to the
batches on that one, apologies.
So we're just gonna go
GitHub Desktop.
The easiest way without using
that other thing.
Let me know when you get
it open.
And if you signed indicated
desktop, yeah, yeah, I got it
open now have you signed into
yours yet? Maddie. Ah.
So it's probably gonna give you
a login screen.
Yeah, I think it looks like it.
So you should be able to click
here current repository.
Oh, mine says current repository
says Daniel's coffee GitHub. Is
that the one that we're working
on is CEO S?
Yes yes yes.
Do you have that on
yours? Yeah, it says.
I. No, I don't know what
you're talking about.
So are you able to share
your screen with me.
2nd.
I say if you click
on metal and pre.
And then click close ad.
Clone.
And we're going to click Daniel.
I'm gonna get coin?
It's gonna pull down
the Master Branch.
She I don't know if I keep that
in mind is already there.
Did you do it on the website
perhaps? Follow the git repo.
I probably bought Daniel right
now. Sorry, but probably
boring you right now. This is
good. I need a refresher.
Anyway, I never I don't really
know what I did to make it
work. I just sort of winged
it. So now if you click the
Daniels repo there there a 2.
Alright and then we can go we
can get open and Adam or we
can go show in Explorer. We're
going to show in Explorer.
Can we click on that now? You
know what games I play?
Oh wait, I see that window.
We only see you get ready
for the right. Give me a
second, I will do it.
I have a.
Mine is like came out with
like a pity. A text file says
get so say attributes. Yeah,
just one moment I'll swap to
the master branch online.
And I'll be able to show you.
Show in Explorer. It should look
like this. Yeah, industry data,
IT technologies, IT work meeting
teams profiles web support files
and Readme MD.
Is everybody say that on this
great? Yes Yep now for example,
if you've got a document that
you just want to.
Add to the repo. Now like I said
like here, I've got the
Mongoose. I'm just going to copy
these to the source is just the
source for The Monkees far and
drop drop that like I was adding
a file to a USB.
Straight into the folder.
Then I'll go back to GitHub
Desktop and it's Gonna tell me
here that I've got two changed
files. One Mongoose which is
adding 'cause there's a plus
and sources and then, uh, right
here I've gotta for every time
you commit something back to
the any of the branches you've
gotta give it a summary and
less. It's just an individual
file change. So in this one I'm
just going to say long
Mongoose.
Image and give it a descripcion.
You don't have. The
descriptions are optional.
So are you adding
this image too?
So you could draw on that later
and add it to the website.
Ah yeah, anybody can grab it.
'cause once I commit this, but
it will commit it. I'm going to
push to origin, which means push
it back to the GitHub Server.
So sending it out to the cloud
if you want to call it that.
Now if you guys open up this
window again. And select.
And just click on fetch origin.
What up
hello right here?
Yeah, click on that.
Yep, that's The One.
Alright.
K.
Yes.
Or are they?
OK, now show in Explorer.
And then if you go to the
web support file web support
files folder. You'll see in
there that there is now 1
goose and the sources text.
Then I moved over just before.
OK.
So how how do we add to
the website?
Now to add to the website,
that's just one branch, so this
is where all your support
documents like your your word
documents and everything go. As
you make changes, even even if
they're not finished, they
should go in the Master Branch.
OK, and then just every time you
edit him, edit him out of.
The location in Shell Explorer.
OK. Yeah.
That way, that way you get these
commit history to say that
you've been committing to the
repo. So like I can see here
that Daniel. Updated industry
data in the Doc. Sam uploaded
it. Re uploaded these
blockchain. I uploaded some
JavaScript files Shannon created
some new file folders and added
some questions and I could see
the changes that we made.
So there's a history of that.
If you click on history
tab here.
Yeah, yeah. So for example, Adam
if I wanna update if I want to
upload my my industry data. You
know like my whatever I have in
Microsoft Exchange Yep.
I do this and I have load my.
I got my Word document into
GitHub. Yeah, like.
Search the branch or the the.
How how do you What Car?
How did you add?
How you added all of that?
Added to the replay.
Current repository.
Cyclic.
Car repository.
Well, we've already done that.
Heavenly, we've done that. Now
if we want to change just to
the website, see over here
where it says current branch.
Yeah yeah, if you click on
that it's gonna bring it this
dropdown menu and then you'll
see under there the website
branch. It may not be under
recent branches, but it'll be
website.
Faster, yeah?
And then click website.
Yeah, and it's Gonna reload.
I'll click fetch from origin.
And let me know when
that's done.
Hey could only be working or
just do a a little side
note. You can only be in one
branch at a time.
Understand the branches.
So branches you'll have your
master branch, which is your
main app that you normally
developing.
And then you would have
branches with different
features, which are all gonna
get merged into the master
later.
And then you build one
source tray again.
So it's it's. It's basically
branches or aid when you've got
like 3040 developers working on
one application that you're not
tripping over each other.
Yeah, I get that.
Just start say how I'm
supposed to know where the
branches are what they do
or who put them there or I
don't see it like when
they're talking about
branches. I'm like OK, so
I'll see a tree at some
point but no no.
They kind of refer it to a
branch is only because you know
if you were to put it down on
paper, how the system worked. It
would look like branch tree
branch. Yeah, so how?
So when I when I was making
my website, I opened up
GitHub in the browser.
And I typed in one big page of
Code Yep and then I committed it
alright so other than that I
have no idea what's going on?
That's all I did, so when when I
want to put text somewhere on
the website, how do I so I've
got some text I wanna add to
website can I? So you've got the
website branch now slot selected
like mine in your GitHub Desktop
app. Ah hold on I'll mirror what
I'm doing so I won't be.
I see your window, so if you
could just point to point things
on my window. I'm I know I think
I can point on.
Hello.
Point with your words, I mean?
Alright, so you've got website.
Can you click fetched origin?
And this is pulling down
the entire website off
the Reaper. OK, so now if
you go show in Explorer.
And then I just need to see
that window, but you should
see a whole heap of files in
there. Yes, sorry.
I got it.
Yep, so that's all the code
for the for the website now
do you have an idea on? What
kind of section you wanted to
edit say? Let's say your
autonomous vehicles?
That is an example.
So if you go to daughter in
this case because it can
change depending on how you
design your your web page now.
If we go to IT technologies.
Alright, so in there will
see the first one
autonomous vehicles.
I probably didn't want to
double click. You probably
want to right click and then
select edit.
I'll, I'll how do you want to?
OK for Google and then
I'll exit that.
So we'll go right, click
open edit with notepad++
that would be perfect.
At next, see autonomous vehicles
tab in industry data. That's
that whole bit of code where you
can just put that information.
Can you see what I'm what? I can
only see you. I take, yeah, OK.
Is it a space the team
version of desktop sharing
is not that good?
Just select no for now, you
don't want to update it so.
I've got some JavaScript,
which is going to fetch this
and then merge it into the
rest of the site as you're
loading it so but this section
is all yours to work in for
the autonomous vehicles.
There is a very trick to the
formatting of this HTML.
I can come along later and tidy
it up so you can just put it out
in however you want at this
stage. So can can I just put it
in as at all. I need to do is
separate my paragraphs otherwise
paste text? Yeah.
'cause I've already got is that
how you doing, or what? How do
you do it? Uh, well I'm assuming
is written it in Word, so HTML
formatted at all.
To copy and paste and then add
the HTML around it.
Yeah, so do I so if it if it's
just paragraphs do? I need to
just put paragraph splits. And
that's it. Yeah, if you wanna.
Just do paragraph splits. If
you go back to that. Explorer
window if you just want to
open up the cybersecurity. One
you can see how I wrote wrote
up Shannons for.
So we'll just we can just go to
the other. To the other to
the other ones and just
look how it is structured.
Left clicking by looking.
I think it's clicking off the
icon before you get to.
Yeah.
There we go.
Yeah, yeah that structure right?
Yeah, so I've got classes here,
were like PT-2. Well that's the
Petes short for padding top and
I'm telling you put 2 units of
padding. PB-3 is saying it
padding bottom with three units,
but it doesn't really matter
because I can come along and
just tidy it up later.
Um H5 I'm using as a general
heading H Forza Page Title H 6
is like a subtitle.
OK.
Yeah, I'm
so really difficult.
Pretty much so far I've just
been taking everybody's word
documents and then doing this
for years and then you can go
along and just edit any section
that you want afterwards.
Oh 610. Sorry and then if we
screw up at some point.
We won't be like,
uh, what can I say?
Damage in the whole website no
no OK 'cause that was one of my
concerns like I don't wanna go
in touch any of that because I
don't wanna you know like delete
something and then so you can
edit the individual files are
due back, it up every every two
days or every day, I've got
rolling copies of the work that
I've been submitting to it, so
as not a big problem. If someone
was to accidentally delete it.
'cause I could just re upload
it. It would probably would lose
minimal. But if you're only
editing like your individual
sections. Like in this case, IIT
autonomous vehicles dot HTML and
you accidentally delete that?
Well then it's not a major thing
because we still got the
original Word document.
To bring back that far.
Sorry. I I can you tell me
again what PT true is?
What 2 units?
Sorry, I need to go now. Yeah
that's alright. OK bye but
anyways thank you.
So PT-2 is just a style class
that I added to want to make.
From aligning everything
easier for me.
You don't have to put that you
could just put paragraphs and
then if you'd like I can come
along and do it if you don't
think you're gonna be able to.
Do that is.
That what you want.
I I want.
I want to do it myself, but
I'm thinking that might take
too long. I'll give you a
rundown of basically the
easiest way. I use PT-2.
For paragraphs that belong to
the same heading. So if you say
H5 there at the top, what does
it do? That
I didn't say they are all well
old pay 2. Up until the last one
which becomes P PT-2 an padding
bottom 3. Yeah, Yep, that means
that I'm going to Ave heading
after that. So as you can see
I've got data loss prevention.
And then say the next client
that that's the only one of that
paragraph. There's no paragraphs
to follow that heading, so it's
only got padding on the bottom
by three units, and I've done
that all the way through.
If you if you don't get it
right, it's not a big deal
'cause we can always fix it up
later, and I can always guide
you through what you needed to
change. Yeah, I still really
don't comprehend. Yes yeah, so
it's more complicated HTML and
CSS that we didn't really. They
didn't really want to teach in
this unit. Yeah yeah, OK. So if
you want you can just put basic
HTML like you did for your
normal page. And then I can
just go through and add that
if I think it's needed anyway.
OK, so I'll just do my open,
do the open paragraph bit
and the close paragraph bit.
Yeah and then.
Some ultra some headings, but
I'll probably get that wrong and
it do do do.
So it will be easier for you to
read if I have it all in one
straight line like this.
Ah. Yes or no. I just indent
that way to make it easier
for other people to read so
it doesn't really doesn't
really phase me. It just
makes it look tidy overall.
Yeah.
I'm OK.
I just finished comprehend
did more so I was able to
contribute more because.
Like I can I can write **** on a
Word document and go on forever,
yeah, and answer all the
questions in double triple
detail but currently I don't
comprehend this just yet.
Get it with.
Yeah, did you teach yourself
this? This yeah, I
was self taught.
I remember writing writing
crappy web pages when I was a
lot younger, with like a
little icons that used to
follow your mouse around the
screen or like a big chain of
my little bouncy balls. It
would waive around with it,
and that's awesome, yeah?
Well, I think.
I just just wanna get rid of
this and go back to how to
upload mine one more time.
Want to?
If I want to add to add
to this one.
How do I do that?
How to re edit?
Yep.
I. Then then I talked in
that the pop up window,
they can't say yeah.
So they make it change, right?
So just just make any change
on it. So say Maddie was
here or whatever you like in
that document.
That you've opened.
You can't see what I'm
doing. Can you know?
Change this line like that.
This one. That wasn't it?
So we got.
Notepad game the corner. Yeah we
gotta not gone.
Sorry I I'm trying to find where
I put it.
I can't see my own.
I see.
Yep, that's it.
And then we're gonna just hit
save the little floppy disk that
one, Yep, now if we swap back to
the GitHub desktop window.
Now that you've saved that every
time you make a change and you
done for whatever time frame
that you were going to work on
it, you save it. Then you go
back to the GitHub Desktop app.
This one, I see. Now it's saying
that it's picked up or change
and it's a It's got the red. The
line, it's taking away and then
the green is the line. It's
putting in which was Maddie was
here. So because it's only one
file you've edited, you don't
have to put in a summary at the
top, so we can just say we could
add a description, or we can
just click commit. To
website Yep.
So we've committed that now and
then. The next step we gotta do
is we gotta go push to origin.
So This Is everybody else can
pick up the change.
OK, so when when I'm committing
it, why isn't that that like
what is the commit do that's
different to the push? Alright
So so, for example, you were
going to edit like 10 different
files in one hit. You can do
individual descriptions and
summaries for each file or each
group of files for the task that
you were doing.
Right and then you can then you
don't have to push him to the
the repo until you're ready. So
you can say. I've done 10
commits. These are all the notes
and the commits of what I did,
and then why now that I've done
put all those notes in and I'm
done for the night. Now I'm
going to push it back to the
repro for somebody else to grab
OK that does help me a lot
because I was like? Why are you
committing once and then pushing
like you're committing twice?
Yeah, OK OK cool. I think I've?
So now if I was to go to GitHub.
We can go to should be able to
go to Daniels the website. Now
it should actually be live.
Love it.
I'm gonna go to IT technologies.
I'm gonna get autonomous
vehicles and look.
This is data blah blah blah.
Matty was here. OK cool it's
already on the site.
Thank you for that. I that's
plenty for me. For now I think.
If you get stuck general near
a computer most of the day an
can normally respond.
It seems that says I'm online
and I haven't responded. It's
because I can't really respond,
but I will as soon as I can.
Alright, you're not obliged to
respond immediately. I certainly
don't. Yeah, I I tried to but
then there's this times when
you like you got a customer
there and you're just like I
can't really just open this
up right now.
Oh, thank you so much for that,
that's that's great. Yeah, I
hope that was helpful, but.
Kid.
I I didn't say her in
the cameras.
She started it.
They keep sneaking in here
and stealing all my
permanent markers.
Yeah, that's dangerous, yeah,
and then I find like a warm or
something colored in.
Magic eraser becomes like your
best friend. Does it work for
the permanent? Yeah
surprisingly. But there's
only so many times you can
use it on a wall before the
paint comes off.
Say yeah.
Do you have questions?
I'm pretty good, I've just been
doing what you guys been
talking about on the on my
industry data section. Now I'm
just I'm just doing the changes
in GitHub and sort of copying
some of the formatting of
Shannons industry data section.
Just wanna say hi there we go.
Set alarm
like where the reason why dad
has to leave the camera. So
many times because once dads
on the camera. There's nobody
watching them.
So we I get after all
kinds of dodgy stuff.
Alright, I'll end
the recording here.
These are very mischievous.