So do we know who's chairing?
Yummy.
Last one.
Welcome everybody to the
last meeting.
Congratulations, we made it
made it. Yeah thanks Adam.
Well, should we do just like a
quick recap of.
Morning's meeting?
Or should we just?
Just for the people that
work that missed it.
Not to mention their names.
Yes.
Do another. Yep.
Sorry.
I'm sorry, I sometimes I can't
hear guys like did you. Did you
want to recap it for everybody?
Yeah yeah yeah. Yeah, so um.
This morning we talk
about like the.
Contribution form if everybody
has signed that.
So Is everybody happy
with the percentage that
16 is at 16 1/2 or 16.6?
It just works out
as an even split.
2 Oh yeah, yeah everybody. Happy
with that will just sign that
one or just check who's Missy on
it. Me.
Of course it was many.
Where do I find that
meetings files
contributions form dot dot
X?
And then I never I was gonna put
a folder in there to say actions
and agendas like I did on
GitHub, but I was like there
someone else can do it.
And the group reflection George
and the group? Yeah yeah. So we
need to. Team the team
one the group
reflection. One that
with the team.
Oh yeah, I've got. It
contributes to that. I
haven't done that yet.
When so everybody just gonna
write something or we gonna like
get all together in elaborate.
In the first meeting we did.
Just need to do it again for
this, then somebody can just
squish them together.
I had done that look like
the web page done.
Cool.
And then the last one will be
like if there's any like
changes to the repo that will
be doing. Anybody will be
doing any changes. Everybody
is going to keep. Make sure
what's on the Ms teams file is
matches what's on GitHub.
Except for the different
spellings or grammar that
changes that we make in the
next day.
Yeah, that's like
they can be well.
The individual documents can
have the spelling mistakes
as long as the site in the
report doesn't.
And all of this one has to be
done before Sunday, right?
Because that's the when we
when we plan to submit,
ideally before lunchtime.
'cause we want to submit around
lunchtime. To both the PDF and.
The Ms teams document and then
we can all do our contribution
form submission after that.
So I I'm actually working
tomorrow morning. Yeah, so can
we push it back?
Three hours.
Or there, is there a reason
web submiting at midday? I
was just easier for me to do
it on midday.
Yeah I can.
Do a 10.
10:00 PM.
Yeah.
And then at 10:00 PM, Daniel
needs to lock the GitHub repo to
read only. OK OK OK yeah, no
worries so that Yeah 'cause If
we make changes to it afterwards
submitted we lose marks.
Yeah, OK, so once we've done
this admission and we don't
really want changes once matys
copied everything from the
website and the documents to the
report, because then they
probably get missed or not make
it in. Yeah yeah, so that one.
And plus once of Repose locked
then we won't lose marks if
anyone changes something later
and it stops anybody
accidentally deleting them, the
revo. As well, when it's
read only.
Then at 10:00 o'clock every
Monday or whenever they get
a chance like the following
day after we've submitted,
you've all got to go to
GitHub to Daniel's repo and
click the fork button.
OK, yeah, that's part of the
criteria for the assignment.
We've all got to have a copy
of it.
GitHub profiles yeah, yeah.
Yeah, I'll I'll have my my group
reflection. Finish by
tonight, so that should be
ready before 10 probably.
Come on, don't don't fork it
before we've all submitted our
stuff because you won't get the
changes. So if you **** it now
and we do some updates tonight
or tomorrow, they won't be in
your copy of the repo, just
just pointing that out.
OK, cool Ann.
I'll remember my question in
a second. Sorry yeah. Well
yeah that's all everything
that I have to do. Agenda.
Yeah I don't know what else
we another subject.
You could ask the group
reflection questions.
Maddie.
Yeah, 'cause we've got our
response I got yeah Daniels
response. Forgot Georges
response. Don't know we don't
have Daniels response 'cause you
went there in the in the morning
so we need medis and Daniels
responses to those questions.
That's the one that comes
together is a 400 word piece,
isn't it? Yeah, but everyone
wrote like kinda 600 words or
so for their individual words
so we can grow it.
Pretty short as well.
I don't see how the how it
could possibly answer those
questions. One sentence each
and then it amounts to 400.
Anything we can do is maybe
trying to find like common
themes.
If I said similar things, just
say a popular point.
Wow, I don't know.
We'll just do it. Do it. We've
done in. He can just read it.
So you want me to read it then?
Yeah.
So just some quick
product placement.
My Christmas
not fun.
We get paid a dollar every
time we do that.
That's mine.
Or ask questions.
Yeah, yeah so.
What went well? What you think?
What went well in the team?
Think just getting.
Starting early.
Starting Eli was pretty.
Pretty Ki think we would have
been screwed if we haven't
started early. Yeah.
Nice and early and we started on
time. Not really. Yeah, we don't
want to. We don't want him to
think we started before the day
that we were supposed.
We had a group organized a bit
early, but we didn't actually
start early. They told us to
start organizing groups.
Pretty much the first week.
Yeah, that we should look at
doing it and which we did.
So we formed groups on time
which was just before everyone
else. Yeah, except but I
think Brad already had his
done by the time we all
joined up about it, but he's
done before the week started.
Yeah, and I think the
regular meetings were good.
I mean when we first
started, we didn't really
think that they were all
necessary, but I think we've
done well with them. I think
we've used them quite well.
Yeah, so maybe there's
something in that.
Then what could what
could be improved?
Nothing is perfect.
You can improve on awesome.
Teams
listen miss teams.
Sort out like file storage
system, sort of between GitHub
and Ms teams so we don't have to
double up. Or I don't know.
OK, there wasn't. There is a
plugin that you can use that
will sync Ms teams to get.
Aubrey fly fly.
It's involved to set it up
because you need to. You need
somebody. You need the person
that owned the repo to set it
up, and then they've also got
to be the ones that created
the Ms teams group.
Yeah, I think I think we did
well with Ms teams as best we
could. And like Shannon Adam
did well with creating the
different channels, channels
and files and then uploading.
The different groups in it? Yeah
Yeah, but then you uploaded all
of this stuff as well. You know
anything that was on the repo
you put on teams and that was
really handy. I don't think.
I don't think we could have
improved their like that was
really good. It's just Ms
teams was a bit.
It was getting painful when
the image is still like copy,
paste, copy, paste, copy,
paste, copy, paste, drop and
drag all over the place.
Someone's editing that one.
I've gotta wait, then forget
about it. 3 days I don't want
Oh yeah, that's gonna go there.
The use of Ms teams
is just it's painful.
We used it well considering.
Yeah, I think it's like canvas.
The more you get, the more
you use it. The more you
get used to it. Like yeah.
Yeah.
Just because you used to
return, you know you use a
turd. Doesn't mean you
should get used to a turd.
I'm putting that nicely. I
would have used another 4
letter word that Tim would
like to sing in the
transcript.
In at least one thing
that was surprising.
No arguments, everything was
pretty chill between
everyone's good. I was
surprised it went so well.
I like, I always go into group
projects thinking, Oh, it's
going to get done at last
minute. Who's going to lag
behind where we gonna have to
pick up after we didn't really
have to do any of that.
Yeah, unless the whole bunch
are crumbs on the GitHub so
you guys can clean that up.
Yeah, it's good.
I went.
Yeah, and it on time, so
that's good.
On time with the right
amount of meetings.
Yeah, good insect
squishing those in.
Anne. At least one thing that
you have learned about groups.
So as hard as I thought it
was going to be.
Working with strangers was good.
Yeah.
I know I put on mine that you
know, it was like it was
surprising how well we got along
with each other like we already
knew each other for years.
Yeah, I think we've done
well there.
I've learned that it's not
always hard. It's not always
hard work to work in a group.
Yeah.
Sorry guys.
That's all at the beginning. I
was like, oh, this is gonna go.
And then, just like you know.
But it went really well. Just
like bang yeah, divvying up
the work went really well.
Yeah, I thought that was
going to be tricky.
Yep, good Dan.
Oh yeah, that's it.
Sweet.
Yeah, so we've just gotta all
we've got to do is right up the.
Group affection, reflection.
Upload that and then the PDF
and that's it.
Yeah, pretty much.
The PDFs are two Part 2 document
thing. Did you? Did you see that
in the assessment criteria?
First one.
Hold on, I've got a page here so
we need one with the assignment
in the report on the cover page
it had we have to change the
template so it's got a link to
the. Website. And the
GitHub repository.
And then the the full normal
report. Anyway, as you're doing,
and then the second document is
A is called the PDF Ms teams
info which needs all the Ms
teams artifacts such as agenda,
notes, recordings, minutes,
action notes and the Ms teams
invite link. Which is like a
one pack which which you can
just copy off the website
'cause I got all the document
links on there. Yeah yeah.
Like a 10 page thing? No, no.
It's just like you grab all the
agenda notes. And the action
report action. Action documents,
so you grab those.
Combine them and just like and
condense them into like a
couple of pages. I copy,
paste, copy, paste, put the
dates.
Yeah, well I.
Hey Jakes and then just put a
title on it. This was this
document. I don't know that
last one. If you if you want
sorry and you know what, I
realized that we didn't do.
Nobody wrote minutes.
Did we have to or was that
just the transcript? It says
here that he wanted minutes
and action.
Did we did the action?
Minutes and action nights,
though. Kind of the same thing.
Yeah, it's fine. That would be
great if we could do that.
George, yeah, yeah I'll do the.
PDF Microsoft Teams, yeah?
For all the links, it yeah I
can do that tonight.
All the links she walks with
the meetings go away and
then you click links and
then you just grab the three
team links off each meeting.
OK, and then the Ms teams invite
link is on the main page with
the little Ms teams icon I made.
Yeah, I guess I'm doing
that tonight.
I'll finish my group reflection
up to this and then I can start
working on that and then.
Maybe just upload them to teams
when you're done them.
So we can then Adams submitting
all of it.
So after then then you pull
it from there and then
submit it into canvas.
Ah, the PDF. Yeah, yeah,
I'll send me both of them
to canvas. Yeah, but you
pull it from from team.
Yeah.
And then we've got to like the
a couple of five days after we
submit the assignment, or five.
I think it's like the 25th or
something. You've gotta submit
the A2 contribution form. If
you don't do it, you won't get
a mark for the assignment. So
is that is that the one we just
talked about, or is that the
one we just? That's the one we
just don't sign? You've got a
separate assessment called. I
think it's just called like a
two or something.
Yeah, you gotta submit it to
their or you won't get graded.
If that does not have the app
involved or their little
program or something.
Spot plus.
Spike plus we've got like 2
weeks after the due date to
complete, but he hasn't finished
putting everybody in it yet.
Because not everyone was in
a group or kept changing
groups or something.
So we don't have links to it
yet, right? Yeah.
OK, so. That will talk about
that next week then.
Those two things we'll talk
about next week.
Which do you think?
State contribution form.
Contribution forms you should
really just submit on Monday so
you don't forget or even.
Little. Could probably submit
him now. I don't see why not
since we've got it filled out
and then tomorrow. I'm gonna
submit the other bit. I don't
think he's going to have a
problem with that, so do we each
do each submit the contribution
thing separately, or is it just
the one person everybody has to
submit the contribution form
individually? Only one person
submits the PDF assignment at
right? So yeah, so I'll submit
the PDF assignment report and
the Ms teams info PDF.
But that's for the project, but
you and I'll also submit myself
the contribution form, but every
team member has to submit the
contribution form. Clear Yep, so
if 'cause Yeah.
As one person forgets that
person won't get a grade
for the assignment at all.
Yeah.
Open that shooter thing is
that an Ms teams at the moment
the contribution form yeah? Or
is it on canvas? It's on teams
at the moment, yeah?
So that's all done so I can
download it right now. Submited?
Yeah, I'm to get out of order.
I'll make it a PDF 'cause he
wants it in a PDF so I'll save
it as a PDF and then I'll re
upload it and give you the.
Great front, you stand ready.
Oh, thank you what? What did I
Press? I don't know.
Squidbillies
Sorry, is that just? That's just
what I've just signed that we're
talking about. Yeah, right?
So since then.
It's uploading two teams now, so
you should see contributions
form dash completed PDF.
So we each we each submit
that one.
Do the assignment A2
contribution by the 25th of
October and you can do that now.
Try to download it.
Even though it says this
assignment doesn't count
towards your final grade.
But if you don't submit
it, you don't get it.
According to Mr. Tim.
It's good.
I have
everyone else good burger.
We're missing Sam Sam
Tonight. We could remind him
to submit that floor.
Comments.
Done.
Dude.
Maddie, can you put some
pictures of $100 bills at the
end of that report?
And then put it put some text
over it. You can't touch this.
Was there anything else we
needed to talk about?
I think that's it.
Everything is pretty much
ready to go.
Dress where everyones at.
My brain's no longer
working, sorry.
Times like 4 hours ago.
What contribution forms that's
already submitted? So I don't
know if that just borderlines
everybody in one person
submitted. It is
automatically submits it.
What anyone else? Yeah,
'cause I just went into my
assignments and just went to
submit it and it says it's
already submitted at 723.
Oh really, oh I I 23 so you got
I had my window open while Adam
you are submitting yours so I
had already opened the window so
maybe that's why might allow me
to submit it. I thought I
submitted mine too.
Just there just says resubmit.
Does it matter 'cause he
said we each had to submit
that individually, yeah.
'cause mine says if you click on
the details it says my name and
then submitted it, but I didn't
actually submit it. Hold on. I
see submission demos, download
contributions, form dash. Ah
hold on hold on. I submitted it
so that's in the list.
And many submission.
I'm guessing.
We got a submission details. It
has the name of who she met with
him, 'cause he said, Yeah.
He said that we all had to
submit that.
It's all right now.
Would be interesting to see when
you do submit the actual aid to
the rest of it, whether it all
comes up on all of ours as well,
whether they've already just
automatically grouped us. Yeah,
'cause we join that group. Maybe
it worked out that that's the
The Group 1. Maybe they tap
flagged it. But it says.
It says when you go to
assignments in a two
contribution, you go down the
bottom of those dot points. It
says if your group cannot agree
on the contribution factors,
fractions. You have to submit by
the deadline as a single PDF.
Consolidated contribution forms,
which insinuates that we could
each submit something different
and separately, yeah.
Otherwise, I should we all just
retry and resubmit where each of
us are asking for.
I think we should just contact
talk to Anthony.
Because.
It's like two or three of ours
have gone through, but not the
rest. I mean, you really
don't need 1, right?
You do that, so maybe action to
say once Adam submits the rest
of it tomorrow. If you click on
when we click on assessment to
to see if everyone else says
it's submitted, and then it says
resubmit. That way you know that
just linked or six of us and all
our submissions are mutual.
So when Shannon, when you open
the A2 contribution assignment
on the right hand side, does it
say? Submited exclamation point,
the data submission details and
then downloaded. Sorry download
contribution form completed.
It looks like you're connected.
Then when I click on submission
details, it comes up saying that
I submit it, but I didn't.
It must be all joined together,
yeah, just cool. How many days
do so we have to submit that
particular thing, Adam.
There's another way to 25th,
25th, so we can ask them before
the week is done.
Yeah.
We've got, we've got until next
Sunday to ask to clarify, so
that should be fine.
Yeah yeah Oh yeah.
Mine to show up like
that too. Yes it is.
I just realized my Mike was on
mute. Submitted, yeah?
Show anything you just
shown out, yeah.
It was a little strange
that you weren't talking.
Self and other stuff like
submission details details yeah.
Alright. So. Very good, well on
track or my son.
Does the project or
do you have a name?
Oh yeah, like an app name.
**** Sorry I I. I thought
about, you know, maybe we
should give it a name and it
was just like security to you.
Matthew, Facebook just call
it the social resolute
Revolution. Social Security.
What's on my site. Social
Security number.
I acted like oh people might
install it by accident. Pay a
dollar for in America.
American to be downloading it.
I was thinking why is like the
app could make money with her
like out out breaking like the
rules like 'cause we don't want
to keep any of the cast in any
of the users data. Otherwise
it's just as bad as user
Facebook. Yeah, so it's like.
We could sell ads, but will tell
him all. All we can tell you is
our target audience is people
that are concerned about their
online security. So you know we
could put like VPN ads in the
bottom or like automatic
scheduled. A security check will
you have to pay for the
privilege to have that feature?
So you gotta pay like a you know
$5. Boy, you know just the basic
version for dollar, I was
thinking about that because
there's not. There's not many ad
ads that will want to sell to
someone who. Good audience.
Everyone likes Doritos.
Are you on social media at
the moment? Did you think
about eating a bag of Doritos
while you run a security
check up on your social media
platforms? Because these
chips are just delicious.
I'm holistic to cheese. I
can't eat. Doritos are and you
can't have the normal pack.
You have to have the party
size pack because that's big
enough for a single city.
I recently just got over at
Doritos addiction.
I get these temporary addictions
that I'm like I can't stop.
Three dice was the most
recent one.
When you get to absolutely
monster bags on Audi. Yeah, I
haven't had him for a second.
This is those giant. The mega
bags that are like.
There's like two party
size bags.
It's Inside, is it still half
full of air probably?
Alright, so we'll finish
recording here then, Yep.
Come up with the name.
One last thing before the name
that's alright. I asked Adam, I
just wanted to see your guys
opinion on it. I don't want to
give him too much more work
before. Oh those changes. Yeah,
you should bring that out. Just
the changes on the website.
I don't know like all pink.
Like I'm just thinking because
there's a lot of text fields in
the rest of my broken up into
tabs with her, but break like
the IT work. The video can be
home tab, then have a tab beside
it for the transcript. It just
means when and then the same for
all technologies. Have a home
tab and then selections.
And project on the break that up
into individual things in tabs
as well, not just
it, just means like if Tim, for
example, is on the home page and
goes, I'll go look at the
project idea first. It doesn't
just do that big massive scroll.
It is just clicking up and
then if you do it really
quickly, it just gets stuck
in this and just goes to.
And eventually stops
and like Jack pot.
You're not like that idea,
especially with the
transcript. I reckon 'cause
That's probably quite long.
Now you can see the video
there, you click on the
transcript and then you'll have
the heading straight after the
video of YT technologies. If he
clicks back and the same of
technologies, you can click
back to home and then you just
gotta Scroll down a little bit.
Technologies.
Sir, is that much extra or
is that alright?
You've already got actually
technology and tips.
I mean just having around tab
home tab. What are we gonna put
on the home tab? That's all. I
don't know 'cause that's why I
deleted it 'cause I was like.
There's nothing to go on it.
I don't know, you can just put
the floor. If I shrink the
project down, they'll be less
scrolling. And then if I.
Stripped down mighty work I
think will save a bulk of that
stay there longer than like.
Yellow ones, the other one.
That's fine. Yeah, at least with
project, because I thought that
somebody might say this. I did
already break it up into
individual parts 'cause I'm like
I'm not editing this again and I
know somebody's gonna ask for it
to be exact.
But I didn't think about the the
IT work one when I was doing it,
I was thinking about it and I'm
just like maybe they won't know
I can get out of not doing it.
Sorry, I was laughing at what
Daniel said. Oh sorry, I didn't
hear what no comment he made.
Just replying to Adam from
like an hour ago. Oh he said
Oh yeah, looks looks something
along the lines. It looks
good. Maddie will catch all
the rest of the mistakes.
That way I won't try and do
any proofreading.
Woodbury
alright, so I'll stop breaking
that stuff up now even though I
was hoping it was done.
Me, I might have to update
my group reflection now to
say that you're all mean.
Romaine and I maybe do stuff
late at night.
Yeah, 'cause you're gonna
go to bed early.
I was I was just going to
play Red Dead Redemption.
I'll just play it while I'm
doing it, and then just slowly
slide by wine while I'm waiting
for the voting screens.
When it cuts to that
cinematic cinematic views of
thing, yeah, yeah, yeah. So
the name of the app.
Mongoose magic.
Face one Facebook.
What you said, what rhymes with
duck? No, no, no
face and then but.
Gotta keep it classy. Yeah, it's
certainly a project code name we
can. Put down that we will
do marketing research to
come up with a better name
in the future.
Now as well. What's up with the
name next song? We could
just click and sucks.
Should.
Facebook security.
When you're on public
transport and really need to
protect your face and butt.
Facebook safely.
I know it sounds like you gotta
put your face in a butt.
Safely.
I think they call that a
dust mask.
Oh wait, wait wait, here's
one we prepared earlier.
This can be the logo.
I'm here. What's a good time?
Secure social.
Secure if you wanna be
real boring.
That's a good description of
what it is, I guess.
Yeah. All your data belong to
us, but that might be simple.
I think that's racist.
'cause it was a video game
that they got translated and
they did it wrong.
I don't know what's this
username generator.
Pro James.
Lighting.
It can't have the word face.
Secure SM like a radio station
listen tune in to secure.
Kind of catch you.
Perhaps a little
misleading though.
I don't know how this one is
going to generate a name is
asking me like option one? It
gives you a list seller like
select Dinosaur, option 2 bugs
and then unusual animals.
I don't even know how to say
that that didn't work. Well,
sounds great, and romeris
beady tags.
Do you have favorite dinosaurs?
Ever done is love?
The T. Rex.
'cause it's the cow. Is
it gonna eat the goat?
I had a.
Louis and I had a manager, very
temporary manager, but the first
thing he asked me was what is
your favorite Dinosaur?
I don't even ******* know.
The ice breaker.
Yeah.
I did find an answer for him
though. And then he had an
answer I didn't recognize.
It was just like a little
running thing.
Factor of some country.
Is there one way? Is there a
generator where you can put in a
bunch of trigger words in it
all, like push them together?
Yeah, that is why it's called
businessnamegenerator.com.
How do you find?
Hot.
Social media security.
Hey, you know there's a chat
thing that we could use in
the meeting too?
To put the name.
I am there that you could use.
I don't know what you're talking
about, so if you click the hand.
Where it says raise your hand.
And then there's that little
conversation button. Click on
that like the The Little Bubble
Square thing with the.
Just say it.
Next to the left of that.
Yeah.
It tries up on Ms teams.
Just got the notification
on my phone.
Alright.
It only has to be a code name.
For the project, like a
project name and then the
app name can come later.
Yeah.
Well, you mean?
Socially secure, secure social.
There is a VPN to protect
my *** online.
Protect my *** online.
What's this app? Do you know it
protects my ship? Private
*** on Facebook.
Private Facebook. Yeah,
though I wouldn't call it
private *** on Facebook.
Revealed on Facebook.
Just I'm on. I'm taking this
medication that makes me really
tired right now, so I'm going to
be getting no help.
Spelling out gibberish.
Seamonkey Social Security.
Yeah, can you?
Yeah, you need to say it's a
working title. The working
time. Yeah, working title
without title when they
developed like Grand Theft
Auto online and stuff. They
didn't call it Grand Theft
Auto online.
The Xbox One with the new
Xbox when it was in
development was called
Scarlet.
Yeah, is it like Windows 7
code Longhorn or something?
I think there's some weirdness.
What do you put Mongoose and
Facebook together?
Mum book don't don't like that.
Just call it Mongoose
media. There you go.
Mongoose book.
A book of mongooses.
Face goose
my squash. My screws.
So cookie mongers.
My scarce rolls off the
Pokémon guys said we sell,
like bear, Mace, or Mongoose.
Pokémon.
Security settings OK.
Mongoose Aholic
nice 'cause you know it's it's a
Mace Mace spray that you use
other social media stuff and
stealing your **** yeah?
Medical social Mace
video social make security.
Mace security Mace.
Privacy.
Or we can just go with project
712 or just add some random
numbers at the end.
Just do that.
We just leave it. It's
project idea. Yeah, yeah,
we'll come up with the name.
I'm sorry I brought it up.
Will come up with a name
for it later.
In the next assignment, will
spend a whole 3 meetings trying
to pick an area.
Yeah, that's cool.
I'm gonna finish recording here
before I actually pass out.
Is there anything else?
No, I think that's it.